<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>The Morning After STL</title><link>https://www.tmastl.com/</link><description>The Morning After STL is the longest-running local sports morning show in St. Louis. Tim McKernan, Martin Kilcoyne, Doug Vaughn, and Jackson Burkett have the fortune of hosting the circus each morning from 7 a.m. to 11 a.m. -- LIVE on 101 ESPN Radio at 101.1 FM, https://101ESPN.com, https://TMASTL.com, TMASTL YouTube, The TMASTL app, and anywhere you find podcasts.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://megaphone.imgix.net/podcasts/c2c9a202-613d-11ed-93db-af2e32addf35/image/5053dbe40cb94b50d40a8f72b568161e.jpg?ixlib=rails-4.3.1&amp;max-w=3000&amp;max-h=3000&amp;fit=crop&amp;auto=format,compress</url><title>The Morning After STL</title><link>https://www.tmastl.com/</link></image><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 21:00:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>08-24-18 TMA Live Segment 1 Legendary "Name That Celeb" Game</title><description>TMA is Live from the Hotshots on Manchester in Ballwin. "Who said it?" A legendary edition of "Name That Celeb" game. Iggy's Drops of the Week.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7531256881.mp3?updated=1731088729" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 11:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-24-18 TMA Live Segment 2 Masters song sing-a-long and EMOTD!</title><description>The gang plays "Dead or Alive." Bertarelli Cuts of the Week. Tiger Trivia. The crowd sings the Masters song with Doug. EMOTD!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6793879238.mp3?updated=1731088784" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-29-18 Segment 3 Frank O. Pinion talks TMA emails and EMOTD</title><description>Frank O. Pinion talked about the TMA email he read on The Tim McKeranan Show. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2884542600.mp3?updated=1731088710" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-31-18 Segment 2 Columbia, MO is big this hour</title><description>Sliding into DM's. Talk of Columbia bars My House and Room 38. The Tri Delt house at Mizzou PLTD the program. House Mothers help keep fraternities in order. Iggy and Plow boy don't care who sees them naked. Iggy's Drops of the Week. Talk of Booches, The Diner, El Rancho, and other Columbia eating establishments. Iggy and Biff at the Tushy Booth.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5623116245.mp3?updated=1731088595" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-20-18 Segment 1 Have your mom drop you off at TMA Live tonight</title><description>Doug will be recording TMA for the next 9 hours. TMA Live at Hotshots on Dorsett tonight. Have your mom drop you off. Drop talk. Danny Mac gave a shout out to the Dotem's on the broadcast yesterday. Vaughn Index is 5.5 for the Cards. Graham Bensinger mentioned Tim on MLB Network last night. He is the latest guest on The Tim McKernan Show Podcast.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1781287746.mp3?updated=1670455924" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 12:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA-9-21-18 Seg 1 Live From Q in the Lou</title><description>Live from Q in the Lou. Doug's mic isn't on and Rochhio no where to be found. Plenty of wind and a guy throwing up. Big TMA Live last night. Cleveland Browns talk. Doug doesn't like beans. People showed up at Iggy's Patio last night for an impromptu party. Some lady stops by to talk BBQ. More strangers stop by. Boys beg for ribs, but they wont be ready for 4 or 5 hours. What's a good smoker. There are no ribs to be found. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5638417330.mp3?updated=1731088323" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 11:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 9-21-18 Seg 2 Some BBQ Talk and We Make Our Picks</title><description>Cat wants a Big Daddy Kane documentary. Pappy's BBQ stops by. Time for Iggy's Drops of the Week. Plowsy was really high last night. And Larry was smashed. Time for the Maggie O'Brien's Picks of the Week. Fan Dual posted a incorrect line and had to pay 82 grand in bets. Some Francessa sound. J Boyd dont play. Plowsy weighs 133 lbs. Another Francessa prank call. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2511320427.mp3?updated=1731089135" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 13:02:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 9-21-18 Seg 3 Lisa Ann Talks Fantasy Football and Stag</title><description>Lisa Ann joins us, and answers all of your fantasy questions. Bertareli Cuts of the Week, EMOTD! 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3434451101.mp3?updated=1731088249" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-28-18 Segment 1 TMA Live: Who Said It? Seinfeld Trivia</title><description>TMA Live recorded at the Dorsett Hotshots on 9/20/18.  The gang plays TMA Who Said It? and Seinfeld Trivia.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8231551888.mp3?updated=1670455916" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-28-18 Segment 2 TMA Live: Name That Tune, Cardinals Trivia, and EMOTD</title><description>TMA Live recorded at the Dorsett Hotshots on 9/20/18.  The gang plays Name That Tune and Cardinals Trivia. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8212398585.mp3?updated=1731088135" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-04-18 Segment 3 Columbia, IL has a big hour and EMOTD</title><description>Ride Her Cup price breakdown provided by Jay. Plowsy and the texters are going after each other. Plowsy says he is the power top and the listener is the bottom. Lern grew up in Columbia, IL...according to Iggy. Jeremy Piven is doing other shows in the area. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5109952372.mp3?updated=1731088039" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 14:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-09-18 Segment 1 Stingray may attend a TMA LIVE</title><description>Iggy will see A Star Is Born on Friday. Andrew Dice Clay shows his love in the movie. Tim and Stingray had a FB Live sesh last night. Stingray may come to a TMA Live. Uniform talk. Francesa is getting pranked on the app a lot. Grocery store discussion. Iggy eats raw meat sometimes.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8933137117.mp3?updated=1731087998" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 12:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-15-18 Segment 1 College Football Hour</title><description>Dan calls in to recap his trip to Tuscaloosa. Talk of the cuck studio. Mizzou football talk. Rough week for the Top 10. UCF playoff chances. Notre Dame has clearest path to playoff. Dissection of Mizzou v. Bama.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4096279529.mp3?updated=1731087970" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:05:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-16-18 Segment 1 Iggy's boy, Potter, will attend TMA Live next Thursday</title><description>The Cat brings up Elizabeth Warren very early in the morning. Paul Azinger will replace Johnny Miller in the booth. Working on a Stingray and Larry meeting. "I'm burying this damn Gamecock." Izzy texts in to hold Doug accountable. Potter Varley is attending the next TMA Live. Springfield, MO stories from Iggy. The starting 5 for the SMS women's basketball team is discussed.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9082213044.mp3?updated=1731087959" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-16-18 Segment 3 Iggy's pal, Lern, will attend TMA Live next Thursday. EMOTD.</title><description>The Cat has a "get off my lawn" take about scooters. Tim has breaking news: Lern will be at the TMA Live next Thursday. Iggy and Lern are just friends, guys. Iggy may or may not be on tilt about Lern attending TMA Live. Iggy invites the guys to the Potter Varley Christmas Party at the Ritz. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3225345168.mp3?updated=1731087927" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 14:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-26-18 TMA Live Segment 1 Iggy and Lern reunite and Potter is in the house</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in South County. Lern and Potter Varley join the program. Iggy's drops of the week. Who Said It?
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9317902556.mp3?updated=1731087708" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-26-18 TMA Live Segment 2 Lern and Tim play Rock &amp; Roll trivia and EMOTD</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in South County. Rock &amp; Roll trivia. More Lern and Potter. Bertarelli Cuts of the Week. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7811149585.mp3?updated=1731088656" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-9-18 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hotshots in O'Fallon, IL</title><description>Mike Lee sings Billie Jean. Larry is banty. Who Said It? Name that tune: Cable TV theme songs.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6426806331.mp3?updated=1731087413" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 12:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-9-18 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hotshots in O'Fallon, IL</title><description>Seinfeld Trivia. Blues Trivia. Natty Nate is sideways with Doug. Happy Birthday Mike Lee. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9839120510.mp3?updated=1731087413" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-26-18 Segment 1 Pies, Christmas Trees, and Sports</title><description>Chuck is dropping dimes from the point position. The guys break down pies. Real v. Fake Christmas Trees. Iggy begs for GoT DVD's. Iggy bashes The Match. Mizzou whipped Arky. Illini coaching sitch. Blues continue to mystify.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2969807158.mp3?updated=1731087179" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-29-18 Segment 2 Christmas movies, MLS, and Danny Mac</title><description>Is Die Hard a Christmas movie? Top 10 Christmas movies are discussed. College Football Playoff talk. MLS break-down. Danny Mac is awesome.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4444865590.mp3?updated=1731086855" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-20-18 TMA Seg 2 Movie Talk and Picks of the Week</title><description>Did Robyn Wright get naked in Forest Gump? We break down the movie. Then we break down School Ties. More movie talk. Time for the Maggie O'Brien's Picks of the Week. Big Al joins the Show. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9355525834.mp3?updated=1731090822" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 15:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-20-18 TMA Seg 3 Top New Restaurants of 2018. EMOTD</title><description>Mike Francessa gives his listeners some dead air while he thinks. Post Dispatch lists their top 10 new restaurants in 2018. Captains D's didn't make the list. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6246253661.mp3?updated=1731090738" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 16:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-21-18 TMA LIVE Segment 1 Christmas Trivia and Name That Artist</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in Fenton. Christmas Movie Trivia. Christmas edition of Name That Artist.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7639969790.mp3?updated=1731090765" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-21-18 TMA LIVE Segment 2 Foot Stuff and EMOTD</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots in Fenton. Foot stuff and EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5681282745.mp3?updated=1670455825" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-26-18 Segment 3 Best of TMA</title><description>Best of TMA from 10/31/18.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5776585706.mp3?updated=1670455823" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 15:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>1-2-19 Segment 2 Iggy has a big hour</title><description>Deke Dotem got married over the weekend. Las Vegas food suggestions. AVN travel arrangements are set. Riley Reid is Iggy's white wale. He would like to talk to a transsexual. The guys troubleshoot audio issues. Iggy is working on logistics to accept Lisa Ann's AVN awards. Plowsy is afraid to live in Las Vegas because of the cocaine. Iggy has a plan to avoid prostitution sting operations. Could the Cards be in the mix for Bryce Harper? Iggy calls Brandel Chamblee a curmudgeon. Mac's Local Eats is fire. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1658819343.mp3?updated=1731090389" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:23:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA-1-11-19 Seg 1 More Problems with the Loop Trolley and AVN Talk</title><description>Big win for the Blues last night. Gangster Pete is in the Hampton's. Mike did not have a good phone call. Iggy in no mood to screen calls today. Swope is a news hound. Swope is sideways with KSDK. The Loop Trolley is too big. A little Judy Garland talk. Big AVN Red Carpet news for Iggy and Biff. Tim took BP yesterday at Busch. Doug was a Home Run hitter in College. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5215198854.mp3?updated=1731090111" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 14:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 1-11-19 Seg 2  Iggy's Drops of the Week along with Francessa Sound</title><description>Iggy's Drops of the Week. Mike Francessa not happy with his callers. Listeners want betting tips. Donald Trump talks divorce. What would you do with 70 billion. Caller Adam joins the Show. How popular will the Ballpark Village Apartments be? 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9727136492.mp3?updated=1731090083" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 15:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 1-11-19 Seg 3 Cuts of the Week &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Cuts of the Week. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7256519362.mp3?updated=1731090015" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 16:02:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 1-14-19 Seg 1 AFC-NFC Championship Talk. Where will Harper Go.</title><description>Stan Kronke doesnt like anyone in the bathroom with him. The boys are rooting for anyone other than the Rams. Cat is just looking forward to Maroon 5. Our listeners are pulling for the Chiefs. Is it OK to steal signs? Doug wants productive emails. Tim will not be signing at Winter Warm-Up. Bob Nightengale thinks Bryce Harper is going to the Phillies. Minor League Ball Players need to be paid more. Win totals for MLB Teams in 2019. Cards are at 88 1/2. What can Tim expect at Cardinals Fantasy Camp. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6125846568.mp3?updated=1731090069" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 14:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 1-14-19 Seg 2 Francessa Sound. Are the Cards interested in Machado.</title><description>Some Francessa sound. Are the Cards the mystery team for Machado. Do you want a guy who doesnt run out ground balls. Some in Cardinal Nation dont believe the Cards have done enough in the off season. St Louis got almost 12 inches of snow. Tim was in Swansea when the snow hit. Cat shoveled his own driveway. Is Princess Fierce still sending the Fan Page a video. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2799748700.mp3?updated=1731090042" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 15:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA-1-14-19 Seg 3 Pitch Fork Mafia. EMOTD</title><description>Fred Rogan sound from L.A. Some Patriots talk. There is shoveling going on outside the building. Max Kellerman weighs in on Tom Brady. Fox NFL Pre Game Show vs CBS. Charles Davis is good on Fox NFL Games. Bradshaw and Jimmy Johnson are in their 70's. Walter Cronkite was forced to retire at 65. Tim discusses the mind set of Pitch Fork Mafia and the Joe Rogan podcast. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8312720894.mp3?updated=1731090044" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-21-19 Segment 2 Ela Darling makes her TMA debut</title><description>Iggy's Interview of the Week with Ela Darling presented by Danny Schwartz. The girls really love Iggy's interviews. Tim thought he forgot to record his conversation with Dexter Fowler yesterday. After golf with Jim Edmonds, he realized he did record it. Dexter had glowing words regarding the skipper. CPG talks shorts on the course. Boeheim car wreck.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7557629954.mp3?updated=1731089248" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-25-19 Segment 1 Lady Gaga Recap and TMA Live</title><description>Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper. Oscars recap. Iggy's suggestions. Doug pokes Iggy. Billy Porter wore a man dress. Was Spike Lee mad? Pat Sajak tweet. The Irishman is intriguing. TMA Live on March 7th will be a pony. Win dinner with Doug. First 50 get a Doug t-shirt. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4488571957.mp3?updated=1731089209" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-01-19 Segment 2 Honda Classic and TMA Live logistics</title><description>Tim took his son to the Honda Classic. Tim loved it. Dad talk. Honda talk. Draft Kings. TMA Live logistics. Iggy sniping porn stars on Twitter. Big Al contributes.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5513447748.mp3?updated=1731089073" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 15:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-05-19 Segment 3 TMA voted best show in the entire world and EMOTD</title><description>This show has been voted best in the world. No-name Champion. Honda Classic talk. Adam Long got his invite to The Masters. He's an upcoming guest on The Tim McKernan Show. Anna Benson and Iggy's relationship is revisited. Iggy doesn't think he would be good with kids. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6321680888.mp3?updated=1731089059" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-08-19 TMA LIVE Segment 1 Doug Vaughn Trivia</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots in O'Fallon, IL. Doug Vaughn trivia highlights this segment of radio brilliance.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9922743218.mp3?updated=1731088792" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-08-19 TMA Live Segment 2 Win a date with Doug and EMOTD</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots in O'Fallon, IL. It's time to date Doug. The Doug dinner date contest. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2906688221.mp3?updated=1731088785" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 14:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-21-19 Segment 1 TMA Fan Pin Membership Drive</title><description>Tim interviewed PGA golfer Adam Long for The Tim McKernan Show. Iggy can't refrain from commenting on other men's wives on FB. Florida golf swing. Fan Pin Membership Drive. Lena Paul is Iggy's porn guest. Shrewsbury Seminary Student wants to date Lucas. Women are joining the Pin at an unprecedented pace. Mayor of Lower Arnold calls in. The Dotem logistics. California Bill calls in for a weather report.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6540535901.mp3?updated=1731088251" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 12:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-28-19 Segment 3 Autumn Falls makes her TMA debut and EMOTD</title><description>Plowsy wants Kaden and Manuel to come to a TMA Live. Steve in Dogtown calls in to talk sex at weddings and baseball. He will Venmo for rolls that Cards win 100 games. Autumn Falls is the subject of Iggy's AVN interview. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8465819860.mp3?updated=1731087753" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-29-19 Segment 2 TMA History</title><description>Cardinals trivia. Drops of the Week. Fescoe and Barrett are fondly remembered. Tim tells the Doug origin story. TMA History.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9889262025.mp3?updated=1731087733" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 13:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>04-24-19 Segment 3 Get your TMA drip at insideSTL Shop</title><description>insideSTL Shop is shipping shirts. Iggy can't believe Ellen won't go out with him. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9650957006.mp3?updated=1731086815" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 14:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>05-31-19 TMA LIVE with Lisa Ann Segment 1</title><description>TMA LIVE recorded 5/29/19 at Hotshots in Fenton. Lisa Ann is live with Tim and Jay Jr. The guys catch up with Lisa Ann and Blues trivia.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3094106446.mp3?updated=1731091009" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 11:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>05-31-19 TMA LIVE with Lisa Ann Segment 2</title><description>TMA LIVE recorded 5/29/19 at Hotshots in Fenton. Lisa Ann is live with Tim and Jay Jr. Lisa Ann's casting couch and EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3076564603.mp3?updated=1731090981" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 11:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-05-19 Segment 1 TMA is a national brand</title><description>Chara has a broken jaw. The dais feels bad for him. Iggy got punched on the button for kissing another man's gal. Doug was on WEEI in Boston. The dais was featured on Barstool Radio. TMA is a national brand. Montana talk and Bozeman weather report. Caller Ellen holds Plowtake accountable.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2003201438.mp3?updated=1731090889" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 12:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-06-19 Segment 3 Tony Luftman, D-Day Tribute, and EMOTD</title><description>NHL Network's Tony Luftman joins the program. Game 5 discussion ensues. 75th Anniversary of D-Day. Diary from D-Day. Iggy spins a yarn about love lost. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5713116791.mp3?updated=1731090843" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 14:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-27-19 Segment 2 The Roman Empire is big this hour</title><description>Fan Pin Championship expansion? Iggy tells a story about Susan Anspach.  Andy Dick slept in Prod Joe's hotel room. Iggy is a big fan of the Roman Empire. He doesn't know the years. A Roman Empire history lesson ensues. Who's Joy Anime? 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9894131849.mp3?updated=1731091548" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 13:05:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-28-19 Segment 1 Amateur hour</title><description>Tim tries a new delivery. Doug is not a fan. Jersey Shore break down. Amateur night recap. Shildt comments led to Cat attacks. Cardinals discussion.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7142849388.mp3?updated=1670455534" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 12:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-15-19 Segment 1 Science hour: Climate change</title><description>The Cat is back. Tim is on vacation. The Cardinals are hot. Iggy would babysit for Tim if asked. Iggy watched Our Planet and is a climate expert now. Rick calls in to talk cow farts. Biff doesn't believe in bovine flatulates. Biff is going "brown."  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2543875690.mp3?updated=1670455519" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 12:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-25-19 Segment 3 Iggy's birthday celebration is at TMA LIVE tonight and EMOTD</title><description>Iggy's place is going to be a who's who of STL after TMA LIVE tonight. USMNT will play Uruguay at Busch. It's Iggy's birthday today. Bring gifts. Dillion digs the Igg. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3788918467.mp3?updated=1731089494" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 14:07:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-26-19 TMA LIVE Segment 1 with Dillion Harper</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots on Dorsett. Dillion Harper joins the show to celebrate Iggy's Birthday and the show's 15th anniversary. Caddyshack Trivia. Ask Dillion Anything.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1336135820.mp3?updated=1731089556" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 12:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-26-19 TMA LIVE Segment 2 with Carlie Lawrence, more Dillion, and EMOTD</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots on Dorsett. Blues in-game host Carlie Lawrence joins the program. Foot stuff with Jr. More Dillion. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8892203375.mp3?updated=1731089487" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-29-19 Segment 1 TMA Live and Iggy's patio party were lit</title><description>TMA Live was up for snatch grabs on Thursday. Leo had grass from Mars. 35-40 people showed up at Iggy's patio party. Iggy and Biff went to see Dillion at the Hustler Club. Biff's crib is tight. Leo was handing out usb cards with Dillion "scenes." Fan Pin Club Championship update. Iggy was eliminated from the FPCC after an epic choke job. Doug is not here for it. Iggy fires off a few excuses. Don't sleep on Peg Boy. The new Swope ep is his best. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6259561633.mp3?updated=1731089469" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 12:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-04-19 Segment 1 The Appliance Discounters 7 O'Clock Hour gets chippy</title><description>Dipped in gooold! Press conference Wednesday. J Flare is enfuego. Doug reads a Shildt quote. The Cards are hot! Francesa may be accepting a reduced role soon. Drop boy drops heat. Iggy loves cracked pepper. All insideSTLshop.com gear is in stock. Iggy v. The Cat. The Cat v. Plowsy. Bantyism abounds. Giovanny Gallegos is at the center of it all. Iggy left the Fan Pin.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7435061896.mp3?updated=1731088638" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 12:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-05-19 Segment 2 Sorry, dawg, #cartgate, and TMA Court</title><description>Cubs pen is struggling. Jay will be in tomorrow to discuss Cart Gate. The $1000 bet is discussed. Cart Gate explained. Sorry, dawg. TMA Court at the Improv Shop will resolve all TMA-related cases. Iggy likes to be teased. Text me and I'll talk dirty to you. The lie detector bet is picking up steam. Doug can't tell the cats from the dawgs.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9028621354.mp3?updated=1731089154" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-19-19 Segment 2 MIZZOU Stingray is back on TMA</title><description>Larry Nickel's intro to the defunct 6 AM hour. Stingray calls in. He has lost 75 pounds. Stingray describes his weight loss journey. He has the energy and want-to to record some more college football rants. Stingray breaks down the state of college football. MIZ-ZOU!!! Back to QFTA...Does Plowboy really get high at work at every day? What happened to the lovable, laid back Plowsy? Would Plowhawk quit smoking if it would save his relationship?
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6543937929.mp3?updated=1731088220" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 13:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-26-19 Segment 1 TMA LIVE tonight, Cards hanging on, and brilliant producers</title><description>TMA Live at Hotshots in Edwardsville tonight. Doug is panicking. Former gang members have given up a life of crime to watch baseball on YouTube. Cards B-team lineup is discussed. The new AVN Magazine has a Gabbie Carter spread. Fan Pin update. Gangster Pete's mic issues are addressed.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5498247562.mp3?updated=1670455336" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 12:06:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-27-19 Segment 1 TMA Live with Larry Nickel</title><description>TMA Live from the Edwardsville Hotshots. Larry Nickel makes his glorious return. Plowsy and Natty Nate challenge Da Garbage Disposal. WWE Trivia.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8783965446.mp3?updated=1731087975" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 11:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-27-19 Segment 2 TMA Live with Larry Nickel</title><description>TMA Live from the Edwardsville Hotshots. Larry interviews a Hotshots waitress. The Post presents Iggy's Drops of The Week. Iggy's Cuts of the Week. Who said it? A surprise for Larry.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7919006955.mp3?updated=1731087956" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 11:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-24-19 Segment 1 TMA Live, social media posturing, and threesomes</title><description>TMA LIVE tonight at Hotshots in South County. Sassy Cassie will be in the house. The Cat will eat wings during that segment. Plowsy is prepared for the herb to hit. Does Plowsy hide during TMA events? Caller Adam is bringing a Gameboy tonight. It's very sad when people have to post on FB to get laid. Apparently, this is a polarizing topic. Mr. and Mrs. Jones talk threesomes. Plowsy is still learning new positions. Texters take over.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8270239493.mp3?updated=1731087347" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 12:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-25-19 TMA LIVE Segment 1 from Hotshots in South County</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots in South County. Halloween Trivia. Horror Movie Trivia. Mike Lee sings Billy Jean. Larry Nickel receives a Championship Belt. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6116190065.mp3?updated=1731087295" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 11:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-25-19 TMA LIVE Segment 2 from Hotshots in South County</title><description>TMA LIVE from Hotshots in South County. Sassy Cassie joins the show. The Doug Vaughn Costume contest. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2311590348.mp3?updated=1731087278" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-01-19 Segment 1 South City and the TMA movie</title><description>Plowsy and Iggy are out. Rock is in. We pray for the return of our fallen producers. Halloween recap. The St. Louis Hills is prime trick or treating territory. Doug has a laughing fit from his own bad joke. South City talk. Tik Tok and other media platforms. Theft is discussed. Original gangstas. Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. The Irishman is out. TMA movie is in the works. Everybody loves the backup quarterback.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1598996837.mp3?updated=1731087131" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 12:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-01-19 Segment 2 The TMA movie script develops further</title><description>Phil Maroon is on a heater. TMA movie is picking up steam. Mizzou can't lose this week. They can do plenty of that next week in Athens. A lady was killed by a snakes in house full of snakes. Producer Joe is listening to the program. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8866180281.mp3?updated=1731087109" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 13:09:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-13-19 Segment 3 Katie Nolan hour and EMOTD</title><description>insidestlshop.com update. Katie Nolan no-shows due to technical difficulties. Iggy is happy. Prod Joe is mad. Mizzou lost to Xavier. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8861911296.mp3?updated=1731086696" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 16:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-13-19 Segment 2 Get Gash to TMA Live and Picks</title><description>Listeners are bringing toilet paper to the studio. Biff calls in for a series of non sequiturs. Get Gash to TMA Live. Maggie O's Picks of the Week.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1315512419.mp3?updated=1731090866" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-18-19 Segment 2 TMA Live tomorrow in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live tomorrow night in St. Charles. The STL Today makeover is sharp. Doug is watching impeachment prostests on his phone during the show. Odom to Arkansas and a RB is following him. A concert of olds is coming to Busch. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5813991699.mp3?updated=1731090802" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-19-19 Segment 1 TMA got a 360 machine and Lern got a present from Iggy</title><description>TMA is live from Hotshots in St. Charles. A 360 machine has been gifted to TMA. Exciting times. Shelby Lynn Gash will be in attendance at TMA Live tonight...maybe (it's a long drive). Bring an unwrapped toy for Friends of Kids with Cancer. Iggy got Lern a Christmas present. The Blues are ballin'. Daddy Padre gives Blues shooters confidence. Cardinals hot stove talk. MLB jerseys will have a Nike swoosh. Doug loves it. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5524095581.mp3?updated=1731091535" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-20-19 Segment 1 TMA LIVE from Hotshots in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles. Shelby Lynn Gash joins the show. Foot stuff attempt. Dead or Alive trivia. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4859896818.mp3?updated=1731092123" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 13:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-20-19 Segment 2 TMA LIVE from Hotshots in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles. More Shelby Lynn Gash. Name that Artist - Christmas Edition. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9876937195.mp3?updated=1731090760" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 13:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-24-19 Segment 3 Christmas cuck and EMOTD</title><description>Ryan Kelley. Christmas cuck is a popular search today. What's the most popular search on Christmas? Blues have 54 points. A special QFTA with the dais. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1065566421.mp3?updated=1731091526" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 16:04:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 1 1-10-20 Cards Are Dealing</title><description>Radio used to be just reading scores. The Cards are dealing. Doug gives a scouting report on the Cards new lefty. Doug doesn't want to trade prospects. Are the Cards interested in Ozuna. Blues win last night. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6597471141.mp3?updated=1731090548" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:06:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 2 1-10-20 We've Done Nothing With Our Lives</title><description>A little Royal Family talk. Tim is interviewing listeners family members. If someone interviews us when we're 90, we will realize we did nothing with our lives. Cat changed a water filter yesterday. Some Barstool Chicks sound. Denise Richards hooking up with Brandi Glanville. Drops of the Week. Iggy doing Petes job today. Frontenac doesn't have peep shows. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9978543979.mp3?updated=1731091087" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 15:07:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 3 1-10-20 Picks of the Week, Cuts of the Week and EMOTD</title><description>Our listeners dont live in rich neighborhoods. Maggie O's Picks of the Week. Cuts of the Week. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3837982314.mp3?updated=1731091085" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 1 1-13-20 Arenado Rumors are Swirling</title><description>Doug rants on the Texans blowing a 24 point lead. Who roots for the Chiefs. Any chance Arenado comes to St Louis. What players would be involved in the trade. Some dork on the fanpage said he knew where Joshua is located. David Perron added to the All Star roster. Oscar nominations are out. AVN's awards are up in the air. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1828464556.mp3?updated=1731090443" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 2 1-13-20 Plowsy wears a youth XL and Vagina Candles</title><description>Marshawn Lynch says farewell. Players need to take care of their money. Hard to believe guys can last 10 years in the NFL. Plowsy wears a youth XL t shirt. When he stretches his pubes show. Recovering Alcoholic in Belleville has a podcast.  100 years ago people weren't overweight. We haven't done it in a while, so we break down our favorite deli. A chick goes to Hedo without her girlfriend. Paltrow selling candles that smell like her vagina. Zack Zane wearing his Grandpa's jockstrap. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7162444112.mp3?updated=1670455093" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 15:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Seg 3 1-13-20 Zack Zane and EMOTD</title><description>Plowsy's headphones are too heavy. Tim's MRI update. Zack Zane bangs a lot of guys. Plowsy's pants are un-bled. Plowsy and Iggy have cost Normandie 7 grand over the past 3 years according to an emailer. Only 3 emails today. emotd.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5304203007.mp3?updated=1731090404" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 16:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-04-20 Segment 1 TMA scores a lot of points this segment</title><description>The Blues did it again. 8 in a row. The new points system for EMOTD. The new prize is tight. Broadway Oyster Bar is delish. Cardinals Spring Training update. Astros get heckled everywhere they go.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5124509113.mp3?updated=1731089121" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 14:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-12-20 Segment 1 A lot has changed in the last 24 hours</title><description>A lot has changed in the last 24 hours. Coronavirus discussion. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7908825649.mp3?updated=1731089055" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 12:09:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-13-20 Segment 3 TMA is a wildlife show now and EMOTD</title><description>Daddy Padre will continue to not play for the Blues during the pandemic. The dais looks up random animal facts. Cuts of the Week. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7575213475.mp3?updated=1731088950" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 14:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-16-20 Segment 1 TMA grinds on</title><description>High school basketball is still happening. TMA is still grinding. O/U we'll be back to normal by May 9th. The latest on the coronavirus is discussed. Its a rough time for gamblers. Where are the tests? Everybody is worried about local businesses.  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8823912731.mp3?updated=1731088950" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 12:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-05-20 Segment 2 TMA dolls, drops, and Francesa</title><description>Akoostic Sessions. Pepper &amp; Genie logistics. Iggy doll loaded with drops is a big idea. Doug's doll would get abused. Recovering Alcoholic's wife. Brad calls in to praise the show. More directional discussion. Iggy's Drops of the Week. Francesa on how to name a horse. It makes Iggy mad. It's raining everywhere. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1578316305.mp3?updated=1731087318" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-09-20 Segment 1 FPCC, MLB, and TMA "athletes"</title><description>The Cat couldn't sleep due to FPCC excitement. Chick, dame, toots. PGA Draft Kings is back. Iggy's weather forecast. Iggy's aunt was a lesbian gun runner with a girlfriend named Twink. MLB discussion. Plowsy is a mouse killer. Who is the best athlete on TMA? Iggy is pretty sure it is him. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4093104310.mp3?updated=1731087282" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 12:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-10-20 Segment 2 Big hour for Christina Kim</title><description>The studio bathroom is in disrepair. Iggy ogles Christina Kim who has lost weight. Ryan Kelley joins the show. Who does Iggy use? Koi ponds. The show is on adderall. Dillion Harper. Iggy tweeted at Kim to visit his sister...9 years ago. Bob Costas? Lady Gaga. Iggy struggles to say "quid pro quo." Plowsy ate at San Jose. West County Mall looks to be in trouble. Drive In concert and movie venue. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6742703908.mp3?updated=1731087225" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 13:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-15-20 Segment 1 He was just an old perv. Iggy has a big hour.</title><description>The Cardinals scrimmage last night was so boring. Iggy cried during an old Christmas movie last night. Iggy is good at geography. Iggy is banty about his internet service. Draft Kings. Somebody is threatening to out my sex club visits. The dais explains internet to Iggy. Iggy talks balls. Dirty debutantes. Coming out parties. Ed powers liked to have sex with his black socks on. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9769633652.mp3?updated=1731091331" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 12:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-28-20 Segment 1 TMA goes international</title><description>Tim thinks he's an underdog in the FPCC. Tim has a WHOOP. Iggy has a lot of unboxing to do. Is today dildo day? Maybe butt plug day? Find out at noon today. Cherie DeVille sent Iggy a Birthday cameo. Amber Cezanne takes TMA international. June Ann and Iggy are heating up. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3118418841.mp3?updated=1731090913" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 12:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>7-31-20 TMA Seg 1Butt Plug and Blow</title><description>Pete off and Iggy is having trouble with the podcast. Tim having Wisdom teeth pulled. More listeners getting cucked. Tim paid for Lesbians in Vegas. Iggy stole his girlfriends roommate.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5004843323.mp3?updated=1731090745" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 12:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>7-31-20 TMA Seg 2 - Cards Game Postponed due to Positive Covid Test</title><description>Iggy posted Seg 1-Butt Plugs and Blow to The Cat Chat Podcast. Dear Diedra. The studio fly is still around. The pandemic has increased threesomes. John Heyman reports Cards game postponed due to positive Covid test.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5608421615.mp3?updated=1731090686" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>7-31-20 TMA Seg 3- Cuts of the Week. Multiple Cards test positive. EMOTD.</title><description>Jethro Tull is the 9 o'clock hour song. Cat will be back on Mon. Cuts of the Week. Multiple Cardinals test positive. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2673327069.mp3?updated=1731090738" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 14:02:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-28-20 Segment 3 Lisa Ann, The TMA House, and EMOTD</title><description>Lisa Ann joins the show. Foot stuff. LA talks NYC. Mike Lee joins the show. LA talks stag bubbles. Big Al invites LA to Lake St. Louis. LA may move to STL and ope the TMA House. Lisa Ann talks about filming cuck scenes. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5142492496.mp3?updated=1731090006" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-14-20 Segment 1 A banty hour of radio</title><description>Call in big man. Arozarena looks a little like Willie Mays. Tim was on The Stingray Show. Doug guesses golf courses. Draft Kings Showdown will be tomorrow. Iggy is upset he has to cut out the names of players in the field in the CJ Cup. Iggy is cooking wahoo at 5 on FB Live. Iggy v. Prod Joe: Round one million. 360 Machine. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6847996007.mp3?updated=1731089366" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 12:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-16-20 TMA Seg 1 $16.000 Raised for Jack and Dan Caesar Column</title><description>Pete is in the Hamptons, so Iggy in charge of the Podcast. Iggy says the Lemmings Open could be chili. The listeners and others have raised $16.000 for one of our listeners. Help Us Have Jacks Back on Go Fund Me. We discuss today's article in the Post Dispatch by Dan Ceaser. Frank Opinion will be leaving the Station in 2 weeks. Tiffany Smooth joins the Show. Iggy has never paid for a hooker.10-16-210-1
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2585833500.mp3?updated=1731089285" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 12:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-16-20 TMA Seg 2-Drops of the Week &amp; Can Iggy Upload the Podcast.</title><description>Iggy having trouble uploading the Podcast. Former Cardinals are raking. Doug misses the old time announcers. Drops of the Week. Tim and Doug tell Jack Buck stories. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6793652050.mp3?updated=1731089228" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 13:06:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-16-20 TMA Seg 3 Lisa Ann, Cuts of the Week and EMOTD</title><description>Lisa Ann joins us for 2 part questions. Do guys grow a winter bush. Cuts of the Week. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1358384037.mp3?updated=1731089222" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-27-20 Segment 1 Ripper story hour</title><description>Cam joins Tim and Doug. Cam had a rough experience at Glen Echo yesterday. Who are the best Blues golfers? Cam and Strick's podcast is blowing up. They are big in Canada. DP calls in because he loves Cam. Mike Lee calls in to brag about his roster. Adam Long joining the show at 9. Ben Fred on Molina and Cards. Tim and Cam talk rippers. Iggy tells a sex story. Cam got bored and left. Nicksy's WWE Report. Cam knows guys in the 500 club. Iggy was being used for sex in Bermuda. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8488390180.mp3?updated=1731089136" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 12:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-02-20 Segment 1 Murphy's Law strikes TMA</title><description>Tim had to get a COVID test, so he is broadcasting from home. His internet is down, so he is joining the show through the phone. Murphy's Law at play here. John calls into The Doug Vaughn Show. W. Earl Brown was on Biff &amp; Show. Tim is back! Doug took advantage of absentee balloting. He didn't wait 5 seconds. Political discourse. Iggy is really trying to stir the pot. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2303557987.mp3?updated=1731088983" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 14:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-02-20 Segment 1 Prod Joe story hour</title><description>Prod Joe joins the show with Tim and Doug. TMA producing history. Prod Joe passes judgement immediately upon meeting people. Stories of TMA past. Barrett stories. Prod Joe on his ass. Prod Joe on Iggy. Prod Joe's boxing career. Iggy v. Prod Joe golf match. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3257132985.mp3?updated=1731088048" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 14:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-18-20 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles. TMA Trivia. Drops of the week.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2840185389.mp3?updated=1731087613" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 14:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-18-20 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hotshots St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots St. Charles. Guess (and rate) that celebrity foot. Christmas Vacation Trivia. Bertarelli Cuts of the Week. EMOTD
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3557032806.mp3?updated=1731087534" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 15:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 1 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4781072652.mp3?updated=1731087377" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 2 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1785246848.mp3?updated=1731087385" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 14:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 3 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5440733972.mp3?updated=1731087326" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 4 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6160713859.mp3?updated=1670454061" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 5 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3404350480.mp3?updated=1731087360" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-28-20 Segment 6 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following game 6 of the 2011 World Series. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8693160034.mp3?updated=1731087309" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 16:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-29-20 Segment 1 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following the Blues Stanley Cup victory.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6508788887.mp3?updated=1731087343" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 14:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-29-20 Segment 2 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following the Blues Stanley Cup victory.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2860713779.mp3?updated=1731087314" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 15:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-29-20 Segment 3 TMA Classic</title><description>Relive TMA following the Blues Stanley Cup victory.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4215467340.mp3?updated=1731087324" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 16:06:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>01-14-21 Segment 2 Advice hour</title><description>Greatest sitcoms of all time. Friends. Ellen. Porky's. Madonna kissing celebs. Trash on 170 north. Did Justin Timberlake get cucked? Rich Gould. Dan joins the program. His uncle is flirting with his wife. Breaking it all down. Texters are banty. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4233184736.mp3?updated=1731086830" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 15:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-10-21 Segment 1 Variety hour</title><description>Cold in the Lou today. We will power through. Lunardi. COVID in Columbia. Sex scene in CoMo. People celebrating their families loss of virginity. StrodeCast. MoDot continues to fumble the bag. Icebergs. Iggy is a scientist. Ice truck. Spiders. Mice. The Prod Joe vs Iggy chronicles continue. Pebble Beach preview. Phone numbers. Iggy vs. texters. Does the tournament field suck? Tim's shoulder and sleeping position. Jackson sleeps face down. What percentage of couples watch porn together? Iggy has advice for an audience member. Iggy spins a yarn. Doug's Glue Guzzler. Swinging. Nikki Glaser. Cletus. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9169143878.mp3?updated=1731091270" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 14:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-11-21 Segment 2 Golden hour</title><description>Presidents day song. Zachary Taylor... not the kid from Home Improvement. Fan page mad about callers. Texters sending in photos. Golden hour. Green flash. Sunsets. Plowsy had never seen the ocean before his trip to spring training. Tom Brady got a little boozy at the parade yesterday. Body painting at Hedo. STL Business Journal has more about the NFL lawsuit. Eric Grubman no-showed his deposition. The town hall meetings. NFL may be scared. St. Louis could handle at least 3 NFL teams. Cool Valley Cools. Big Al. Cooking with Ken. Chargers. NFL in London. Ursula. Iggy vs. Doug is now underway. More Ursula talk. Hedo ladies. Grossmutter.  Texters sending in pictures of themselves. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1025205762.mp3?updated=1731091571" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 15:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-05-21 Segment 1 TMA safari, Work, and Francesa</title><description>Doug is banty about the Redbirds. Update from Bay Hill. Cookin with Ken. Ursla Smiley. StrodeCast. Outback animals. "A dingo ate my baby!" Hippos. Bob Welch's wife. Update on the Mungenast DK Showdown. Iggy's research. Doug is not pleased with this research. What is work? Doug and Iggy get sideways. Mike Francesa audio. Golf picks. Online poker. Prod Joe is listening. Once again, what is work? Work by Rihanna.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2915505075.mp3?updated=1731091540" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 14:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-15-21 Segment 2 TMA Awards</title><description>One voice was heard. Iggy has been named as a finalist for Best Radio Personality in St. Louis Magazine. TMA is a finalist for Best Show. Tim and Doug are finalists for Best Sports Anchor. Somehow, 1380 the Woman is a finalist for Best Radio Station. This contest is becoming more suspect as we read more finalists. StrodeCast. Iggy doesn't have a passion for meteorology, but he is just great at it. 360 machines. Dear Deidre article. Hrabe has a new audio creation, coming up. Dicky V. Spring breakers in NY Post and an interesting photo within the article. Forest Hills. 1380 the Woman. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6876498084.mp3?updated=1731090650" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:06:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-24-21 Segment 2 TMA Shark Tank</title><description>Ween Wednesday, good dog fluffy. Dell Tech Match Play update. Raptors. Audio from NHL refs wanting to call a penalty on the Predators. Mafia. Dr. Oz getting backlash after hosting Jeopardy.  Burt Reynolds. TMA Shark Tank. Jackson's movie review website. Lemmings. The same ref caught on the hot mic was fired. Sports cheating movies. Charlie Sheen. Charcoal House. Swinging conventions. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8125303877.mp3?updated=1731091109" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 13:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>03-31-21 Segment 1 Variety hour</title><description>UCLA, wow. Mizzou, shame they can't #Survive and #Advance. Boat raced. The StrodeCast is undefeated. FPCC update. Hrabe vs. Strode. Fantasy baseball. What constitutes a Hoosier.  Lady Gaga. 09 Sports recap. Tyler Hansbrough. Leaf blowers. Gabbie Carter. Valero Texas Open preview.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2710496492.mp3?updated=1731090400" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 12:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>04-23-21 Segment 1 TMA Star Search</title><description>SGO Angel Julia will be on at 9:05. Blues lose another one last night. Mungenast DFS Showdown update. Cardinals homestand. SGO Julia. Doug is fed up with SGO nonsense. Iggy brought in some fish. Iggy can't change the radio. Towing cars. SGO Julia and Jackson? Are we jealous of SGO Kai. Is there more young money in STL or Miami? Gabbie Carter. Neil Allen Craig Paquette joins the program to give a state of the Fan Page address. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5189909587.mp3?updated=1731089974" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 12:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>05-11-21 Segment 2 Advice hour</title><description>Ryan Kelley joins the program. Kenny Mayne gone from ESPN after 27 years. Iggy has thoughts on podcasts. Iggy vs. Terri. The poor side of Manchester. Jeff joins the program for advice on his wife's possible infidelity. Should Jeff hire a private investigator? Snapchat. What's up with Facebook marketing? 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7222254481.mp3?updated=1731089506" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 13:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>05-17-21 Segment 2 TMA Trading Cards</title><description>Cards got swept. Iggy asks a favor from the listeners. Ken Reitz. Baseball cards. TMA trading cards. Blues-Avs tonight. The Blues may be without Perron. The rarest TMA trading cards. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7683469099.mp3?updated=1731089287" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 13:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-18-21 Segment 1 Best Of TMA Live</title><description>Enjoy some of the best moments and segments of TMA Live!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1756777248.mp3?updated=1731088646" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-18-21 Segment 2 Best Of TMA Live</title><description>Enjoy some of the best moments and segments of TMA Live!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1588503589.mp3?updated=1731088642" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-18-21 Segment 3 Best Of TMA Live</title><description>Enjoy some of the best moments and segments of TMA Live!
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5769136874.mp3?updated=1731088629" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-28-21 Segment 2 TMA History and Buck Swope</title><description>Rain coming in, heads up! Joe Strauss. Iggy's guest booking ability. Tim's show with Edmonds. Hall of Fame of shows. TMA history. HBO Max. Buck Swope audio postcard. The more popular MMF. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7806995595.mp3?updated=1731088571" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-30-21 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live from Hotshots in St. Charles. Olympics trivia. Iggy's Drops of the Week. TMA Who said it trivia. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7514870994.mp3?updated=1731088097" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-30-21 Segment 2 TMA Live at Hotshots in St. Charles</title><description>TMA Live at Hotshots in St. Charles. Chicken wing eating contest. Cuts of the Week. Name that Movie trivia. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1923397184.mp3?updated=1731088815" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-27-21 Segment 2 TMA QFTA</title><description>Mark Hannah joins us to drop some knowledge. Iggy's Drops of the Week. What would Iggy's podcast format be? Iggy's straight to the web interviews. The Cat and Ted Danson. StrodeCast. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3816235420.mp3?updated=1731087648" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 13:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>08-31-21 Segment 1 A Magical Hour of Radio</title><description>Text line antics. Cal May questions. Jackson's Tinder FFF proposals. Great drops. Mount Rushmore of appetizers. Iggy v. Hrabe golf match. St. Gabe's golf tournament. Iggy will go gay for pay. A lot of people talking. Larry Nickel joins us for the WWE Recap, brought to you by The Post. Foot candidates' texting in. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2031079596.mp3?updated=1731087617" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 12:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-03-21 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hot Shots O'Fallon, IL</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots O'Fallon, IL! Featuring a breakdown of the Iggy v. Hrabe match, Guess Iggy's musical artist, and Drops of the Week.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2893551622.mp3?updated=1731088810" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>09-03-21 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hot Shots O'Fallon, IL</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots O'Fallon, IL! Featuring TMA Trivia, Cuts of the Week, a Foot Fetish Friday, and EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2395449747.mp3?updated=1670453295" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-01-21 Segment 1 TMA Live at Hot Shots Webster Groves</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots Webster Groves. Featuring TV Theme Music Trivia, Iggy's Drops of the Week, and Uniquely Named Athlete Trivia.  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7489521111.mp3?updated=1731087000" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-01-21 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hot Shots Webster Groves</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots Webster Groves! Featuring Iggy's Foot Fetish Friday, Cuts of the Week, and a wing eating contest. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3499920141.mp3?updated=1731086987" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 10-11-21 Seg 2 Rams Lawsuit News and Iggy Has a Big Week Ahead</title><description>Mike Florio has more news on the Rams lawsuit. Hrabe joins the show. Iggy calls out listeners and wants to take them on in golf. Iggy has a big week ahead. Listeners don't want Skip Berkmeyer to help Iggy with his putting.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9724454042.mp3?updated=1731086678" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 13:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA 10-11-21 Seg 3 College Football Talk. Mental Health Discussion.</title><description>Gabe's post game show goes off the rails again. National Championship talk. Mental Health discussion. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9149038144.mp3?updated=1731086649" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 13:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-26-21 Segment 2 The Iggy Hour</title><description>Gloria! Ryan Kelley joins us on this fine Tuesday morning. StrodeCast. Where is Oakville? Iggy upset nobody is working at Dunkin Donuts. Gobble Bowl logistics. Hrabe struts into the studio. "You wanna know how Ken spells Venti". Hrabe with a flat tire story. Ken banty about Hrabe's predicament. Hrabe breaks down the Blues win. Fan Page issues. Iggy's eating situation. Things go off the rails. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9523877764.mp3?updated=1731091461" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-28-21 Segment 3 Comedy Bits, TMA Live, and EMOTD</title><description>Iggy takes a requests from Action Jackson for Greta Van Fleet. Iggy and Hrabe do a bit. As you can imagine, it goes poorly. Scott's Wrinkled Ballsack has announced he will be there. Iggy says he would like to have an MMF. Iggy says he is different off the air then on the radio. An article about a gentleman dumping during sex. The dais has thoughts. Mark Hannah joins us. Mark requests for a Jewel update. The Iggy costume contest. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9798038762.mp3?updated=1731091393" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-29-21 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hot Shots Maryland Heights</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots in Maryland Heights! Featuring Horror Movie Trivia, Drops of the Week, TMA Who Said It (Halloween Edition), The Iggy Costume Contest, and Cuts of the Week. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2356138741.mp3?updated=1731091431" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-29-21 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hot Shots Maryland Heights</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots in Maryland Heights! Featuring a Wing Eating Contest, a Foot Fetish Friday with Jewel, and EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7647882285.mp3?updated=1731091368" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-10-21 Segment 2 Drops and TMA Karaoke</title><description>Gloria! Doug thinks they should bring that tune back. Iggy's Drops of the Week. Our favorite truck stops. Pancakes and waffles. Iggy got Lern a gift. The boys sing some Christmas tunes. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6099554523.mp3?updated=1731090592" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-17-21 Segment 1 TMA Live from Hot Shots Fenton</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots in Fenton! Featuring Christmas Vacation Trivia, Drops of the Week, and TMA Who Said It Trivia. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3029002097.mp3?updated=1670452999" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-17-21 Segment 2 TMA Live from Hot Shots Fenton</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Hot Shots in Fenton! Featuring a Wing Eating Contest, Foot Fetish Friday, Cuts of the Week, and Hrabe's audio postcard. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4505746446.mp3?updated=1731090487" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>01-20-22 Segment 1 TMA Boy Band</title><description>Tamm Avenue Capital Partners. Gape. StrodeCast. Florida real estate. Iggy brought in some salmon. Fish in the microwave. Mount Rushmore of Boy Bands. Is Marky Mark a boy band? Enrique Iglesias. Having kids late in life. Pick 6. Caris LaVert. Iggy reviews a movie. Lip fillers. Iggy loves Hubbard. Nikki Glaser. Iggy DM'd Nikki again. Is Nikki getting dragged
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1524263139.mp3?updated=1731089935" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>01-26-22 Segment 1 Mizzou Hoops and TMA Wildlife</title><description>No Tim, but we will flourish. Mizzou hoops falls to #1 Auburn. Bruce Pearl. Iggy wants to   Iggy wants to see full nudity on Family Guy. Futile. StrodeCast. Antarctica. The Boys rank their favorite animals. Did an Owl take Doug’s cat? Iggy is mad again about the Hedo fan page. Duck sized horses or horse sized ducks? 

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2276090202.mp3?updated=1731089855" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-01-22 Segment 1 TMA Sleepover and The Unicorn Tells a Tale</title><description>Iggy is interviewing Ellen Foley, Meatloaf's backup singer. Bat out of hell. What would Meatloaf not do? Ellen Foley's filmography. Sir Mix-A-Lot. Iggy's Straight to the Web. StrodeCast. Iggy makes a big prediction. Beverly D'Angelo. Mafia talk. Larry Nickel joins us for the WWE Recap. Should we all have a sleepover at Iggy's? Maybe we will get 1 hotel room. The unicorn calls in to tell us a story about an all-girl sleepover. Did the Unicorn cuck anyone? Iggy's patio. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2367899977.mp3?updated=1731089955" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-11-22 Segment 2 Aliens and TMA History</title><description>Drops of the Week. Sullivan. Jay recommends a UFO documentary. Alien talk. Lern was awesome yesterday, and she is so talented. FPCC talk. Iggy's putting. A Philly radio host was VERY excited about the James Harden deal. Jay is confused by all the Rams hate. Radio Row. Balloon Party. Radio history of the fellas. The Man/Woman station. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2374577655.mp3?updated=1731089581" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 15:26:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>04-12-22 Segment 2 TMA Wildlife and The Titanic</title><description>Cardinals vs. Royals, 1985 reunion. Friday night is pizza night. Panda talk. Predators. Skeeter. Titanic sinking. EMOTM standings. Al Pacino goes on a date with Mick Jagger’s ex, who is 28. How does all this happen? Iggy claims to be shallow. Depends. Reaching old age. Eyesight issues. Blues take on the Bruins tonight. Berube. Bally’s App. Cheating. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9424696801.mp3?updated=1731088635" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Live from The Dotem Pre-Party: Segment 2</title><description>Enjoy this special podcast episode of TMA Live at The Dotem Pre-Party from Maggie O'Briens. Featuring the Lisa Ann dating game.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4889817549.mp3?updated=1731087788" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Live from The Dotem Pre-Party: Segment 1</title><description>Enjoy this special podcast episode of TMA Live at The Dotem Pre-Party from Maggie O'Briens. Featuring two-part questions with Lisa Ann and TMA Who Said It. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3992100465.mp3?updated=1731087771" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>06-07-22 Segment 2 LIV Golf, NFL Settlement Money, and a TMA Fashion Show</title><description>Glo little Glo worm, Glow! LIV Golf press conference. The morals behind the golf tour. LIV schedule. DM’s on Facebook. Karate Kid the Musical. The NASCAR race over the weekend. Iggy throws shrapnel at someone who didn’t deserve it. Downtown discussion. The NFL settlement money. App Madness. Iggy claims he is better dressed than any person listening to the show. TMA Pageant.  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3745091769.mp3?updated=1670452574" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 13:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-12-22 Segment 1 TMA News Team</title><description>Hooiser Daddy. We are a news organization at heart. Cindy sends another email about Iggy’s controversy. In turns out that someone found the name Cindy, made a Gmail account and then represented themself as Cindy and made up the story. Odd folks, man. Naked drive-in movies, hot. Don LeGreca had a spicy rant. Callers need to use their locations while calling. Birthday Hawk. Larry in Alton joins us for the WWE Recap. DFS Showdown results. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3607234704.mp3?updated=1731086814" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 12:06:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>07-13-22 Segment 2 TMA Trivia News, DFS Showdown, and Kenny Strobe</title><description>Boys club. TMA Trivia night news. Tickets are now $50 and anyone who previously purchased tickets at the older price will be refunded the difference. There will also be STL Sports questions in addition to TMA Trivia. Bathroom attendant. Mungenast DFS Showdown. Tony La Russa walked someone on a 0-1 count, both broadcast booths were confused. Lisa Dergan. Plowsy’s OnlyFans. Iggy spins a yarn about Christina Model. Buck Swope sends us a great screenshot from the 1380 the Woman website.  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1270875300.mp3?updated=1731086851" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 13:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>7-29-22 Segment 1 Christmas in July</title><description>No energy from the boys today. Plowsy’s crave case challenge. Buffets. The sirloin stockade. Plowsy’s star is danger. Who took Doug’s fish. Winter Wonderland in Tillies Park is brutal. The boys discuss Christmas Lights. Iggy spins a yarn. Iggy leaves mid-segment in protest. PitchCom. What will the Redbirds do at the deadline?
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9695960032.mp3?updated=1731091516" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 12:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-3-22 Segment 2 DFS Showdown and TMA Science Class</title><description>Ryan Kelley joins the program. Mungenast DFS Showdown. Jay picks along with Doug and Iggy. The boys discuss LIV Golf. Tiger's LIV offer. TMA science class. Bowling. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2277065453.mp3?updated=1731092120" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 13:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-3-22 Segment 2 DFS Showdown and TMA Science Class</title><description>Ryan Kelley joins the program. Mungenast DFS Showdown. Jay picks along with Doug and Iggy. The boys discuss LIV Golf. Tiger's LIV offer. TMA science class. Bowling. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2655035516.mp3?updated=1731091499" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 13:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Live from The Lemmings Open Pre-Party - Segment 1</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Maggie O'Brien's in Sunset Hills for our Lemmings Open Pre-Party. Including Dead or Alive Trivia, TMA Who Said it, and more. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3306208650.mp3?updated=1731091537" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 10:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA Live from The Lemmings Open Pre-Party - Segment 2</title><description>Enjoy TMA Live from Maggie O'Brien's in Sunset Hills for our Lemmings Open Pre-Party. Including the Chicken Wing eating contest, Classic Rock Trivia, and more.  
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8584970158.mp3?updated=1731091537" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 10:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>9-29-22 Segment 1 Gossip Hour</title><description>Mount Rushmore of holes. Are glory holes real? We talk toes. Bunions. Plowsy is sans big toe nail these days. Flip-flops. Iggy's hedo underoos. The PlowDash. Plowboy's strategy. Someone took Tim's laptop charger. O/u on the mile time. Hurricane going crazy right now. Bridge to Sanibel crumbled. Falling into Tampa Bay. Post 2000 Rams. The new Jeffrey Dahmer series. Fan page questions. Showing off at Church. Jimmy Ballgame. Bora Bora. Iggy's producing skills. Mount Rushmore of TMA producers. Buzz joins us for a press conference Thursday. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7150705634.mp3?updated=1731091537" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 12:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-10-22 3TMA Mizzou Football Chatter</title><description>Gabe joins us from PowerMizzou.com to talk about the fighting Tigers giving it their all in the Swamp....and of course....coming up short. How will Mizzou handle the potent Vandy offense after this weekends bye week? Iggy not a fan of Buck Swopes emails which are typically 40 paragraphs long. Email of the Day 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8642978347.mp3?updated=1731091228" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 14:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-20-22 Segment 3 TMA TikTok Star D'Angelo Hopkins and EMOTD</title><description>KG in O-Town in studio. We talk to KG (D'Angelo Hopkins on TikTok) about his TikTok's. Sybians. We rehash the Bachelor party discussion from yesterday. The breathing is back. We ask KG about his interview with Cassie Moore. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2642738505.mp3?updated=1668115829" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 14:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-11-22 Segment 1 TMA Myths</title><description>Finna be a dirty Friday. Plowsy will be spending this weekend camping. Iggy's tenure as a boy scout. Merit badges. TMA Myths. Is Iggy really going to write a book? Good books to read. Who's the cuck of the century? JFK. Iggy's days at Mississippi Nights. Plowsy's mile run. Iggy's chip challenge. The Fan Page
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4580852377.mp3?updated=1731089084" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 14:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-15-22 Segment 1 TMA Awards</title><description>Special announcement: We are having our first ever TMA end of the year Listener Award Show at Harpo's in Chesterfield. December 8th at 7pm, and guess what? Lisa Ann will be there! How awesome! Gonna be a great evening, all you need to do to get in is bring a toy for Annie's Hope. Looking forward to seeing you there. Gobble Bowl. Tim and Jackson interviewed Hot Wife Autumn yesterday. Plowsy and Iggy still don't believe it. Larry Nickel joins the show for the WWE Recap. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3810174679.mp3?updated=1731089004" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 14:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-28-22 Segment 3  TMA is going to Jamaica &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Steadfast Eyes. Trish Wolf joins us. A Hedo tale from Toga Night. Golfing with David Freese vs. Taking pictures with Santa.  TMA is heading to Jamaica. Iggy will not, I repeat, will not be going. We'll be giving away a trip to Jamaica.  Jackson will be prowling. Applications are flying in to win the Jamaica trip. Gareth's shoulder hair. Plowsy's tendencies. The Tamm Avenue Capital Partners can't get it done. Will Iggy run the board? Fun with Mike Francesa audio. EMOTD
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1266310049.mp3?updated=1731089910" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PP&amp;KG Talking TMA Awards</title><description>KG in O-Town absolutely bringing the heat in his 2nd full day in the big boy chair on TMA. We talking award nominations. Were there any snubs? Who is the leader in clubhouse for each category? It's what you wanted damnit 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1562038652.mp3?updated=1731089837" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 16:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-5-22 Segment 1 Historic 7 o'clock Hour</title><description>We are starting early today because we have Gasparilla Bowl takes. We want a piece of these Demon Deacons! Ok, now let's get to the meat and potatoes, is Iggy going to Jamaica with Lisa Ann? So much is going on. Lisa Ann joins the program to talk it over! Retired Air Marshal joins us. Caller Ellen chimes in. Mizzou bowl situation. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7624042065.mp3?updated=1731089807" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 14:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-7-22 Segment 1 TMA Winter Meetings</title><description>Tim could be an auctioneer. EOTY Listener Awards will be a pony. KG in O-Town's interviews with the nominees. Tim's hand. The acceptance speeches. ILL with a huge victory over Chris Beard's #2 Texas bunch. Can't wait for Braggin' Rights. Blues pick up a big W. Vacation. SLU falls to Iona. Aaron Judge back to the Yankees for a staggering $360 million for 9 years. Hot stove talk as the Cubs are making moves. Will the Cards sign a catcher today? Who and what position do you value the most? 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7874115392.mp3?updated=1731089762" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 14:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>1-12-23 Segment 3 Christmas Card, DFS Showdown, and EMOTD</title><description>Comedians. Stag starlets. Mr. Lix joins the program. Lix has thoughts on the Matty Dread interview. Old money vs. new money. Relatability. Christmas cards. Mungenast DFS Showdown. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9792519667.mp3?updated=1731090624" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>02-06-2023 Segment 2:Low Hanging Fruit Hour</title><description>Tim lost 8 pounds when he joined the vom-com the entire weekend due to a stomach bug. Doug is stunned that Iggy weighs 160 pounds. Mizzou shoots terrible from the field and lose to Mississippi State on the road. Doug never lets a loss from a sports team to affect his entire weekend. Doug doesn't seem to care about Mizzou and the Cardinals. Another disappointing loss for SLU Men's Basketball. Ranking MLB teams from 1995 to present day. Pirates are considered the worst team in that era with a -4 point total, the only team with negative points in ranking systems. Cardinals are in the to 3 of the rankings, with the Yankees being the best team in this era. Plowsy is not high on the last decade of Cardinals baseball. What is Moe's approval rating in St. Louis? 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6555361450.mp3?updated=1731091056" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 15:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2-10-23 Segment 2 Polarizing TMA Characters Over The Years &amp; STL Civics</title><description>Joey says the golf video is up.  Is it though? Mr. Lix calls in and he's not happy with Hrabe.  Kevin Na is kind of a try hard. Lix is not happy about much of anything.  Is Mr. Lix the most polarizing figure in TMA since Timberfake?  Reliving The Battle on Broadway from February '17.  TMA approval ratings over the years.  Are the Blues in St. Louis if the Spurs deal goes through? St. Louis and its history of making the wrong decision.  Civic discussion. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7118990789.mp3?updated=1731087576" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2-14-23 Segment 1 The TMA Wars</title><description>"Making Whoopie." PrizeGate. Listeners are looking to make some waves. Listeners banty about the Cardinals scouting. A lot of listeners are wishing Doug a happy Valentine's Day. Buck Swope posts an audio postcard about 2 separate times of being peed on, much to Iggy's chagrin. The possible weekend music show with Iggy. StrodeCast. PlowHawk is taking off Friday to go on a birthday hike with his girl. STL CITY SC jerseys. Simpin' in Jamaica. Dogs away kits. Beercats joins the show to spike the football on being Listener of the Month and to grill Ken. Larry Nickel joins the program for the WWE Recap.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8198321048.mp3?updated=1731086931" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2-15-23 Segment 2 TMA History Class</title><description>Ryan Kelley, the title sponsor, joins the show. Mungenast DFS Showdown. Talking fruit. Best way to re-heat beef. A nice little cooking segment. Social media posts likes and comments. Discussing STL history and Iggy's got a gripe with the Louisiana Purchase. Lewis and Clark. Listeners are furious with this breakdown. 

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6918102403.mp3?updated=1731090836" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3-7-23 Segment 2 TMA Sabermetrics</title><description>Cassie. A listener sends us a breakdown of time talked for the dais for a 4 hour sample size. Larry Nickel joins us for the WWE Recap. Dogs captain Roman Burki was asked how the atmosphere at City Park compares to Signal Iduna Park (Borussia Dortmund). The boys break it down. Audio of Jon Miller ripping the D-Backs for not giving him any info during a split-squad game. Ted Lasso may end after this third season. Shows that have gone too long. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2077585732.mp3?updated=1731087043" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3-28-23 Segment 1 Variety Hour</title><description>Tornado talk. Iggy's Mount Rushmore of hot men. Doug's cruise. Mississippi River cruises. We are being held accountable for our college basketball takes. Biggest cities in America without a pro sports team. Iggy and PlowHawk say the MLS isn't one of the 4 major sports. Sylvester Stallone. Happy Birthday Lern! Iggy got her a gift. Will he get Doug a gift for his birthday? Man Oysters. The Masters. Doug's favorite things about Augusta. The Fan Page Club Championship.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6751309342.mp3?updated=1731087635" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>4-12-23 Segment 1 Cruising with Doug and Iggy's Story Hour</title><description>Tim's soft s's. The Dotem fees will be less than last year. Going on sale on Friday at 8am! Be ready! Doug cruise to the Mediterranean. Will he be peacocking around. Cardinals win last night in Denver. Hello Nolan(s)! If we can just get hot, we can win this baby. Miles Mikolas. Plowsy has a massive Oatmeal Creme Pie. We play guess the calories. (Chairman) Steve in Wildwood's mic drop. The Rays can't draw flies. They are changing the name of the Rays ballpark to the Keisha Dome. Missouri Sports Hall of Fame inductees. The film 'Notting Hill'. Julia Roberts. Brentwood High School Hall of Fame. We dovetail into stories from Brentwood circa mid-70's.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4547657493.mp3?updated=1731089199" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 13:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>6-14-23 Segment 1 TMA Day at the Ballpark</title><description>We are Live from Salt + Smoke at BPV! The Youtube lighting is subpar but the content is oh so hot. This location is beautiful. The Cardinals are in last place and the Dogs are in the first. The Redbirds are +1000 to win the division. The AL Central is even more hot garbage. Oakland A's reverse boycott. Possible Kroenke stadium in San Diego. Bailey's Sports. Iggy was unaware that the Oakland A's are moving to Vegas. PlowHawk was unaware Vegas won the cup last night. Breaking down the Cup final. Pepper n' Genie will return on Friday.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8745232270.mp3?updated=1731088396" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>7-24-23 Segment 2 TMA Shark Tank</title><description>Jackson's going to see Barbie tonight. Iggy reads an Oppenheimer review from someone on Facebook. Big weekend for movies at the box office with Barbie, Oppenheimer, and Sound of Freedom. Movie theatre catheters. Iggy presents possibly the worst idea ever given. Iggy slam dunks on the texter with belching knowledge. Best WR duos of all time. Ms. Butler held Doug accountable back in the day. Buckeye Girl ripped Iggy.....somewhere.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7021580756.mp3?updated=1731087273" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:07:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-11-23 Segment 2 Casting the TMA Movie &amp; Drops of the Week</title><description>Iggy heading to PartyTown at 9:30. Arenado's mad dash to score from first on a single yesterday. Workshopping a new Fetish Friday segment when Tim is out. Drops of the week. Jackson reads a cheeky little article on "Rizz." New Yorkers apparently have all the rizz. Shirtless in the brig. Jackson, KG, and Roch recorded an Oppenheimer review podcast yesterday. Casting the TMA movie.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5093452093.mp3?updated=1691764242" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-14-23 Segment 2 TMA QFTA</title><description>Steve in Wildwood gallup poll. Gregg Popovich's HOF speech. Ahmad Rashad. KG in O-Town &amp; Iggy. How we handle topics. TMA 'inside baseball'. Mount Rushmore of Oscars. Splitting sammies.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8946823042.mp3?updated=1731088780" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-17-23 Segment 1 TMA Auctions and Missouri NIL</title><description>Long texts to start the show. The listeners have time today. The Loomster brought data to the table. Steve in Wildwood and PlowKing played golf yestersbee. Honey holes. Hazards. Iggy wants to give away a foursome to the Megan Meier Foundation Golf Tournament. How will he give it away on the show? No clue, but we do believe in it. Jackson's rec league championship. Ween tips. Story about Missouri NIL. The boys break it down.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1073783016.mp3?updated=1692278482" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>8-21-23 Segment 3 Rush TMA and EMOTD</title><description>James Carlton in studio talking Mizzou football. Who will start at QB. Trying to go to CoMo for the LSU game. Talking sorority rush. The differences between Frats and Sororities.  Rush week. House mothers. EMOTD. 
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7789375242.mp3?updated=1731090947" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 15:02:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>9-1-23 Segment 2 The TMA Hit &amp; Giggle</title><description>We are excited to announce the first TMA Hit &amp; Giggle. Friday, October 6th at Family Golf. Tickets go on sale on Wednesday, September 6th. Iggy's long drive contest will down at the event. Head to TMASTL.com for more info. Iggy's call with Dillion Harper gets panned by the audience, with many people not believing his story.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5558453123.mp3?updated=1731091437" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-6-23 Segment 1 Live from the TMA Hit &amp; Giggle</title><description>Good morning from the TMA Hit &amp; Giggle. Check out KG and Jackson's Brian Kelly themed mini movie on Twitter, IG, and the FanPin. Is Doug The Wizard? Sharp money on Mizzou. Odds Mizzou is undefeated going to Athens. Iggy's shoulder leading into the long drive challenge. Iggy's HOF induction tomorrow. Dick Butkus passed away. Will Chairman Steve and Iggy make amends today? Boner pills in The Villages. Players not happy with Alan Shipnuck. Action on the short game area.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7858256394.mp3?updated=1731089246" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-17-23 Segment 1 TMA Law: John's Drill</title><description>Rat-a-tat-tat delivery to kick off the show. Phillies ripping baseballs last night. We do a deep dive on Dave Kingman. Jason Momoa may or may not be coming by. Class warfare breaks out in the text inbox. Trivia night. Dear Deidre about a man losing his wife to a local. We get into divorce talk and non-compete agreements. TMA Law. Caller Buzz joins us to talk fingers and pegs. More law talk. Larry Nickel joins the show for the WWE Recap.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4932503583.mp3?updated=1731087638" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-19-23 Segment 1 - Radio Wars Episode V: TMA Strikes Back</title><description>New gear from TMASTLShop.com left and right. The boys are decked out. A long time ago in a galaxy far, far away... Radio Wars are upon us. First, the Rizz Show thinks we are peeing on the ground/toilet seat. Plowsy's toilet treats. Iggy sits when he pees, so he claims he's safe from any accusations. Bathrooms from stations past. Iggy defends himself sitting to pee. KG does some investigation, much to Ken's chagrin. JeffCo shots are taken. The audio from McGraw Millhaven's show on not mentioning Tim in his SoundStory live read. Was Iggy the one who texted the McGraw Millhaven show? Iggy's golf rival game. The Golden Bachelor. Would Iggy consider being on the Golden Bachelorette? Analysm. More urinal investigation.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5904669032.mp3?updated=1697723927" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 13:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-23-23 Segment 2 TMA Think Tank</title><description>Gillman... North Carolina Football... Mom won't watch the news at night. Arizona State football. Plowsy's text to our boss, Tommy (at 9:00pm on a Sunday) about his idea for a toilet food show. TMA Think Tank opens up as Iggy wants a gilstrap style fart show.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6354311076.mp3?updated=1731088414" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>10-25-23 Segment 2 TMA Bowl</title><description>Dear Deidre about a failed swinging attempt. We double dip with another Dear Deidre. Updates on Mad Dog Russo's retirement. He may have to wear a bikini. Buzz continues to say that his buddy shoved a phone up his ass. Ken and Doug push back. Trivia Night. Dabo Swinney on playing on the CW. Bowl projections. Who can still be live for the CFP? Missouri ducking KU. Bowl game affiliations.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6377427659.mp3?updated=1731087961" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-7-23 Segment 1 TMA Swap Meet</title><description>Where's Ken? He is taking a recreational. Giving away 4 tickets to the Blues games tonight vs. Wins Per Game. Parking at Blues games. Trivia night. What are some of the categories? Iggy's music questions. Paying bets. Nipple rings. Texter class warfare. Owning private jets vs. fractional ownership. Looking at the clothes and physical media Iggy has brought into the station. Iggy brought Plowboy some shirts. Why wouldn't he just donate this stuff?
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3491275021.mp3?updated=1731087662" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-9-23 Segment 2 The Lainey Hour and College Ball</title><description>Talking about the Country Music Awards. Lainey Wilson. Iggy 'crowbars' in Lainey Gardner. How old is she? The listeners go after Iggy for his music takes. The Lipstick Lass is here for the Lainey Wilson talk. KG vs. Iggy as KG claims Lainey Gardner will join us at 9:30. Iggy is dubious that she will joins us. Country stars resonating with the younger crowd. Iggy's sketches and bits. College Football talk. Where will Missouri's motivation be after the Georgia game? Playoff scenarios. Coach of the Year odds.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4107039563.mp3?updated=1731089731" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>11-14-23 Segment 3 TMA Bowl and EMOTD</title><description>Listeners upset with Iggy's tardiness to start the seggy. Adobe issues. The Athletic put out their bowl predictions. Doug has 10 chances to guess the Peach Bowl opponent the Tigers will play, per the prediction by the Athletic. New Year's Six bowl talk. Iggy confused by the bowl system. Would folks be interested in matchup like The Athletic is predicting? Jon Morosi audio about the Braves interest in Gray and Nola. Trade market isn't yielding a lot of hope. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8717058171.mp3?updated=1731088511" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-6-23 Segment 1 TMA Winter Meeting</title><description>Iggy's date tonight at Olive + Oak. Illinois with a big win yesterday against FAU. Boca Raton. FAU's satellite campus in Jup Town. SoundStory guest from a few weeks ago who is dealing with terminal cancer will join us in the 8 o'clock hour. She is awesome and has an incredible outlook on life. Year End Awards next Thursday. What's the worst part of Florida? The state of Florida is up in arms about the situation. Iggy is confused about plugola. Audio galore. Someone farted during the Lightning goalie's media scrum. Francesa dealing with prankster callers. A wild story about New York radio host Joe Benigno texting with Jets coach Robert Salah. Benigno shares his texts with Salah, and misinterpreted the communication. Media ethics discussion. Talking about the Winter Meetings. Plowsy is anti-Winter Meetings. Some baseball insiders frustrated by the hush-hush nature of the Ohtani negotiations.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1563372774.mp3?updated=1731089223" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-8-23 Segment 2 TMA End of the Year Award Nominees</title><description>We announce the nominees for Listener of the Year, Texter of the Year, Worst Texter of the Year, Best Caller of the Year, Emailer of the Year, Rookie of the Year, Naughtiest Listener of the Year, Fan Page Member of the Year, and Drop of the Year. Carlos Spicyweiner with a Florida State-esque snub for the second straight year. Animal talk. Jail talk. Bigger win: Mizzou over KU in basketball or Mizzou over Ohio State in the Cotton Bowl? Cody Schrader made no NIL money this year. Ladies and gentlemen, the skeleton is changing.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2897345001.mp3?updated=1731090717" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 15:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>12-20-23 Segment 2 "Welcome To TMA. Shut The Hell Up"</title><description>Christmas with young kids. A.J. Pierzynski audio saying he thinks the Cardinals are done making moves. Plowsy has thoughts. The Bailey's situation. Discussing the possibility of Amazon investing in Diamond and taking over the broadcasting rights. Talking it all over. What is wealthy these days? Credit card debt. Part-time jobs. Plowsy vs. the audience. What's Iggy's retirement plan? Jeremy Rutherford joins the program to talk all things Blues. Mark Hannah's hair.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3452669805.mp3?updated=1731088988" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>2-22-24 Segment 3 Generation TMA and EMOTD</title><description>Iggy is on time for this segment, no door locking needed. Cigarettes. Good weather coming. Boomer memes. Generation talk. Doug vs. Pepper N' Genie. Trade school. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3193461243.mp3?updated=1731090698" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 16:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>3-1-24 Segment 1 QFTA On TMA</title><description>Doubling down on the end of winter. QFTA on TMA with an erotic story. A little bit of man-on-man action. Some of the audience is down on the story. You make the call. Full stop on the Cognizant. More QFTA. Rick Ankiel. Media-Athlete relationships. Ray Lankford at the bar at Bristol when he's supposed to be in the starting lineup.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8284316422.mp3?updated=1731089829" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ep. 631 - QFTA: Community Christmas Card</title><description>Topics include:
-Posting your kids on social media
-Ranking the toxicity of each major social media platform
-Masters odds
Please support our sponsors:
Mark Hannah – Evergreen Wealth Strategies
James Carlton Agency (State Farm)
Design Aire Heating &amp; Cooling
Mungenast
Longo Biggs
Follow us on Social Media: @TMASTL on Twitter, @tma_stl on Instagram
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4121533455.mp3?updated=1712002998" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>5-29-24 Segment 3 TMA Invitational &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Iggy goes 0 for 3 on the day. Tim has to forfeit his Sweet 16 matchup in the FPCC. Doug wonders why the match can't be played at another course, showing his obvious inability to chairman. Iggy is down on the FPCC. Iggy proposes a TMA Invitational Ryder Cup-style tournament. DFS Showdown time. Audio of Pat McAfee apologizing for perpetuating fake news regarding Mark Davis and a 26 year old pregnant woman. EMOTD.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2429881303.mp3?updated=1731089060" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>6-11-24 Segment 2 Big Phone Call 8:00 Hour</title><description>Larry Nickel is here to recap last night's wrasslin'. Happy belated birthday to Larry. Full board of calls and we're gonna start with Big Al. Big Al's got Jackson's back. Up next is TMA Walrus #1 with a little James Carlton love. TMAW1 dropping some Civil War facts on us. The audience not happy with the metronome in the background. Cal is our next caller and he's not happy with the hold time. Questioning Iggy's return from breaks and soliciting Country Clubs in Austin. Losing interest in the Cardinals since moving out of St. Louis. Fastest growing cities in America.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2193080988.mp3?updated=1718115903" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ep. 648 - QFTA: LBJ Would Have Been Great on TMA</title><description>Topics include:
-2024 American politics
-College Football
-Play radio GM and make your ideal TMA lineup
Please support our sponsors:
Mark Hannah – Evergreen Wealth Strategies
James Carlton Agency (State Farm)
Design Aire Heating &amp; Cooling
Mungenast
Longo Biggs
Follow us on Social Media: @TMASTL on Twitter, @tma_stl on Instagram
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3058804295.mp3?updated=1722889021" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-28-24) Hour 1</title><description>Hey look, everyone, it's Martin Kilcoyne and we're on 101 ESPN now. Bittersweet this morning. There's not another personality around like Iggy Strode. Iggy's rolodex. Jackson has a dossier ready to go.

One segment down and Martin is thinking about quitting. Joey Vitale is up and listening and his nips are hard. The formula for creating a TMA text name. Tough one for Mizzou on Saturday, especially after Brady Cook went down. Drew Pyne may not be the guy. The Tigers laid two eggs against their two biggest opponents. Big miss to not have a backup QB. Luther Burden had 3 catches for 3 yards. Lots of talent back from last season but it just hasn't translated. Our niche is homoerotic sports radio.

Chariman Kurt "met" the love of his life in Tuscaloosa. Met might be the wrong word as he didn't exactly talk to her. She just had an aura about her. Would she have been willing to date an older fella? The Hinge and Bumble scene down in Alabama. Hard to bring a girl back to the Red Roof Inn with your dad in the same room. The needlepoint belts were all over the place. Doug is officiating the Plowhawk's wedding.

Martin has prepared a poem for us. Jackson may or may not have given out the wrong phone number. Not sure who is going to filter the phone calls during this moment of transition. Martin meets Libby Jack.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9667519708.mp3?updated=1731090666" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-28-24) Hour 2</title><description>The YouTube chat is active this morning. Martin reads some mean tweets about the show changes from over the weekend. We welcome your hatred. Everything goes back to, "It should be good for Timmy."

Our first guest on 101, Chris Kerber, joins us to talk about the Blues' weekend. Chief coming back to St. Louis. Some breaking news coming up on the Tuscaloosa girl in the Tiger striped dress. Does Buck Swope have a real job?

A listener has DM'd a picture of what could be the tiger-striped dress girl. Unfortunately it is not her, but it is Brady Cook's mom. Audio of Drink following the loss in Tuscaloosa. Drink's post-game presser was short and sweet on Saturday.

Audio of Freddie Freeman's historic game-winning grand slam on Friday night. Hell of a call from joe Davis. Audio of Aaron Boone explaining the logic of using Nestor Cortes. Dodgers up 2-0 going into Game 3 tonight in The Bronx. The BYU coach went to Kirkwood High.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9653198517.mp3?updated=1730126849" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-28-24) Hour 3</title><description>Missouri is where I live. Gabe DeArmond joins us to talk about the disaster in Tuscaloosa. How long will Brady Cook be out with his hand injury? Hope is that it is not season-ending, but the Oklahoma game could be in jeopardy. Hopes of the College Football Playoffs are dead. Will players be opting out with less to play for now? Looking back on the many TMA stops throughout the 20 years. The 590 The Man/1380 The Woman situation. The Late Night Score &amp; Nick and The Badger.

Quite an ending in the Commanders Bears game yesterday. Bone-headed play by the Bears defender. Audio of Mike Francesa and he's not happy with the Jets and their interim coach. Some of our old texters have found their way to the new text line. Doug's fescue situation. Martin's gotta go at 10.

Warfare going on in the two YouTube chats. Hate listeners. Guest hosts when some of the regulars are out. BenFred's article about Nolan Arenado. Will he be back next season? Moves that weren't made in the last couple years.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3882986857.mp3?updated=1731088895" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 15:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-28-24) Hour 4</title><description>Balloon Party is now Hour 4 of TMA. Just know, Jackson is happy. Jackson's got some questions for us. How the 12-Team Playoff will affect expectations within college football programs. Anarchy is on the horizon. Missouri and Illinois hopes are gone but lots of excitement down the stretch in the CFB world. Should Jackson and Tim forget their salaries in exchange for longer segments. Chairman still reeling from missing out on the love of his life. Will Mizzou score again this season if Drew Pyne is the QB?

Mike Elko firing some shots in his postgame comments on Saturday. Who was he talking about? Tim's tongue. Big game Saturday in the Big Ten between Ohio State and Penn State. Outstanding College Gameday in Bloomington. Kirk Hebstreit and Lee Corso.

Doug is getting acclimated to the 10:00 hour. The debut of the Email of the Day segment on 101 coming up. Tim found himself pulling for the Cleveland Browns yesterday. Audio of Jameis Winston channeling his inner Marshall Mathers after the Browns win. Supercut of Gabe's voicemails from the Power Mizzou post-game show. Jackson's not a fan of Harrison's Brother, Master. Jackson's JUICY shorts. Follow us on IG at tma_stl.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9233598613.mp3?updated=1731087470" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 16:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-29-24) Hour 1</title><description>This Burke guy is kind of a mutt. What's Jackson's hockey nickname? If you can see us as you drive down Olive, give us a wave. Jackson's magic dossier. Martin said down with John Mozeliak for the 2Fox. Piddles is a poor speller. The Whale Tail Phenomenon. WHY IS CHAIM BLOOM HIDING?!?! Pale Whales. Props to Tommy for reducing the commercial breaks. Figuring out the phone liens in this time of transition.

John Kelly joining us at 8:15. Yankees might be in some trouble. Should Aaron Boone sit Aaron Boone? The LaRussa/Rolen beef. Fun with percentages. Ludacris at The Dome. Fat Joe at Yankee Stadium. Fat Joe can't walk. Cardinals had Rascal Flats perform and ProdJoe proclaimed that the Cardinals would never win another World Series. Audio of Fat Joe's performance. VIP Pat is our first caller. Banty on The Fan Page yesterday.

Listeners are streaming while sky-pigging. YouTube chat talking about Mt. Rushmore of fat rappers. Audio of John Sterling getting fooled by a fly ball. Martin sat down with Martin Kilcoyne yesterday. Audio of Mo talking about the rumor of the Cardinals being sold. Is there a succession plan in place for the DeWitts? Bad time to sell. The structure of the Cardinals' front office.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5420323734.mp3?updated=1731088119" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 13:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-29-24) Hour 2</title><description>A little clock abuse so we're gonna get back on track. Who is your "Pale Whale"? Doug thinks Mike Shildt. John Mozeliak gave Shildt the green light to talk about the firing but we've never heard his side.

Blues play-by-play guy John Kelly joins us on the phone lines from Ottawa. What positives and negatives has he seen in the Blues early on? Injuries has been a problem. Team speed seems to be improved. Reuniting with Craig Berube.

Jackson's random NBA SportsCenter update. Taking calls at the 2Fox asking for scores. Should we get Fernando Vina to call in? Caller Adam has found his way to the 101 phone lines. Adam is angry about no one answering the phones. Globule of lube. Coconut oil at room temperature. Tom Schmitt knows good lube and BBQ. Adam has been potted down. Would Kevin Demoff talk and would you want to talk to him? Speculation of Demoff being a possible NFL commissioner.

Martin wasn't happy with Adam's call. The conspiracy theory around drafting Michael Sam. Tim had Jeff Fisher on his podcast. Doug's Fisher impression is all jowl. Texts coming in on Pale Whale suggestions. Mike Keenan and Frank Cusumano didn't get along real well. Calvin May &amp; The Skipper.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9779091689.mp3?updated=1731090179" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 14:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-29-24) Hour 3</title><description>Andy Crouppen and his luscious head of hair join us in-studio talking about perjury. How could we get Kroenke and Demoff to tell the truth? Rams trying to buy the spot in Earth City for $1.

Jackson's got "So What'd Your Grandma Think" for us. Jackson needs the drapes drawn. Giving Martin the context with audio of Calvin May asking Jason Heyward what his grandma thought. A reporter questioned Trevon Diggs' effort and Diggs went lookin' for him. Things got a little tense. Audio of Shannon Sharpe defending the reporter on his podcast with Ochocinco. Ochocinco is Jackson's Pale Whale.

Martin was pleased with Jackson's NBA update. Audio of Mozeliak talking with Martin about the fans supporting the Cardinals going forward through some tough times. Cards use of technology. The Minor League pipeline. The Cardinals were wondering in 2014 what they had in Oscar Tavares. The difficulty identifying talent goes back a decade. The Cards' model going forward.

Liaa has a question on the phone lines. Lisa's not happy with Oli's leadership and Doug's not happy with Lisa's language. Strange timing of the Marmol extension. Managers vs. Analytics. Martin very briefly goes into Tony.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4121048918.mp3?updated=1731087491" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 15:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-29-24) Hour 4</title><description>Doug's concerned we may have to start going to Blues morning skate. Checking in on the text line. Jackson is really battling the sun in this studio. Doug's Jackie O sunglasses. Doug's had enough and he's gonna fix the drapes situation. Jackson's all about the giggles. And in a surprising hot take, Jackson seems down on the premise of Back To The Future. Is Martin cruising around Creve Coeur Park?

Questions 'O' Plenty with Lil Piddles. Fandom in cold weather vs. warm weather cities. Would Jackson rather go to the Blues vs. Leafs or stay home and play video games? Local athletes with wide deltas of fan approval. Matheny was beloved as a player but not so much as manager. Warner &amp; Bulger.

We somehow missed the 13 year anniversary of the David Freese game. Thanks to the listener in the text inbox for letting us know. But that means the Cardinals won the World Series 13 years ago today. Yankees on life support. Uniform nirvana. Human lamb.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7914173850.mp3?updated=1731090623" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-30-24) Hour 1</title><description>Martin ran into Misty Plops and he seemed totally normal. We really wanna test out the phone line system today. Someone called in that saw Martin in Maui. And Caller Buzz makes his 101 ESPN debut. Martin would like to know if he has to go to trivia night. There's some hate coming in the text line but we're going through a reset. Blues had a small issue last night in Ottawa.

Tim had a nice conversation with a listener yesterday. Tough one last night in Ottawa. Blues lose 8-1. Audio of a disappointed Drew Bannister after last night's drubbing. You can't chase the game, Tim. Big Walt had to have been happy last night. Encouraging start to the road trip but not as much now. TMA After Dark. Bringing the cuckold and sports communities together. Clock changing soon, quite soon. Jackson wasn't allowed to say, "I don't know."

HUGE win yesterday in EMOTD by Misty Plops. Is Plops a nesting body now? We have a Game 5 in the World Series as the Yankee stave off elimination. Audio of the fans trying to pry the ball from Mookie Betts last night. The brothers aren't welcome back at Yankee Stadium. Are these guys the Yankees Rally Squirrel? Jack Flaherty on the mound tonight for the Dodgers. Reliving the Flaherty/Derrick Goold exchange. When the Hoosier Father/Son tandem attacked the coach in Chicago. Too much Bama runnin' through my veins.

Jackson's opening up the doors to the Fan Page today. Power outage in Ottawa last night and they sure turned the lights out on the Blues. The journey of the Blues trunk. Evanesence stole it but left it in Ottawa.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8756063283.mp3?updated=1731090813" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-30-24) Hour 2</title><description>We're joined by the man who coined the nickname "Lil Piddles," Jamie Rivers. Jamie has an issue with the show already. Rivers is friends with some members of Evanesence and he wasn't happy with Piddle's song choice. What to make of that game last night. Growing pains with some of these younger players. Is this a playoff team? The Note in Philadelphia before returning home to face Chief. Dental cuckings.

Would Jackson rather watch the Blues or answer the phone lines? We may all get together to watch the game. Team transportation doesn't wait for media. Frank Cusumano steals luggage. Is Jackson too elite to answer the phones? A symphony of Frank drops.

Calling into sports talk radio. Audio from Martin's conversation with John Mozeliak. The path that lead to where the Cardinals are currently. Roleplaying with Tim as the reporter and Martin as Mo. Mo's answers are rather unsatisfying.

Reading rapid fire texts from the text line.  Reminiscing the days of randomly calling sorority houses on The Morning Grind.  Francesa and Stan Lee. 

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2699912279.mp3?updated=1730297498" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-30-24) Hour 3</title><description>Jeremy Rutherford joins us for two-part questions following the drubbing in Ottawa last night. Where are the home white sweaters? Country Roads. Adults wearing jerseys. Does Drew Bannister have a presence as coach? Corduroy. Which Blues have sand paper to their game? This year's expectations.

Texters coming after Martin. Those pesky brothers at Yankee Stadium trying to take Mookie Betts glove. The boys were ready to D Up. The Yankees haven't responded to ESPN's request for comment. If the Yankees come back will they be on the ring?

The ESPN voiceover guy had some issues with Jackson's last name. Great job if you can get it. Mr. Lix is down on Charlotte. Filling Martin in on Jackson's boys trip to the mountains. IT's starting to happen, we're starting to win em over. Bobby Magic and The Human Ashtray. Catching Martin up on what he's missed the last 18 years. Going dutch on a bed. The Professor.

More fun with voiceover miscues. Dough Vaughn. Ooooh, the 618 is a lady. Nevermind, they don't like us.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7754508514.mp3?updated=1731088896" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 15:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-30-24) Hour 4</title><description>Janet calls in to defend our great city's honor against Charlotte. Scorching hot St. Louis takes. The texters are on board with Janet and she has a direct line to get on the air. Comrade Burkett doesn't think he's better than anyone.

Buck Swope has texted Tim to correct the EMOTD standings. Audio of Desmond Howard talking college football with some strange sound effects in it. Ferrario's ball gag. Jackson's golf swing. He's a little champion. Courier Tom is on the phone lines and he wants to know if Luther Burden is ready for the pros. Burden's draft stock.

Wide Berth Wednesday. Lot of statue talk going around with the Dwayne Wade statue situation. Which St. Louis athletes are statue worthy? Is Pietrangelo worthy of a statue? A Kyle Lohse Skip Schumaker statue would look good. Doug missed the Freese homerun in 2011 for a live shot.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1154809410.mp3?updated=1731091155" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-31-24) Hour 1</title><description>(Apologies for the first few seconds. Hardware issue.) Doug is dressed like a little conductor today. Sirens going off around 2:45 this morning. The TMA Glossary: The Webster Groves vs. Cottleville War. Tim's keys are going off. Janet is a rising star. Bobcat Nostalgia. It's Listener of the Month SZN. Joe Strauss coined "Pee Pee Talk." Amendment 2. How do the teams benefit? Martin's got a surprise guest at 9:30. Jackson wanted to take in Reteif Goosen.

Two horse race in the October EMOTD contest. Audio of the final out of Dodgers World Series win. Yankees really let one slip away last night. Judge's drop in centerfield reminiscent of Matt Holliday. Gerrit Cole forgot to cover first base. Paul from the wealthy part of West County calls in to pitch a TMA Halloween party. The texters aren't real pleased with it.

Polling data on Amendment 2. Why is Martin so against this amendment? Is it morality and religious beliefs working against it? Doug's not much of a gambler. TikTok is not just moms dancing and looking for attention. Get your FYP right.

Martin's getting texts from Cousin John. Some are concerned about the effect on minors. Does our audience skew more liberal or conservative? Jackson doesn't wear a lot of khaki. We make picks.....YOU MAKE MONEY! Martin's read on Jack Flaherty was spot on.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6688557455.mp3?updated=1731089233" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-31-24) Hour 2</title><description>Austin Capobianco dominated the news cycle yesterday. Audio of Gronk talking with friend of the show Kay Adams about his old buddy. Mike Francesa had takes on the whole deal. Mike was hanging out at Barstool watching the game. Doug's not convinced that 'dossier' is being used correctly. Reuben Studdard.

Blues Hall of Famer, Bernie Federko joins us. What type of response does he expect to see after what happened in Ottawa? Shaking up lines. What kind of reception does he expect when Craig Berube returns? The Hubbard President seemed a little confused with Doug's conductor hat. Polar Express. Joe Davis &amp; Vin Scully.

Audio of Joe Davis talking about his World Series calls. Announcers preparing calls for big moments. Jack Buck thought he blew the Go Crazy Folks call. Eric in the CWE is on the phone lines. Trying to alienate 101 ESPN and TMA listeners. Just a couple guys flirting with each other.

Someone's not happy with Jackson and Eric in the CWE flirting. Martin questions the dossier. Cards Nation 95 is on the line and he's not happy with us. Talking burgers and fries. He's trying to give us a chance.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6840235027.mp3?updated=1731087440" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-31-24) Hour 3</title><description>Robert Thomas checking in. Talking about the Blues bouncing back from the 8-1 loss in Ottawa. Disappointing to be injured and not be able to help the team. Reminiscing on the famous road trip that brought the 2019 Stanley Cup winning Blues team together. Getting a better feeling in the room by getting the boys together. Knowing right away that the ankle was injured. Martin not taking any of the blame for the injury even though he jinxed him. How well does he know Daddy Padre? His golf handicap.

We're boring and talk no sports, Tim is arrogant and never gets to the point. You can criticize, just be factually correct. Martin's gonna have periodic surprises. Martin and Jackson exchange DMs. Tim and Doug are feeling a little left out. Gonna set up an alliance with Chairman Kurt. The Fescoe Year. Looking back on the years at the picnic table.

Martin's first surprise is none other than Keith "Walter" Tkachuck.

Sketches and bits. Joe Buck. Bag 'o' Bits. Martin's heading down to City Park.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4232416733.mp3?updated=1731086789" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (10-31-24) Hour 4</title><description>Press Conference Thursday and Jackson's got some questions for the dais. Best college football game to attend. Jackson loves the Penn State White Out Games. Audio of Lane Kiffin talking about the schedule. People know TIm for seeing both sides and fairness.

Tim's gonna stand this segment. Blues CEO Chris Zimmerman joins the show to talk Amendment 2 and its importance to local teams.

Texts coming in saying we're boring and don't talk sports. In fairness, there were 4 Blues guests. But they've flipped in just over an hour. We're not the only one with ADHD. Is Jackson a groomer? Would Jackson rather have a WNBA team or the Blues. Mouth breathers.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7805404433.mp3?updated=1730391317" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-1-24) Hour 1</title><description>Martin and Tim have been spending time talking to listeners. General banter leading off the dossier. Don't say "Under Center." This show is like St. Louis City SC. Energizer Park. Complaints from prep sports parents. PigPen is on the phone lines with a question for the dais. Did ProdJoe fund a trip on a private jet to a gentlemen's club in Atlanta? Was PigPen a smoker? Wayne Huizenga.

The Note having trouble getting the puck on net and drop one to the Flyers. Audio of Drew Bannister talking about missed opportunities. Right where they wanna be in sixth place in the division. Retooling and resetting. Cheeto dust. Hate piling up on Jordan Kyrou. Cards passing on Lynn, Gibson, and Middleton.

We need to bring the TMA and 101 listeners together at TMA Trivia Night. Ozempic pukes. We've left general banter and entered light vamping. Not surprised by not resigning Lynn and GIbson. Martin's got deferred money in his contract. Will Arenado be back next year?

Chairman Kurt's doing podcast stuff. Favorite college football games of the weekend. Penn State and Ohio State. Jackson was caught caressing himself. Jets and Texans last night. Shout out to Bear Down.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8231565957.mp3?updated=1731086790" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-1-24) Hour 2</title><description>Tim was dressed as garbage for Halloween. Blippy Mode. People wanna be like Tim and dress like garbage. When in doubt, reference a man's vertical issues.

Friend of the show, Joey Vitale checking in this morning. Blues struggle as of late. Atmosphere at Enterprise Center tomorrow. Over/Under on the ovation for Chief. Going All South County. African elephants and the zygote community.

This is a pro free speech dais. Martin is loving some of the names in the text inbox. Manut Bol Eligible wrote the article on Hoosiers &amp; Hummers. Hard to be single in your 30s or 40s in St. Louis. Jackson's got some air in his esophagus. Mr. Lix makes his HD1 debut. Lix stands with Janet. Problems with burgers. Lix vs. Martin. The Papal Conclave meets today to name the Listener of the Month.

Caller Allen chiming in and wants to talk about the new show. Not a bad call but he had to be potted down. Spin-off of the Hoosier Trojan Horse. The Martin/Jackson alliance is on the rocks.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9953160576.mp3?updated=1731089176" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-1-24) Hour 3</title><description>Matt Zollers taking a trip to Happy Valley for a visit this weekend. Should Coach Drink and Mizzou be worried? Is Sam Horn's future in baseball or football? If playing time is important, Mizzou may be the place to be. Mizzou uniforms. The anthracite period. Drew Pyne just hasn't been good. Tim had all the tools football coaches look for.

It's time to make people some money with Pick 6. Jackson's leaning into the stink. Multi-day parlays. Big game in State College, PA.

Bill DeWitt III joined BK &amp; Ferrario yesterday. Audio from their conversation. The current television deal. Streaming service. Juan Soto is going to get a monster contract. Where will he end up?

We're gonna air some grievances in the 10:00 hour. Jackson's down on grocery stores. Alliances are forming in the studio. Martin's got some things.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2397774633.mp3?updated=1731089500" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-1-24) Hour 4</title><description>The TMA Trivia Night is really going to bring everybody together. Iggy is planning on being there. Two weeks from tonight at St. Gabe's. Oh, the banners. Fun with architecture. Friday Six Shooter. Tortured fan bases. Mizzou fans gotta be in the conversation. Some people don't like the topic.

Gabe DeArmond of Power Mizzou joins us. Gabe's thoughts on Zollers visiting Penn State. Gabe's temperature of Mizzou fans going through the disappointment of this missed opportunity. 9 or 10 win seasons shouldn't be considered a failure at Missouri. Outlook for the final four games of the season. Brady Cook's return.

Big streaming numbers in Hawaii. Chairman still searching for the Tiger Striped Dress Girl. Time for Jackson's airing of grievances. Too many items in the self-checkout. FIght Pug, Beat Gator. Reviews coming in on the first week of shows on HD1. Jackson just can't let this grocery store thing go.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8053399488.mp3?updated=1731087937" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-4-24) Hour 1 - Where's The Dossier?</title><description>I hear buzzing. The Papal Conclave met over the weekend and congratulations to Buck Swope on winning the Milagro Tequila Listener of the Month. Tim's six-game parlay. Dan Lanning is taking food off of Tim's family's plate. TMA Trivia Night coming up. Is there more Chiefs or Cardinals gear around town? Naming the STL WNBA franchise. Rhythm &amp; Blues.

Jim Dandy at the Enterprise Center on Saturday night. Broberg's injury looked concerning. Injuries starting to pile up a bit. Doug's not happy with the price of parking at Blues game. Doug timed Berube's ovation. 2 minutes 15 seconds. Dirty wings. Hockey fans in St. Louis vs. Toronto.

Reuben Studdard, winner of Season 2 of American Idol, is unhappy in the YouTube chat. ESPN gives Mizzou a 6.5% chance of getting in the CFP. Can't see a scenario where Mizzou would have any chance of getting in. No signature win. Looking ahead to potential chaos in the CFP world.

Everyone that gambles is fat. The Doo Doo Man. Maurice Drummond and Martin filled in for Dan Patrick back in the day. College football teams running up the score.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4910513518.mp3?updated=1731091344" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-4-24) Hour 2 - What's Your Name, Pal?</title><description>Jason Kelce got himself into a little situation with a banty fan on Saturday. James Franklin got into it with an unhappy fan after the loss to Ohio State.

Chris Kerber joins us on the phone lines. Blues hoping to find some consistency. The Broberg injury. Roster getting a little thin with the injuries. Full Metal Jacket = Good. Martin's having some camera and computer issues.

Results from Friday's Pick Six segment. Tim wins the week. Home dogs in night games. Audio of James Franklin getting into it with an unhappy fan. Pat McAfee trolling Fox's pregame show. Today's phrase is Punching Down. Biff checking in on the phone lines. Biff &amp; Show making a comeback?

Tom Brady in the booth for Fox.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9071342821.mp3?updated=1731088637" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-4-24) Hour 3 Gabe DeArmond &amp; ETSY Shops</title><description>Gabe DeArmond from Power Mizzou joins us to talk about Brady Cook's injury. How good is Oklahoma? Fan frustration. How does ESPN have Mizzou at a 6.5% chance of making the playoffs? Mizzou more than likely won't have the resume to make the playoff. Will conference divisions make a comeback? Matt Zollers and next year's QB situation. Cousin Shane.

I hear buzzing. Audio of Joel Embiid getting into it with a Philly media member, man. 76ers taking on lots in fines for not properly reporting injuries. Are we back on AM? Jackson loves mischief.

The buzzing may have been fixed. Jackson loves to love. After a double deep tease, news on Broberg's injury. May miss some time but might have avoided a more serious outcome. Callers checking in to see when Biff and Show will be airing on 101. ROFLMAO.

Jackson's ETSY shopped selling game-worn wares. Welcome to St. Louis, Rodney Munoz. Gold Glove winners are out and no Cardinals made the list. CFP Rankings coming out tomorrow opposite the presidential election. Ray King joins us on the phone lines.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4246454932.mp3?updated=1731086922" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-4-24) Hour 4 - On My Granny</title><description>We're a trading post show now. Bad beat in the Bills Dolphins game on Tua's passing yards total. Jackson's Weekend Wrap Up. Who is the face of St. Louis sports? Is it Mo? Maybe Binnington?

Jackson's first question was poorly worded. Michael Thomas really wasn't happy with Saints QB Derek Carr yesterday on Twitter. Jackson's breathing technique. Chairman and Jackson constantly waiting for things to implode.

Who is the favorite to win the College Football National Championship? Cougar Night at Brick Tops. No clear cut favorite this year. Sam Hartman, va va va voom.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1577113723.mp3?updated=1731086747" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-5-24) Hour 1 - A Fistful of Pardons</title><description>Doug's not happy with the phone call filtering process. Jackson is committed to playing drops today. Rich Gould will be in-studio tomorrow at 9:00. Martin's got another surprise guest today. Where's Joe Theismann? Jeff Passan and Doug in 2016. Guesses rolling in for Martin's surprise guest. Jackson watched his Tigers last night alone. Not on board with Dennis Gates's rotation. Robbie Avila and SLU. Jackson's masochist tools.

Is Larry Nickel the surprise guest? Gabe's postgame show after the Tigers loss. Jackson's got a little Producer Joe in him. Martin studied some college basketball rosters last night. Larry Nickel makes his 101 debut with the WWE recap. Eric in the CWE claims everyone but Chairman has Low T. Pretty much everyone hates the show. Jackson names more than 5 NHL players. What a puckhead.

Sabrina Carpenter and Taylor Swift. Buck Swope getting banty at trivia night has become a tradition. Martin's looking forward to meeting some of the listeners. Ride hard for the Tigers. Alphas play defense.

Doug's hair is looking really thick. Jackson's laser helmet. RIP Missouri Baking Company. The Horny Baker. Fistful of pardons.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3910820597.mp3?updated=1731091548" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-5-24) Hour 2 - I Miss When I Was Happy</title><description>Ed Hermann in-studio. Players that have left St. Louis and had success. The Cardinals recent downward trajectory. The TV situation has handcuffed the team. Will Sonny Gray be back? Does Nolan Arenado want to be in St. Louis?

Blues play-by-play man, John Kelly, joins us to talk about Blues vs. Lightning. Broberg will be out 4-6 and it could have been worse.

Alperen Sengun. Big win for the Missouri Chiefs last night and they're on their way to an undefeated season. "Updating The Score Too Much Guy." Jason Kelce issued an apology on Monday Night Countdown last night. Not-so-supportive texts coming in about the program. Triggering people with NBA scores. Martin was going to fight Rich From Maryland Heights. Best SNL presidential impressions.

The Horizontal Tease. We're still clueless on Martin's surprise guest. Threats to slide tackle Jackson. Foot Sweeps at Rams Park. Marty, I am a Hoosier. Chris calls in with a hitting question for Martin. Chris wants small ball back. Yearning for HD2.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2959926399.mp3?updated=1731088045" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-5-24) Hour 3 - Show Me On The Doll Where The Sponsor Touched You</title><description>Audio of Dave Roberts talking about being afraid to go back to LA in the World Series. The Joe Kelly moan. The evolution of listeners harassing Doug. More audio of Joe Kelly on a podcast from his car. The potential for a Dodger dynasty.

Trying to adhere to the clock. What is the 2024 equivalent of Hoosiers &amp; Hummers? Where's Budweiser Mike? Martin's surprise guest coming up next.

The surprise guest is on the phone lines. It's Calvin May. How did Calvin land in TLR's lead-off spot? Anybody ever get upset with Calvin for his questions? His relationship with Butch Patrick. Hooking Joe Maddon up with an autographed picture of Butch Patrick. Friends for life.

Tom Schmidt from Salt &amp; Smoke and Caller Adam are in studio. They were told to touch a lot. Doug eats some ribs live on the air. Adam voted.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8217342538.mp3?updated=1731087536" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-5-24) Hour 4 - Hail To The Piddles</title><description>Time for Hail to the Piddles. Which MLB players would you wanna follow along their day-to-day in a Netflix show? You gotta think Matz is on the short list. Once you get past Ohtani, Judge, Soto, and Betts, who else has the recognizability? What is Jackson's life like outside of Hubbard? People texting in with tales of voting and wait times.

Doug flying out to Southern California to purchase some property. Players that you appreciate more as time has passed. Foughten. What about Boom Boom Gunnarson? Does Jackson know about Charles Barkley? He's devastated about the NBA on TNT. The last vestige of the St. Louis Rams. Some guy on Twitter.

Doug's gonna call Tim with an erotic story from the airplane. Doug's last show for the week.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6779589480.mp3?updated=1731089926" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-6-24) Hour 1 - Mid Market Homoerotic Sports Radio</title><description>Doug Vaughn is out and he's probably celebrating right now. Martin has been locked out of the dossier. Amendment 2 looks like it may pass but hasn't been called yet. Rich Gould, Jeremy Rutherford, and Jamie Rivers will be joining us today. Scary situation last night at Enterprise with Dylan Holloway. Audio of Drew Bannister discussing Holloway's injury.

Jackson is the only person on the dais that has been to The Hamptons. SLUH hasn't been the same since Tim got cut from the athletic program. Rich Gould fired off a red hot tweet yesterday chastising Dan Orlovsky. Reports have Amendment 2 passing by 7500 votes. Ears to the streets on a recount. Buzz needs more ass play.

Jackson is not on camera today. The line on the Mizzou/Oklahoma game has shifted. OU -3. Over/Under set at 41.5. Audio of Drink talking about the quarterback situation. Ween or Bob Costas? College Football Playoff rankings came out and Mizzou is #24. Just don't see a path to the playoffs even if they run the table.

Where were you when Amendment 2 passed? Worried Rich Gould may be sleeping. Gould may run the "car wash" here at Hubbard to talk about his book. Audio of Brayden Schenn &amp; Oskar Sundqvist talking about Holloway's scary situation last night. Naming the Blues all-time wins leaders for goalies. Who the hell is Greg Millen?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8682522716.mp3?updated=1731089762" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-6-24) Hour 2 - Smokin' On That Shirtenleib Pack</title><description>Bob Costas audio talking about retirement from calling baseball. Perhaps the fans' and media's critique has convinced him a bit. Al Michaels catches criticism for sounding disinterested at times. Calling games on television vs. radio.

We've got Radio Wars in Boston. Toucher &amp; Rich. Smokin' on that Shertenleib Pack. Jackson's not sure what he's supposed to be doing.

Jamie Rivers joins us to talk about handling the Dylan Holloway situation during the game last night. Despite the emotions the Blues find a way to get the win. Playing through their sticks. Utah Hockey Club coming up.

Rich Gould wanders his way into the studio to hold court.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6197927881.mp3?updated=1731087091" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 15:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-6-24) Hour 3 - Rich Gould In Studio</title><description>Rich Gould is for the 9:00 hour talking about how he got into writing his children's book. The book is based on a true story and Rich was the little girl. A true tale of bravery. Rich is down on Dan Orlovsky and high on Nick Sirianni. Nick and Jackson argue over Sirianni and the Eagles. Beta testing takes. Throwing Mickey Carroll out of a golf cart.

The Sea Spray Inn. Record for live shots in a day on local news. Does Rich miss local news? He's still having dreams about the business. He doesn't miss going into locker rooms to talk to 22 year old athletes. What was the Salad Days of local sports media?

Rich won't wait for people who are late. Somebody stole the station's conversion van back in the day. Tim's giant tie knot. How did Rich find the illustrator for his book? Is Rich financing terrorism by paying for the illustrations for his book? Playing guitar and reading the book to kids. Rich does appearances for book readings.

Quick segment to wrap up the 9:00 hour after visiting with Rich Gould.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1724646176.mp3?updated=1731087939" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-6-24) Hour 4 - That's A Scrotum &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Jeremy Rutherford joins us in studio talking Rich Gould stories. JR's perspective on the Dylan Holloway situation from last night. The identity of this Blues team. Two-part questions with JR. Texts are coming in and some aren't happy with us. Lee Stempniak's stench.

It's a Balloon Party tribute. Wide-Berth Wednesday. The Five Spot in the CFP is going to be coveted. Who's currently in the Top 12 that won't be and who is outside of the Top 12 that will be?

Breaking down all of our favorite moments from today's show with Rich Gould and JR. Rich's business card is a little bit phallic.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6356852633.mp3?updated=1731089919" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-7-24) Hour 1 - Move Girsch To Overnights</title><description>Oh boy, do we have a Jim Dandy today. Joey Vitale and SLU Coach Josh Schertz in-studio today. This height thing's a MFer. General banter has been upgraded to quality banter. Jackson doing material in the dossier. Chaim Bloom MAY be playing third base. Tough hair and complexion situation. Both can be true. Is Facebook here to stay, we'll take your calls. LinkedIn is the zenith of bragging. We're equal opportunity disrupters.

Burning an early timeout to regroup. Tims' the Bastion of Morality. Wilson Contreras is a first baseman now. Speaking to the bigger mess. Were fans happy with the signing at the time? Contreras's popularity in St. Louis. The market for Nolan Arenado. The Dexter Fowler narrative. Mount Rushore of What the Hell Are you Doing?

Natty Nate chiming in and he's not happy with the Cardinals. Where did he get the Natty Nate? He needs talked off the ledge. Lisa's up next and her blood pressure is up over this Cardinals situation. Look at Lisa with some scalding hot takes. Looking into getting some prizes for EMOTD.

Martin's late coming back and he may need to be talked to. Alliances are weakening. A little Cardinal anecdote from back in the day.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9650899872.mp3?updated=1731088412" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 14:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-7-24) Hour 2 - Shirt Tail Out Hobos</title><description>Joey Vitale joins us in-studio,. Getting a read on how someone is in bed based on how they bro hug. High-school shaming in St. Louis. Shirt tails were important at CBC. Jackson's sophomore team beat Jayson Tatum (He played 0 minutes). Martin's mom lobbying for playing time at CBC. Emotional guy at the end of the bench. Joey's happy to be out of the house. Did Tim give Joey the Heisman? John Kijowski makes a surprise appearance and he's not happy with Joey.

Step-by-step, brick-by-brick. Martin is enjoying the text inbox. Martin's wallet is a real situation. Martin's cleaning out his wallet live on air. RAfBaWG has a thing with billet moms. Joey's billet family experience was great. Joey with some actual insight into the Blues current situation.

Jackson's offered his services to dress up as a reindeer. Jackson's force-feeding Buddy Hield on us. Jackson prefers earth tones. Did Uncle Joey make the Red Wings sweater famous? Ranking hockey kits. Maroon and Chase stories.

Everybody is getting assigned characters for Joey's Christmas Party. Jackson's gonna be a slutty Prancer. Joey texted with Sid The Kid this morning. Crosby's a superstitious fella.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1414360983.mp3?updated=1731089035" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-7-24) Hour 3 - Billiken Coach Josh Schertz</title><description>SLU Billiken's Head Coach Josh Schertz joins us in-studio. Outlook on the season. Talking about the loss to Santa Clara. Disappointed in the loss but liked the fight and competitiveness. Why Coach Schertz took the SLU job and the process of landing here.

Coach Schertz talking about the decision and process of leaving Indiana State and coming to SLU. Talking to his players about leaving or staying. Avila thought about it over some orange chicken. The phenomenon that is Robbie Avila.

Jackson has been activated talking hoop rock. Coach talking about the question surrounding scheduling Mizzou. SLU's schedule. Rammer took a job for a trip to Hawaii.

"Fake Doug" in-studio for one last segment. The audience is dying to know Coach's favorite fry. Coach isn't exactly allowed fried foods right now. Coach is winning people over with his answer. Coach was quite the tennis player when he was younger. Tim went to Radio Camp. His coaching path and journey. Not much interaction with Larry Bird.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2175797877.mp3?updated=1731089120" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-7-24) Hour 4 - Fluid Alliances</title><description>People were big fan of the Coach Schertz hour. Coach may be part of the Jackson/Martin alliance. The Chairman/Tim alliance is really starting to gain traction.

This TMA Trivia Night is really starting to pick up steam. The TMA side and the 101 side. Who hates Tim the most? There's always someone upset. Martin's got an event in Perryville with Marshall Faulk. Shoutout to the Doolittle Fire Chief.

Are Billiken updates going to increase now that Coach Schertz is part of the alliance? Martin almost texted Tink Hence instead of Jackson. Doug Chandler Hill. Is there a recount for Amendment 2? Uncle Rich at the Christmas party.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7074236414.mp3?updated=1731001241" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 17:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-8-24) Hour 1 - Marshall &amp; Shorty</title><description>Call us and flirt with us. It's a big show today. Big, big show. Star-studded guests including Bill DeWitt III. Martin's tales of Perryville with Marshall Faulk. New segment: The Whitest Thing. Marshall &amp; Shorty. Robert Thomas will join us and Andy Strickland in-studio. TMA is kinda like your parents. Tim is the mom and Martin's the dad. Turnover Thursday for Kyrou. The Cardinals new TV deal.

The Backdoor Code to the Hamptons. Audio from Claibs Online with Mike Martz talking to Jim Thomas. The idea of the Rams moving going all the way back to 2001 and destructing the roster to help the move. Sabotage going way back.

Kyrou giveth and Kyrou taketh away. Audio of Steve Ott on the Kerbside Podcast talking about the play. A Canadian Rip Job. Self-inflicted wounds get the Blues again. We're gonna run it back. Drops of the week making their 101 debut later.

Will Tim's dad be at TMA trivia? Tamm Avenue Capital Partners. Armadillos, call in. Filling Martin in on Sweet Sweet Ky. Will Chairman be in Columbia not talking to females? Yes. Yes, he will. Ky's been promoted.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4498734138.mp3?updated=1731087290" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 14:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-8-24) Hour 2 - Robert Thomas &amp; Bill DeWitt III</title><description>Robert Thomas joins us talking about the boys scrapping last night but another disappointing loss. The scary Dylan Holloway injury from Tuesday night. The boys trying to stay positive through all the adversity and injuries. Robert will not be going to Columbia with Martin. Plowhawk was on KSDK yesterday and we'll have the audio coming up.

Audio from KSDK of The Plowhawk being interviewed following a tragic story of a man being found in critical condition along the banks of River Des Peres. Still shocked he weighs 115 pounds. Drops of the Week. Prod Joe's landing strip. Joe Buck took the ProdJoe firing pretty hard. I hear ya.

Bill DeWitt coming up shortly. Biggest questions for BD3. How will fans' interest in the team affect things? Will he announce the return of the navy road caps? We gotta work through this.

Bill DeWitt III joins us to talk about his reaction to the Cardinals television deal. The navy caps aren't gone. The direct to consumer option. What will the 2025 payroll look like? The middle ground of business and baseball decisions. Player development. What would he do differently if given the chance? Long term plans on team ownership.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4726705967.mp3?updated=1731089786" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-8-24) Hour 3 - Andy Strickland in Studio</title><description>Andy Strickland joins us in-studio. Breaking down the interesting parts of the Bill DeWitt III interview.

Blues HOFer Bernie Federko checking in. Talking Jordan Kyrou. The disappointing loss last night against Utah. Too many giveaways. Bernie has a good tailor.

Andy Strickland is loving the SportsCenter updates with NBA scores. We get Strick's thoughts on Jordan Kyrou and Jim Montgomery. Kyle calls in and wants Jackson's and the dais's takes on hitting from the chest to the belly button. The Cam &amp; Strick podcast is really taking off. We need to get Pronger on the show. Check out Strick's podcast with Patrik Berglund.

Short seggy but Chairman and Tim's alliance is stronger than ever while Jackson and Martin's is crumbling. Why did the BW3 interview resonate with people so well?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1806391271.mp3?updated=1731086918" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-8-24) Hour 4 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Gabe DeArmond joins us to talk Mizzou Oklahoma. Who does he expect to see at QB tomorrow night? Did the team get a boost from being ranked 24 in the CFP rankings and feeling like they may have a shot? The number on this game has been all over the place. What are realistic expectations for Drew Pyne and the Missouri offense against OU? The vibe in CoMo ahead of the game.

It's the market disruption, just be happy you're witnessing it. Tim and Jackson pick six games from the college football slate.

Is Oklahoma Mizzou's secondary rivalry behind Kansas? Courier Tom checks in with a Mizzou basketball question for Jackson.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9631292593.mp3?updated=1731091310" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-11-24) Hour 1 - WE Stand on Business</title><description>Doug's a huge Eddie Munster guy and back from The Hamptons. Doug, of course, had trouble renting a car in Palm Springs. Drink is mad at everybody. Katessy Shattel. Martin left the game early Saturday. Incredible environment at Faurot. Pyne Tyme.

Doug is the cute little girl in this Sadie Hawkins. There's been some excitement at Faurot this year. Audio of Drink post-game talking playoffs. Drew Pyne made some clutch throws in that final drive. Theo Wease's catach. Percentage chance Mizzou can back in to the playoff picture. Chairman's rage tweeting in the first half. The Path to Chaos does exist.

Blues took one on the chin over the weekend. Worst period of hockey in a long time. Some of the boys weren't happy with the effort. "Summer Hockey." People are holding us accountable for the poor performance.

Audio of Mike Kelly's call of the Zion Young scoop &amp; score on Saturday. Tom Hart called his shot on the turnover. Big test in Columbia East this coming Saturday.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9879335926.mp3?updated=1731336461" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-11-24) Hour 2 - Tom Hart &amp; Chris Kerber</title><description>Tom Hart calls in to join us fresh off of calling the big finish in Columbia on Saturday. Did he go to My House? What does he make of this 7-2 Missouri team? Looking ahead to the South Carolina game. Will Brady Cook be healthy for the SC game? The Oklahoma game was the type of game Mizzou historically loses. The SEC in the CFP.

Doug and Martin's hair combing decisions. Chris Kerber joins us talking combovers and Blues hockey. How do you explain these eight-goal beat downs? Battling through all the injuries.

Jackson is not resigning. What else would Jackson do? Martin issues an apology. Sports analyst, Tim McKernan. Upgraded from Godless pornographer. No update on Chairman's girl in the tiger striped dress. Jackson nailed it. Martin has a Gallup Poll. Are you satisfied with the Mizzou season at this point? The Block M came back.

Where is the Lover Man? Is there a step-dad's weekend in CoMo? Unfinished business with The Minutemen next year. Doug is putting people on notice. Toe service. Congrats to the Missouri Chiefs on their big win. Chiefs and Lions on a collision course. Urinating on your hands in the on deck circle to toughen em up.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3783960108.mp3?updated=1731341315" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-11-24) Hour 3 - Gabe DeArmond</title><description>Gabe DeArmond joins us to talk the night that was in Columbia on Saturday. Drink said the team's offense went according to plan. Hatred online for Drew Pyne. Using the naysayers as motivation. What percentage does Gabe give to Mizzou making the playoff? Is Brady Cook going to play?

Martin vs. The Cough Button. The Big Ten women's soccer finals in St. Louis over the weekend. Billy Crystal will be at The Musial Awards. Introducing Martin to Joey Zanaboni's work. Chairman Steve on the phone lines checking in. Does ProdJoe still have his landing strip? Steve's weekend wrap up.

Steve is our Lee Corso. Emotional moment on College Gameday with Kirk Hebstreit and his dog, Ben. Jackson vs. Dogs and Hot Fruit. Martin and Mr. Pickles. Nancy Drew books.

Poor clock management on Jackson's part.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6550178481.mp3?updated=1731343446" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-11-24) Hour 4 - JigJam &amp; EMOTD</title><description>Let's be honest, we're a variety program. The fellas from JigJam join us in-studio to play a little Irish diddy about St., Louis and McGurk's.

Martin is leaving TMA to join the band. Chairman may do a little karaoke rendition of "Steadfast Eyes" at TMA trivia. The Utah AD got a little banty after the Holy War game in Salt Lake City. Fines were levied.

A little quote from from some guy who was fired up bringing us back from break. Audio of South Carolina Head Coach Shane Beamer getting a little banty on Saturday after beating Vanderbilt. Who's your favorite live mascot? Jackson is respiratory shaming.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8620555118.mp3?updated=1731345321" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-12-24) Hour 1 - Necessary or Nonsense?</title><description>What's on the damn dossier? The Surprise Line is back. Necessary or nonsense? Tim knows bald spots. Big win for Mizzou Basketball last night against (checks notes)....Eastern Washington. Caller Mark chimes in with a TMA Special Project and it's not playing well. Chairman can't hear the phone calls. Phone lines might actually be poison.

Drink vs. Stoops. Drink kept receipts on Stoop's comments and Stoops clapped back on Oklahoma radio yesterday. Tiger Nationalists. Tim and Jackson can't remember what they wagered on. Will Cook or Pyne be under center Saturday? Armie Hammer and Timothy Chalamet had some incredibly sexual energy.

The phone lines are heating up and we start with Larry Nickel and the WWE Recap. Will listeners' wives pictures improve with the move to 101? Things aren't going well for Matt Eberflus in Chicago and that continued on Chicago sports talk radio yesterday. Who were the charter NFL franchises?

Subwoofers. Nonsense or necessary. Keith Tkachuk - Nonsense. Calvin Mary - Necessary. Tim's doing tours now.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3743687768.mp3?updated=1731423805" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 14:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-12-24) Hour 2 - John Kelly &amp; The Path To Chaos</title><description>Technical difficulties to start the segment and Doug has never been angrier. One complaint is better than zero. Airing of Grievances. Jackson's never had pumpkin pie.

John Kelly joins us to talk Blues/Bruins. What does he make of the 8-1 trouncing against Washington on Saturday? Keith Tkachuk's HOF resume.

Audio of Drink talking about 10-2 SEC teams getting into the CFP. Chairman Kurt has a Mizzou Path to Chaos with charts and graphs. The madness that is the CFP situation. "Who's Grifting" is coming back.

Monitoring the YouTube chats. Martin reaches across the aisle to give a game ball to Chairman Kurt for his charts and graphs. Taking guesses at the surprise guest. Libby Jack doesn't like Bruce Springsteen. The Alliance is back.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1017078075.mp3?updated=1731433809" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-12-24) Hour 3 - Who's Grifting &amp; Surprise Guest</title><description>Andy Crouppen joins us in studio. Talking a little college football with Andy. Singing the praises of the University of Wisconsin. Isthmuses.

And now it's time for "Who's Grifting." Todd Starnes wasn't happy with Michael Strahan during Fox's pregame show on Sunday. Fox is standing behind their guy. #controversy Oh my god that's Rich Gould's music!! Rich going after Doug and Jackson. Doug confuses Cignetti and Cirianni.

Time for the Surprise Guest. Coach Gary Kornfeld joins the show. Will he finally admit he made a mistake in cutting Tim from the football team at SLUH? What was it about Tim's game that he didn't like? Doug's going into the Kirkwood HOF in March. Nothing gets Doug laughing like Tim's high school height and weight.

Getting revenge against all the people who have wronged Tim. Mike calls in with tales of driver's ed with Coach Kornfeld.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4326102796.mp3?updated=1731433948" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-12-24) Hour 4 - Gallup Polls Galore &amp; EMOTD</title><description>How many SEC teams will make the playoffs? Can a one-loss Indiana team be kept out? There are no clear-cut top teams this season. Woof, woof, woof, you'll never bark alone. Jackson's Ladue accent. Audio of Syracuse head coach telling us he doesn't shower after losses. We need a group shower. MLS vs. NBA.

Reporting on our recent Gallup Polls. New TMA Wares on the TMASTL Shop. Esteban Yan checks in to offer more Paths to Chaos. Esteban Yan and Pedro Borbon.

Little Piddles Fun With Piddles on Tuesday. Is it important for teams to have a young star? Do the local teams currently have a potential young star?

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1275522221.mp3?updated=1731434099" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-13-24) Hour 1 - You Got a Carport, Martin?</title><description>The Foin Loins are poison. Jackson's scrambling. Martin's a jinx. Scott calls in with some concerns on the Chiefs but Doug is confident in their line play. What does Martin know about Hedonism? We need a little thunder in the two-hole. Jackson is locked out. Michael Strahan has issued a statement and people are outraged.

TMA YouTube is Webster Groves and The 101 YouTube is Cottleville. Martin's only on episode 3 of TMA. Carport Village. Wheels fell off in the third last night, eh? Blues struggling to get any points. Doug says the ice was tilted. Fan Confidence Index of local teams. The winter of our discontent.

The Head Mizzou Nationalist. Which coach does Jackson have the most confidence in? Steven wants to know what the return song was. Steven is down on Mozeliak. Maybe Steven will be a Wednesday regular. Jackson popped him. We're kinda like a truck stop. Jackson's curious about truck stop showers.

Are there a lot of communists at truck stops? Cell phone belt clips and loose change.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4845942066.mp3?updated=1731509625" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-13-24) Hour 2 - Jamie Rivers &amp; Truck Stops</title><description>Jamie Rivers joins us talking about the Blues loss last night. Giving us the business right out the gate. Has his opinion of the team changed since the beginning of the season? Jamie's truck stop experience. Jackson's helmet theory.

Audio of AJ McCarron with an "interesting" story from the day after the Kick Six game. Saban wanted to DNA test everyone. McCarron sure curses a lot. Georgia on the outside looking in after last night's CFP Rankings. Down on the Vols. Rough week for the picks last week.

Haunting rendition of Rocky Top. Hot Dentist. Pat Summerall and Murder, She Wrote. Airing of Grievances. Programming the 2Fox. Brian Stull validates Jackson's Helmet Theory.

Jackson has a carryover grievance. Jay Jr got mad at Tom Ackerman for wanting the NIT in St. Louis. For the Shoe.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8513134599.mp3?updated=1731512900" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-13-24) Hour 3 - Jeremy Rutherford &amp; Taking It Orally</title><description>Jeremy Rutherford in-studio talking puck. Rolling balls. That third period, oh me oh my. Is last night's loss worse than the 8-1 loss on Saturday? Not the young players making the mistakes. Leo Loof. Weekly Kyrou update. Will Joel Quenneville get a coaching job?

Now Martin has a belated airing of grievance. Just playin', sucker. Martin goes to the tough areas. Parking at The Enterprise Center.

This.....is Boof. Big Al is on the phone lines and he's giving us the business too. People coming at Jackson for his grocery store takes. Jackson takes it orally. Doug's clueless to the drug culture.

Audio of Coach Drink talking the QB situation for Saturday and having confidence in Drew Pyne. Is there a higher ceiling with Pyne or Cook? Who will Drink go after if the Tigers win?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7556381305.mp3?updated=1731516688" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-13-24) Hour 4 - Box Score Jim &amp; EMOTD</title><description>People weighing in on Cocky Drink and the Cook/Pyne debate. People are auditing Jackson's drops. Jackson and Tim wagering on the SEC teams in the CFP. Josh Pate has 5 SEC teams in. Rooting for an Indiana drubbing against an Ohio State. Big noon kickoffs in the Big 10. Jackson vs. The Big House.

People just aren't happy today. Drops and podcasts. People requesting drops. Friend of the show, Steven, is back for his second call today.

Is Steven the same as Box Score Jim? Results from yesterday's MLS/NBA Gallup Poll. Which team is closest to winning a championship: Cardinals, Blues, or Mizzou Football?

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2270260494.mp3?updated=1731519800" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-14-24) Hour 1 - Nasty Bit of Business &amp; Kelly Chase</title><description>(00:00-20:21) Red Hot Dossier. Kelly Chase will be joining us. We're the Ladue News of radio. Once you get past the Arnold Water Tower, all bets are off. The SEC begins in Jefferson County. TMA Walrus Number One checks in with an HD2 report and a Kelly Chase tale. Scenes from The Ritz Carlton.

(20:22-28:58) Listen to that jazz flute. Do visiting teams prefer to stay in Clayton? The haunted hotel in Milwaukee. The Chairman's Therapy Line.

(28:59-52:33) The Great Kelly Chase joins the show. Update on his health situation. His mindset throughout everything. Shaving his head and raising money for Siteman. The emotions going to his first game after the diagnosis.

(52:34-59:33) Gabe DeArmond says the quarterback situation for the South Carolina game is still up in the air. We have a big show lined up tomorrow. The Sklar Brothers and Joe Buck will be joining us. Where's Perc?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8425300687.mp3?updated=1731597361" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-14-24) Hour 2 - Robert Thomas &amp; Hype Songs</title><description>(00:00-12:50) Robert Thomas joins us. Back on the ice skating, Who makes the call on getting back on the ice? What's his role with the team while out injured? Golf game is on the shelf and his fantasy football team is spiraling. Who's on top of the Blues fantasy football league? Billet Families.

(12:51-23:24)Youngblood: Good or Bad? Jackson is preparing to launch a new uniform video series. What will Mizzou be wearing in Columbia East?

(23:25-33:49) Noteworthy developments in the Cardinals television situation. Amazon Prime. Wetting their beak. Linear television. Should be much more accessible to fans for streaming now.

(33:50-42:45) Cardinals hype songs over the years. The Heat Is On. Macarena. College coaches on the hot seat. Going over the EMOTD standings.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6396224487.mp3?updated=1731599672" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-14-24) Hour 3 - Bernie Federko &amp; Down With Tom Hank</title><description>(00:00-12:52) Bernie Federko joins us talking about the optimism of Robert Thomas skating. Does every forward want to be a center? St. Louis Steamers.

(12:53-28:00) Sports media news on John Gruden. Gruden will be joining Barstool. Audio of Boomer Esaison talking about Gruden being in the mix for some coaching jobs. Who would you rather have running your franchise: Gruden, Deion, or Bill Belichick? Favorite NFL owners.

(28:01-40:55) Free Dotem. Last day to post scores. Pourin' honey on you, goat. Spittin' Chiclets. Biz &amp; Whit trying to change the playoff format in the NHL. Stay out of the NHL, Haenchen. Strick was Strick Nasty before Biz was Biz Nasty. Johnny Load.

(40:56-55:14) Shout out to Matt. Dressing like a bear to do some robbin'. Our official Furry Correspondent, Buzz is ready and waiting. Change the station and touch grass. Will Jerry Rice be at the Tigers basketball game tonight? Re-evaluating Tom Hank. Floppin' since 2002.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1144135973.mp3?updated=1731603293" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-14-24) Hour 4 - Sports Hot Spot &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-7:25) Crowdsourcing the night game in CFB this Saturday. Tim and Jackson's wager. People mad as hornets over Georgia being on the outside looking in. What's the formula for these rankings?

(7:26-14:42) Gambling plays for Thursday Night Football. Spread covering in CFB as we come down the stretch. Shane Beamer may be looking to run one up on Drink and the Tigers on Saturday.

(14:43-20:37) Where is the hot spot for sports in the country when you include college and professional sports? Indianapolis is Jackson's dream sports city.

(20:38-27:56) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6762636859.mp3?updated=1731604469" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-15-24) Hour 1 - Just Wait Til 11</title><description>(00:00-21:36) Oh Doug, they were waiting on us. Strongest dossier to date. Joe Buck, Joey Vitale, The Sklar Brothers, and Gabe DeArmond all joining us today. Wild Hogs - Good. Does Tim still luh-luh-looooovve Georgia? Steve's mic drops aren't high on the priority list. We just can't win with these people. What did Lou Korac do? Blues drop one in OT in Buffalo. Bouncing around streaming services.

(21:37-35:28) We're just down to earth guys. Fading Tommy Castellanos as Mizzou quarterback. Willy nilly and pish posh. Beamer may wanna run it up on Drink. What kits will the TIgers be in? Desperately in need of an angel investor. Squattin' on domains.

(35:29-48:21) Jackson got to Chairman Steve's mic drop. So many emotions in one call. Really into hot mustard. Joe and Jenkins. Jackson and Martin's alliance is crumbling by the second. Uncle Doug. Bringing blow up dolls to parent parties.

(48:22-56:50) Colby Rasmus fire burning in the outfield. Mike Tyson vs. Jake Paul tonight. Audio of Mike Tyson in an interview with a young tike. Boxing has become a celebrity driven sport.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1236348847.mp3?updated=1731681846" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-15-24) Hour 2 - Joe Buck &amp; Drops of the Week</title><description>(00:00-28:04) Joe Buck joins us and he's impressed with Tim and his ability to recall years. Last week in Bloomington. Joe apologizes on behalf of Monday Night Football for ripping us off. His emotional investment in the Hoosiers season. Joe only will take the question from Tony LaRussa. Joe wants to hear the drops of the week. Not sure how to feel about the Cardinals. Being scared of Bobby Knight. Now we're just naming former Cubs.

(28:05-37:53) Lotta beefcake in this studio right now. Workshopping the Sklar situation. This is a place to go if you wanna win money. Time for the college football picks. The lone wolf barks alone. Piddles Nation.

(37:54-44:58) It's a Big Joe Friday on the show. Marty this, Marty that. Come back, Gary.

(44:59-47:03) Doug's working blue.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2188409280.mp3?updated=1731686944" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-15-24) Hour 3 - Joey Vitale &amp; The Sklar Brothers</title><description>(00:00-16:14) Joey Vitale joins us from Boston and he's not happy that we're 10 minutes late. Missing a minor league morning skate to hop on TMA. Some Blues players logging some hefty minutes. Settling for a Ladue girl at the Resurrection mixer. Stone Cold Steve Austin shirts. Little bit of Blues talk.

(16:15-30:23) Revisiting Jackson's Tom Hanks take. My opinion holds weight. The Sklar Brothers join us in-studio talking drunk Brett Hull. Jose Oquendo. David Freese. Where did they watch Game 6 of the 2011 World Series? Texting Kirk Gibson after the Freeman homerun. See them tomorrow night at The Sheldon.

(30:25-38:02) Teasing next week's surprise guest. Audio of Gary Coleman storming off the set of the The Insider. Who was the last guest to storm out of TMA.

(38:03-43:51) Martin's weekend plans. Doug may still go hang out at St. Gabe's tonight. Martin's going to camp out at Citizen Kane's. Rare plus.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8796382412.mp3?updated=1731689741" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-15-24) Hour 4 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-5:02) Chairman's fortress for EMOTD. Doug's looking kinda cute today. Jackson is down on basketball games in football arenas. Sitting in the nosebleeds at The Dome. Doug saw Lou Brock way up top. Money ruined the end of Game of Thrones.

(5:03-21:08) Gabe DeArmond of PowerMizzou joins us to talk Tigers and Gamecocks in Columbia East on Saturday. Colonel is betting on BC12 to start at QB. How's the Mizzou defense gonna handle this South Carolina offense? Mizzou has been successful in one score games. Gabe and Jarod both on SC. How about that Mississippi Valley State club?

(21:09-30:15) Jackson's Friday Six Shooter. Baths: Yay or Nay? Has William Shattner ever taken a bath? Tigers win, Chairman takes baths for a week straight.

(30:16-38:35) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6288210935.mp3?updated=1731692423" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-18-24) Hour 1 - Enjoy Your Shower, Baby</title><description>(00:00-17:59) Rough weekend for St. Louis with Mizzou, our Chiefs, and Mike Tyson all losing. What's on the dossier? Heartbreaker in Columbia East. Spit on it and shove it somewhere. Wishing you could have gotten more done with Luther Burden. The big boys gonna play in the Bowl Game?

(18:00-37:47) If you call in, be ready to give us your alma mater. The Palmetto State. Poor Chiefs. Lions are the new Super Bowl favorites. Winners get washed and Fran Brown gets to shower. Doug's feisty. Mt. Rushmore of NFL players. AJ McCarron out. Is Brady Cook Battlehawk Bound? Kirkwood vs. CBC. Eric in the CWE (Vianney/SLU) chiming in on the whole Chiefs thing. Eric doesn't like hot fruit either.

(37:48-52:08) Tim's got some new TMA hats. Martin and Doug have large craniums. Who stayed up for the Tyson fight? Tyson was cheeked up prior to the fight. Ah yes, the buffering. The House that Nootbar Built. Sydney Thomas was the star of the show Saturday. Jackson has so much Producer Joe in him.

(52:09-59:15) Joe Burrow wasn't happy with another tough loss last night. Growing disconnect between players and media. Poor lighting on Doug. Things are rising.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3181424730.mp3?updated=1731942282" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 14:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-18-24) Hour 2 - Chris Kerber &amp; Chaos Is Coming</title><description>(00:00-12:35) Martin nearly fell out of his chair. Chris Kerber of the Blues joins us to talk about the Blues getting three points over the weekend. Young guys stepping up with all the injuries. The status of Robert Thomas. Kelly Chase.

(12:36-25:31) Results of the college football picks from over the weekend. Maximum level of despondence. Weeping after the Norfolk State game. Jackson won't apologize for his emotions. Piddles buying out of his SEC Playoff bet with Tim. Kenny Dillingham. That 5 seed is the Sweet Spot. Chaos on the horizon.

(25:32-35:02) Audio of the emotional speeches from Jake Paul and Mike Tyson after the big fight on Friday. The Love Is Blind Reunion. The Netflix CTO came out with a statement. Netflix may be in for some problems on Christmas day with their NFL game. Shoutout Barry Keoghan.

(35:03-36:15) Gabe DeArmond joins us coming up next.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9166132436.mp3?updated=1731942884" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-18-24) Hour 3 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; Brat Doug</title><description>(00:00-25:07) Gabe DeArmond joins us fresh off the disappointing loss and dropping an F bomb in his post-game show. Gabe says Mizzou wasn't making the playoff even if they won out. Despite what one caller into Gabe's show said, Mizzou's offensive line had a great night. Brady Cook's performance. Mizzou bowl outlook.

(25:08-35:16) Callers holding Martin accountable during the break. Drink gotta keep these boys motivated. Jackson down on Mississippi State's cowbells. Chili Davis and Jeffrey Leonard. Mike Lee update. Ladue Blue.

(35:17-45:18 ) Cousin John and Martin's wife are Jackson lemmings. Martin enjoys a good vernacular. Highlights from Martin's interview with Dave Peacock. This show has ruined Martin in less than one month's time. There was a secret plan. Fun sized Snickers.

(45:19-55:30) Missouri uniform chatter. Doug's not happy with all the changes. Why doesn't Jackson respect tradition? Brat Doug. Jackson has an official statement on communism.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6660245736.mp3?updated=1731949915" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:03:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-18-24) Hour 4 - Sliding Doors &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-9:33) St. Louis Sports Fans' Winter of Discontent is here. Are the Blues a playoff team? Is it going to get worse before it gets better? Say words and figure it out later. No Country For Old Men. Sliding door moments of the Mizzou football season.

(9:34-15:35) Bring it to The Lou. Mizzou and Vandy and their place in the SEC. Basement people. Jackson addresses the newest video posted to the TMA Instagram.

(15:36-24:22) Weekend Wrap Up continues. Jackson vs. Pronunciation. Music biopics. People aren't ready for this conversation. Somewhere Under The Rainbow.

(24:23-34:18) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7806300401.mp3?updated=1731950436" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-19-24) Hour 1 - Soy Boy In Oregon</title><description>(00:00-14:34) Friends to the west, don't call in. Oatmeal didn't go to Kansas but he does have huge nipples. Bartender Kurt, ready for your grade level parent parties. Lean dossier. No jumpy sports lede. Big night for Binner. Pronger chose mercy. Who the hell is Bill Guerin? The roof is caving in at Jerry World.

(14:35-33:52) Martin brought in fun with audio breaking down Mizzou's uniform from Saturday. The olds want the Block M back. Loving Brat Doug. The Chairman is accused of being anti-children, which is kinda true. What a goon. Your own kids vs. everyone else's kids. Can we shame the fats? Who would you rather sit next to on a plane: screaming child or 400 pounder?

(33:53-44:50) Going over everyone's wardrobe. Steven is on the line with a comment on kids. Can we put kids on a leash? Was Jackson the crying kid on the plane? A romantic night at the Old Barn. Tim's kids are exempt from Chairman's anti-kid stance.

(44:51-50:27) What's Tim's luh-luh-luh-love pick of the week? Everybody like a good bowl projection. Brett McMurphy in the Gator Bowl against Syracuse. You can't run forever, Kyle. Jackson's taking a real "can do" attitude.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3060625052.mp3?updated=1732027425" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 14:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-19-24) Hour 2 - Chance of Light Grifting</title><description>(00:00-12:57) Ed Hermann is in studio talking about shame being the driving factor in his life. Being fat shamed. Catching Ed up on the olds, and the kids, and the fats from the first hour. Corporate shame. Legal standing of terms on the back of the ticket to a sporting event. Capitalizing on Doug's hunger.

(12:58-24:00) John Kelly joins us to talk about Jordan Binnington going after a historic win tonight. Great Blues goalies over the years. Impact of not having Robert Thomas. Blues need to get some wins in the division. Jackson has some light grifting in the forecast.

(24:01-43:06) A little light grifting with audio from Ryen Russillo talking about Indiana football. There's layers to this grifting. Russillo is famously unmarried with no kids. Ryen isn't the grifter; it's Danny Kanell with the light grift. If Indiana loses to OSU we may have some chaos. The muddy SEC sitch. Notre Dame's schedule. Jackson finally tried pumpkin pie and it tastes like fall.

(43:07-48:48) General Banter and the love affair between Sweet Sweet Ky &amp; RAFBAWG.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2377135570.mp3?updated=1732032285" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-19-24) Hour 3 - Letting The Devil Out</title><description>(00:00-8:03) Jackson has an angle. Inside the NBA licensed to ESPN. Audio ripped from today's headlines....in 2018. Hot takes on the TV over Martin's shoulder. Will Dan Orlovsky be on Inside the NBA? First time Inside the NBA can cover the finals. Doug's fed up. Are the Cardinals the mystery team in the Juan Soto sweepstakes?

(8:04-20:58) Our wrestling correspondent, Larry Nickel, joins the show to let us know what happened on the wrasslin' show last night. War Games preview. Doug thinks there's too much violence. Guessing the top 5 countries. Is Soto going to the Dodgers a problem for baseball? The spending gap in baseball. Childish Bambino.

(20:59-39:01) Was Jackson listening to Spittin' Chiclets? He likes hockey culture, it's just the game he is down on. Not much can pry him away from Cavs/Celtics. Doug just got old shamed. Jackson explains streaming to Doug. Fair and balanced audio. Sweet Sweet Bobby Lou talking recreationals. Justin Rose dropping heat at Bellerive. Letting the devil out. Mitch Album. Honestly, the end of this segment got away from us a bit.

(39:02-47:53) We're gonna give away some Post Malone and Jelly Roll tickets in the 10:00 hour. Post took a nasty fall at Enterprise Center and Jackson was there. General knowledge trivia coming up.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9052468148.mp3?updated=1732036429" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:03:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-19-24) Hour 4 - A Collection of Ghosts &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-9:47) Getting fired up for Jackson's trivia. Roddy RIch. Will Post bring the tail out? Jackson says it's intense being a celebrity of his stature. It's time for Tuesdays with Jackson. Coolest place to have seen or covered a sporting event. Who's spending money to go to the NFL draft?

(9:48-17:33) Sad Boy Post Era. Time for some general knowledge trivia. The answer is not Ricky Paulding. Would Jackson rather watch the Blues on the glass for free or stay home for Cavs/Celtics.

(17:34-26:24) Happier Post. The text inbox may be broken. Is there such thing as a "cursed" team? The Bears may not be cursed but they sure are bad. The emergence of ghosts would really mess with things.

(26:25-35:38) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3426962491.mp3?updated=1732038090" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-20-24) Hour 1 - Public School Hot Towel</title><description>(00:00-18:18) Gettin' high off the dossier. Newsbreakers dropping by at any time. Did Robert Thomas come back because Tim and family were there? Slide tackling Tyler. Another less than optimal third period. Remember the lesson, forget the event. Who the hell voted for Oli? Our forensics department is on it.

(18:19-36:08) Per the Post-Dispatch, there's a situation with the city's Rams money. Dysfunction abound. Welcome to the great unification. The Carlos Martinez perimeter of downtown. The perception of downtown St. Louis in many's eyes.

(36:09-46:48) Caller David on the phone lines with some thoughts on the downtown situation and ways to use the money. More discussion on the topic. We do have Auntie Anne's though. Bob is next on the phone lines with his thoughts on the situation.

(46:49-47:48) Quick seggie. Jim Montgomery fired in Boston. Jamie Rivers and Robert Thomas coming up.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7345766199.mp3?updated=1732113869" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 14:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-20-24) Hour 2 - Jamie Rivers &amp; Robert Thomas</title><description>(00:00-14:58) Jamie Rivers joins the program. Does Jackson have the power? Blues let a point slip away last night. Robert Thomas back on the ice. Binner would like to have a couple back from last night. The Blues lack of fire power. The Jim Montgomery situation in Boston. Martin working on a special (not surprise) guest. Jackson will allow audibles.

(14:59-24:28) The Kilcoyne Conversation. Audio of the intro from The Cover 3 Podcast. Doug's not a fan. Mizzou can't be killed. Is Danny Kanell trolling Drink?

(24:29-36:17) Robert Thomas joins us fresh off of returning to the lineup for The Note. Was he surprised by how quickly he returned? What's the mindset of the team when navigating this rough patch? Did he think about calling us to give us the scoop on his return? Potential NHL expansion. Updating us on his fantasy football team.

(36:18-50:03) Dave Peacock will be joining us in the 9:00 hour. Audio from Cleveland. Nevermind. Actually, wait, we might have it. Breaking Blues news that Doug's not gonna like.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3288960548.mp3?updated=1732119481" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-20-24) Hour 3 - Jeremy Rutherford &amp; Dave Peacock</title><description>(00:00-20:11) The Blues have unveiled their Winter Classic sweaters and in a shocking development, Doug is ok with them. Jeremy Rutherford on phone lines talking Blues Winter Classic kits. Robert Thomas returns. Two-part questions. Jim Montgomery. The Kyrou frustration.

(20:12-29:17) Jackson's best produced show. After a little back and forth, we've got the Cleveland Browns audio. Guy that leaves him out of breath Guy.

(29:18-53:34) Dave Peacock joins the show to talk Greater St. Louis and The Board of Aldermen. Figuring out the right formular for the entire city to "win." Confidence level in seeing real, positive change over the next decade. A St. Louis resurgence. NFL PTSD. The NFL &amp; St. Louis.

(53:35-1:02:02) New CFP rankings out. Audio of Joey Galloway talking about Indiana sitting their starting quarterback for the Ohio State game to protect him for the playoffs. Only one marquee game left inthe SEC. Shout out to Mercer.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1065069932.mp3?updated=1732123355" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-20-24) Hour 4 - Poppin' Spite Bottles &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00) We gotta get this clock back on track after the big surprise guest. Love you guys.

() Jackson's proclamation of his best produced show to date may have been premature. Steppin' on teases. AJ McCarron isn't happy about not being with the Battlehawks anymore. Get Cook and Schrader back together. Chairman is Team McCarron. KG's got champagne bottles ready to pop when his enemies fall. The Polar Express.

Jackson has changed hats. Why? Tim has looked really good in all of his new TMA hats. Views at Jackson's expense on the TMA Instagram.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7738798491.mp3?updated=1732125372" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 17:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-21-24) Hour 1 - Homeless Looking Libby</title><description>(00:00-19:56) Doug, it's nippy out there. Martin sat down with Bob Costas. Criticism of his play-by-play. The origins of Balloon Party. Costas wasn't high on the "Would Ya" segment in The Morning Grind days. He's become quite polarizing. LIbby Martin. AJ McCarron is none too pleased with The Battlehawks.

(19:57-40:26) Audio of AJ McCarron getting a little banty on a podcast about his departure from The Battlehawks. He may be down on KaKaw but he's still got love for St. Louis. McCarron seeking vengeance. Is this Buck Swope's time? Martin's diving into the text inbox. Rhythm and cadence. Brady Cook the next Kawterback? Shaw is gone.

(40:27-52:20) Frozen pizza. The Chairman dunks on Jackson's hot fruit take. Is middle school the worst age to teach? The puberty talk. Shrubs &amp; Tents. Brad calls in with thoughts on the city of St. Louis's issues.

(52:21-ESPN is pulling the plug on Around The Horn. Max Kellerman. Bill Plaschke vs. Jim Edmonds. Jim Montgomery and The Blues.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3081347754.mp3?updated=1732201470" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 14:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-21-24) Hour 2 - Bernie Federko &amp; OnlyFans Talk</title><description>(00:00-12:21) Bernie Federko joins us talking about Jim Montgomery and his firing from the Bruins. Would he ever want to get into coaching? The dynamics of the player/coach relationships. If Chief could get a cup in Toronto, they may name the area after him. You don't see a whole lot of player/coaches these days.

(12:22-34:10) Audio from Martin's conversation with Bob Costas about him stepping away from the play-by-play booth. No one gets out unscathed. Someone can be attractive without being attracted TO them. Will Costas get booed at The Musial Awards? Jig Jam hanging with ROR. As hoosiers, we boo the ones we love the most. Doug on kiss cam at the Blues game. JK Simmons was a great top.

(34:11-36:44) Well Doug, you're right, it's gotten away from us. Martin's got a surprise guest that is either gonna be really great or really terrible.

(36:45-52:15) People chatting about Jackson and LIsa Ann in the YouTube chat. Sleeping face down. Sydney Thomas will not be starting an OnlyFans. She's been ghosting us. People are creating faux OF accounts. Bhad Bhabie.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1851393091.mp3?updated=1732203921" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 15:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-21-24) Hour 3 - Clock Anarchy &amp; Surprises</title><description>(00:00-4:59) It's clock anarchy today and Tim's gonna get a talking to. It's already been quite a show today. Giving away tickets to Jelly Roll and Post Malone later on.

(5:00-41:58) It's time for Martin's surprise guest. Frank O. Pinion joins us. Life in retirement. Does he miss doing radio? Unsure about doing a podcast. Frank's still living in St. Louis. The Big Al clip. Trying to get audio of the Tunnels 12000 email. We finally got it.

(41:59-48:19) Jackson's down on himself for today's performance. The audience is on JBB's side. Jackson's buddies don't need free tickets.

() Lil' Shorty here trying to get back on track. Trivia contest coming up next.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2364523322.mp3?updated=1732208220" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-21-24) Hour 4 - Trivia &amp; EMOTD</title><description>It's time for Jackson's Jelly Roll and Post Malone trivia. The category is US Geography.

Keep an eye on Jeremy Rutherford's stuff about the Blues and Jim Montgomery. Reading between the lines.

We're almost back on track here.

E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5821923335.mp3?updated=1732212793" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 18:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-22-24) Hour 1 - Big Bounce Back Day</title><description>(00:00-16:34) What's involved in a good ruining? Keith Law. Goin' Huntin'. It's evident that Jackson's gonna have a big day. Where's the money on the Indiana/Ohio State game? We may have been a crossbar in overtime away from something significant last night at Enterprise.

(16:35-33:53) Blues came out hot last night with a goal in 12 seconds, go up 2-1 and then in the last ten seconds, boy howdy. Did the crossbar save Drew Bannister? Sliding doors moment. Binnington makes the final save in the shootout and ties Mike Liut for wins. Will Bannister be the coach still by The Winter Classic? Best excuses to get out of something. Is James Caville an alien? Bounce back dossier. 'Due time.

(33:54-42:48) RIP all the dead grandparents surrounding the old Girls Next Door competitions. Browns get in the win in the snow and we've got some Jameis Winston audio. George Pickens is down on the Browns even after losing to em. Crab legs got Jameis at FSU.

(42:49-56:54) Jeremy Maclin making a run with his Pioneers. McCarron vs. The Battlehawks. Audio of Battlehawks head coach Anthony Becht addressing the situation. The parting of ways "wasn't performance based." Kirkwood vs. Jackson should be a doozie tonight.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7726246159.mp3?updated=1732288568" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-22-24) Hour 2 - Joey Vitale &amp; Drops of the Week</title><description>(00:00-6:29) Let's take a look back at the week that was with The Drops of the Week. The Tradesman Hole. Monogramed Shawls. Would you pay $10 to watch a high school football game online? Cadet on Cadet crime.

(6:30-20:44) Naughty sweeper pics. Joey Vitale calls in to talk getting his young son into gambling. Joey's wife not necessarily on board with the mustache. Joey says there's no reason to part ways with Drew Bannister. Blues got a little tight as that clock ticked down last night. Shift length. Tim got the invite to the Vitale Christmas Party. Slutty Vixen.

(20:45-37:07) Does Doug have a bachelorette party this weekend? Reece Davis and Joey Galloway arguing on the College Gameday podcast about Indiana sitting their quarterback for the Ohio State game. A take going sideways. Doug's unhappy with the edit and Jackson falls on the sword. Culture killer to sit your QB in the biggest game in program history. Caller Jen is on the phone lines. She may be in on the Martin/Jackson alliance.

(37:08-49:23) Audio of comedian Brian Regan on his Netflix special with a humorous take on sports press conferences. Mike Ditka. Tim and Chairman may have a lady for their alliance.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7926872186.mp3?updated=1732290902" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-22-24) Hour 3 - Pick 6 &amp; Constructive Criticism</title><description>(00:00-13:04) Time for Pick 6. Rutgers is fancy pants. You ever watch that Meet the Press? You don't have to laugh about it. BYU's a fraud. Mizzou wins by 30 or loses to Hail State. It's a stinky spread. Lean into the stink. Keep an eye on them Gophers.

(13:05-24:20) If you were watching during the break you may have seen Tim and Doug kissing. Good one on line one is unhappy with some of the content of the show. Tim would like to make an official statement on the alleged make out session with Doug. Some are saying this show isn't gay enough.

(24:21-38:26) RIP Bankroll. Drinking scotch and watching Olympic hoops at Mungenast. Audio of Jason Kelce announcing his late night show during the NFL postseason. Guys need dudes. Are you a bro if you wear a tank top? Branch offs of the bro. Watch me take a three pointer, then tell me I'm a sissy.

(38:27-48:16) Favorite television shows from the 90's. Blues going on the road for 7 of their next 8. Audio of Jordan Binnington talking about tying MIke Liut for career wins as a Blue. The revolving door of Blues goalies. Easy, sweet baby.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5708169602.mp3?updated=1732294183" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-22-24) Hour 4 - Gabe DeArmond, TV Trivia, &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-16:16) Gabe DeArmond of Power Mizzou joins us to talk Mizzou/Mississippi State. Gotta win this one. Can you have a letdown and still win? Indiana vs. Tennesse for the CFP. SEC and Big 10 want assurance of 5 spots in playoff. Bryce Underwood flipping to Michigan. Is Brian Kelly in trouble in Baton Rouge?

(16:17-21:48) Doug, you like this return music? Time for Jackson's Jelly Roll and Post Malone trivia. How bout that Mario Lopez?

(21:49-26:03) Friend of Doug Jeff Passan with an article on the Cardinals and their reboot. What level of certainty is there in Helsley being gone? Jackson continuing to beat the John King drum.

(26:04-33:25) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4524730559.mp3?updated=1732297262" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-25-24) Hour 1 - Waiting To Chuckle &amp; Jeremy Rutherford</title><description>(00:00-18:45) We've got a big one today, and Doug's as surprised as anyone. Doug, tell us about scrums. Did you get ruined in Nashville? Jackson's freshly shorn. Five-year deal for JIm Montgomery. Hats off to Tim. Blues saw an opportunity to improve the situation and they took it. Rightsholder radio.

(18:46-30:10) Big wins for Mizzou and Illinois on Saturday. Both squads 8-3. Illini took down Rutgers in an exciting finish. Penn State escaped a near-loss against Minnesota. Teams found out via Twitter that they were going to their conference championship games. Penalizing teams for losing in the conference championship. Drink got a little banty at the end of the Mississippi State game.

(30:11-46:19) Jeremy Rutherford joins us to talk the firing of Drew Bannister and hiring of Jim Montgomery.

(46:20-54:16) Tim's four-game parlay. Audio from down on the plains for the ending of Auburn/Texas A&amp;amp;M in overtime. Layaway on lam-buh. The college football overtime rule is a two-point conversion festival. Staring down the barrel of more chaos in tomorrow's CFP rankings. One loss Indiana's resume. 

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9815877978.mp3?updated=1732545862" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-25-24) Hour 2 - Chris Kerber &amp; Jim Montgomery Scrum</title><description>(00:00-10:10) Chris Kerber joins us as he tries to dodge the secondhand smoke in NYC. How surprised was he by the Blues coaching move over the weekend? What's the level of disappointment in the current Blues product?

(10:11-18:24) You don't want Jackson on the witness stand. Bob Wallace will join us tomorrow along with Martin's surprise guest. New coach bump for The Note?

(18:25-34:05) Jim Montgomery's introductory scrum from Madison Square Garden. The dais's reaction.

(34:06-46:55) Jackson may wet himself. Jaxson Dart had himself a nice little cry on Saturday. Audio of the Ole Miss QB talking about the late interceptions. Florida has been a completely different team lately. Florida State free-falling. Who's the best team in College Football right now?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6185301814.mp3?updated=1732550631" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-25-24) Hour 3 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; The Dead Cat Bounce</title><description>(00:00-20:19) Gabe DeArmond of Power Mizzou joins us to talk about the win in Starkville on Saturday night. Looking ahead to the Arkansas game at Faurot this weekend. Brady Cook's post-Mizzou future. Mizzou's playoff hopes were shot after the loss in Tuscaloosa. The future of conference championship games. A potential Mizzou/Illinois bowl game.

(20:20-31:42) What's the approval rating of the Blues coaching moves from the weekend? Audio of Doug Armstrong talking about his decision. Armstrong wasn't planning on a coaching change until Montgomery became available. Lots of winnable games left on the table. Don't forget about the Dead Cat Bounce. Are the Blues moving to Cape Girardeau?

(31:43-43:10) Results from last week's Pick Six segment. No one on the dais had a losing record. Roll with me, Doug. The Har-Bowl tonight for MNF. Things aren't going well for the New York Football Giants. Audio of Malik Nabers not real pleased after the game. Jackson issues a statement on his misreporting of Brian Daboll's firing. Audio of a reporter asking Baker Mayfield about his Tommy Devito celebration.

(43:11-53:46) Who was happier to be fired: Jim Montgomery in Boston or Jimbo Fisher at Texas A&amp;amp;M with his $70M buy out. Martin's fielding complains at the 2Fox. Rough day for the Commanders kicker from Belleville. Which college football coach will be first to get the short haircut?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1707565431.mp3?updated=1732553331" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-25-24) Hour 4 - Mad Dog vs. Words &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-08:11) Coaching changes that seemed off in the moment. Octavio Dotel breaking the news of TLR's retirement. How 'bout that Nonling?

(08:12-18:33) Feel this funk. Audio of friend of the show, Mike Francesa, comparing Aaron Rodger's injury with his golf game. Mad Dog has a pronunciation issue. Thinkin' about doin' some sprinklin'. Fun with lines for Texas/Texas A&amp;amp;M and Mizzou/Arkansas.

(18:34-25:24) Only three more EMOTDs remaining in November. Jim Montgomery sounds fired up to be coaching the Blues. Audio of the Blues new coach talking about the Blues fans and the city of St. Louis. Jackson's never looked at the lines after a morning skate.

(25:25-34:40) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5039099850.mp3?updated=1732554883" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-26-24) Hour 1 - Blue Collar, Cheap Pop</title><description>(00:00-19:06) New coach bump, boy howdy. There's the humming. SOG, is what I call it. Dan Hurley of the JCC. Schedule the parade, the Blues are back! Different brand of hockey last night and those blue shirts didn't like it. Blue collar, cheap pop. What about the tripod? Audio of Monty laying hosannas on the boys post-game. Take your shirt off.

(19:07-34:27) Who yelled take your shirt off? Katie Woo reports that Cardinals are exploring trades for Nolan Arenado. Arenado moving to first-base? Owed money could be an issue. Nolan doesn't seem to want to be here. How will history remember the Nolan Arenado era? Mr. DeWitt, tear down that wall. Martin's taking his top off.

(34:28-46:04) Chairman's Therapy Line is ringin' off the hook. Audio of Brayden Schenn talking about the win at MSG last night. TLR was hanging out with John Gruden. Gruden asked Tony his top three clutch pitchers in the playoffs.

(46:05-53:10) Jackson is the media watch dog for this program. Audio from Cleveland radio not real happy with Will Howard's antics at the end of the Indiana game. Fun with odds and value for the CFP National Championship.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6442547478.mp3?updated=1732632451" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-26-24) Hour 2 - Bob Wallace &amp; Relocation</title><description>(00:00-14:46) Interim Head of Explore St. Louis, Bob Wallace, in-studio. Talking The Dome and Rams relocation.

(14:47-28:17) Talking with Bob Wallace about the St. Louis Football Cardinals relocation. Playing audio from Gene McNary talking about building a stadium in St. Louis County and the ramifications on his political career and audio of Vince Schoemehl's rebuttal. Asking Bob who was telling the truth. What lead up to the Cardinals leaving St. Louis?

(28:18-48:26) When did Bob notice the Rams relocation start to pick up momentum? No one was complaining about the dome when the team was good and the place was filled. Dealing with the city/county divide. How many billionaires we got in this area?

(48:27-51:38) Breaking down what Bob Wallace had to say.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7560005616.mp3?updated=1732635988" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-26-24) Hour 3 - The Interrogator</title><description>(00:00-9:19) Big night at Madison Square Garden. Audio of Jim Montgomery talking about the Blues tradition in St. Louis and the relationship with alumni. Seems like a good fit. Montgomery's style of positivity. When you set the bar low, you usually get there. Jackson's ready to scrap. Dylan Holloway was the shirt off guy.

(9:20-22:43) Hey, Doug, it's Andy Crouppen. The NFL likes when you sue em a couple three times. Fixing St. Louis's problems start with acknowledging St. Louis's problems. KMOX? Never heard of her. The sibling rivalry between the city and the county.

(22:44-43:36) It's time for Martin's surprise guest. Jackson may have ruined the surprise with a tweet. The Governor Steve Kline joins us. Enjoying life as a college coach. The cradle of coaches. Missing the stag bars. Has one of his players ever flipped him the bird? Banned from Cardinals Fantasy Camp. The Interrogator.

(43:37-46:58) Fun night in NYC last night. Hoping that'll give the boys a little momentum going forward.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8108016906.mp3?updated=1732640151" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-26-24) Hour 4 - John Kelly &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-13:28) John Kelly joins us talking about Monty's first win as Blues head coach last night. Getting Hofer more playing time going forward. JK's observations on the moves Doug Armstrong has made over the last few days. Montgomery the right coach at the right time for connecting with young players. How long can this new coach bump last?

(13:29-23:20) Jackson's been waiting on this topic for a few hours now. Takes on Danny Hurley gettin' T'd up in OT in the loss to Memphis. How do you get so angry in a guayabera shirt? Chairman used to get run out of SLABA games.

(23:21-28:28) I need a 30. We want more sports and less sports simultaneously. The plight of drops on 101.

(28:29-37:56) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9972956279.mp3?updated=1732641365" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-27-24) Hour 1 - A Little Bridge With My Face</title><description>(00:00-24:30) Red Alert, Red Alert. Jackson woke up Robert Thomas this morning. Sleepin' face down. If I ain't gonna sleep, neither are you, Bob. DIckie Betts. Michael Cera Vibes. Fun with the MSHSAA map. Relationship Jack. Getting hate for staying in St. Louis. Manual stimulation night at the Ballpark. TLR's Goldberg t-shirt. Skanksgiving Depression.

(24:31-36:21) Doug, what's the lede? The Dodgers can't stop signing big contracts. They's on scholarship too. Except the Pirates, they've got some walk-ons. Win the press conference, not the offseason. The Yankees and Red Sox arms race in the early 2000's. Winning the '06 and '11 World Series solidified a mindset with the Cardinals.

(36:22-49:49) New College Football Playoffs rankings are out. Chairman's search for tiger-striped dress is dead. There's a chance the Big XII could be left out. The committee focusing more on the wins than the losses. Three loss South Carolina can make a jump if they beat Clemson. It's running up the score SZN. No motivation to schedule quality non-conference opponents.

(49:50-51:23) Hoping Jackson waking up Robert Thomas isn't an issue. May wanna bet New Jersey.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5164272588.mp3?updated=1732721315" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-27-24) Hour 2 - Robert Thomas &amp; Jamie Rivers</title><description>(00:00-15:18) Robert Thomas joins us and he doesn't sound real thrilled with Jackson's early text. Not easy losing Drew Bannister but excited about getting a coach like Jim Montgomery. Young players trying to live up to the hype. Addressing the "Take Your Shirt Off" comment after the win on Monday. Can media call players by their nickname?

(15:19-34:12) Jackson's feeling absolved from any Robert Thomas guilt. We're huge in Puerto Rico. Shoresy. Maybe it was a horned up boy. Chaser's Shouldys. We're gonna do Rivers now! Hi, Jamie. Talkin' new coach bump.

(34:13-46:48) Jackson was presented with an award during the break. Take your shirt off, Jack. JB gives an acceptance speech and it's moving. Remember Trung Canidate? Audio of Ken Rosenthal talking Cardinals moving Nolan Arenado. 2025: We're Sitting This One Out. Who's more likely to be at this Spring Training, Nolan Arenado or this show? A hug takes place and a GIF has been made.

(46:49-1:01:58) Jackson's St. Louis Starter Packs Skanksgiving post is choice. Rainbow showers. Is Skanksgiving amateur hour? Weekday day-drinking. Martin is trying to recruit The Chairman to his alliance but Tim is his one and only. Jackson respects verticality. South County specials.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1083044562.mp3?updated=1732722262" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 15:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-27-24) Hour 3 - Pick Six &amp; Tiger Nationalist Doug</title><description>(00:00-16:58) The usefulness of the jock strap. E-Mail of the Day showdown today. Time for Pick 6. Jackson is Petey Public. Doug's getting fed up with the segment. Longhorn Doug. Bonus points for lock of the week.

(16:59-26:36) The Dodgers assembling themselves a nice little all-star team. Sonny Gray, now we're talking. Jackson declares you can't win a World Series on paper. Would the Dodgers be interested in Nolan Arenado? Red Sox keep coming up in regards to Arenado.

(26:37-35:59) Looking like Cook and Burden's last games on Saturday. Audio of Brady Cook talking about his legacy at Mizzou. Where does the 2023 team rank all-time at Mizzou? What might have been with Jayden Daniels in a Tiger uniform. Is Doug Tiger Nationalizing?

(36:00-38:29) Jeremy Rutherford will be joining us coming up but won't be in-studio.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2254177390.mp3?updated=1732727270" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (11-27-24) Hour 4 - Jeremy Rutherford &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-19:28) Jeremy Rutherford joins us to talk about the Blues and new coach Jim Montgomery. JR does TikTok dances and Get Ready With Me videos. Playing the "Take Your Shirt Off" audio for JR. Can a dead cat really bounce? Beautiful Newark, New Jersey. JR dunkin' on STL. News and notes for tonight's game in Jersey.

(19:29-27:44) Chairman doesn't have a LinkedIn page. Recovering Alcoholic from Belleville &amp; Webster Groves checking on the phone lines. Here for the milking. A Cam Janssen statue with a nice bulge. Ice heads from Dupo. Staten Island is the Jefferson County of the New York burrows.

(27:45-32:44) RIP DMX. DMX gave a sermon at Hooterville. Wide Berth Wednesday. Social faux pas. Rawdogging is timeless.

(32:45-42:02) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7063635345.mp3?updated=1732729996" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-2-24) Hour 1 - It's Not Romantic, It's Erotic</title><description>(00:00-19:04) Festive Banter. Audio Galore. Gus Johnson had a rough go of it on Saturday. Planted flags 'o' plenty. Are you pro or anti flag planting? Ohio State Jack Sawyer wasn't about to let that flag get planted. Ryan Day feelin' the heat in Columbus. Furnace Face. Dan calls in unhappy with Jackson's Thanksgiving programming. You hurt him with that one, Pale.

(19:05-33:36) One at-large spot out there for the CFP. Jackson doesn't wanna talk about his lock of the week. Texas A&amp;amp;M blowin' up parlays. It's not romantic, it's erotic. Rolled 'em at Willie B. Coaches are running up the score all over the place. James Franklin and the Maryland coach got into it about scoring late in the blowout. The Audio Ranking Committeee is confusing. Barry Odom and the Runnin' Rebels.

(33:37-43:02) Tears at Enterprise Center. Binnington with some big saves on Saturday. 5 of 6 points since Montgomery took over. Audio of Binnington talking about the all-time wins record as a Blues goalie. Thomas got the Burkett Bump in New Jersey. It's about Bob. Wins Per Game. Did we just stumble into the perfect system?

(43:03-54:56) Chaser in the booth on Saturday. The Battle Line Rivalry. Brady Cook takes his final touch as a Tiger to the house to win it for Mizzou. Love Howard Richards. Audio of Drink talking about the "rivalry." Pittman just coaching in darkness from the press box. Would Mizzou be in the conversation had they beaten South Carolina? Impressive wins vs. losses. Conflicting messages from the committee.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4190610536.mp3?updated=1733150577" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 14:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-2-24) Hour 2 - Dodger Blue &amp; Gettin' Washed</title><description>(00:00-8:44) Filling Doug in on K Dot and Dodger Blue. Stop with the scat play. Arenado's photo dump. Missed opportunity not parting ways with Arenado sooner. Red Mean Go. Dodgers making it rain. College Football Playoff overtime rules.

(8:45-20:29) Chris Kerber joins us. Blues getting 5 of 6 points since Montgomery came aboard. Different feel to the team with the coaching change. Having Chaser in the booth. Make or break month of December for the Blues.

(20:30-31:52) Syracuse Head Coach, Fran Brown, had himself some fun on Saturday beating Miami. I'm getting washed, ayyyyyy. Was the Texas Tech coach going after Gary Pinkel? Wide delta for Clemson pending what they do in the ACC Championship. Takesmith's Delight on Thanksgiving with the Bears clock management. Jackson wants a Madden playing teenager as a clock management coach. College programs naming GMs.

(31:53-40:06) Going through some old texts. People are down on Jackson's Madden Kid idea. No plans to walk back the take. Clearing the deck. We all get choices everyday. Ok, Bucko.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1626268485.mp3?updated=1733152706" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 15:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-2-24) Hour 3 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; Uniform Jack</title><description>(00:00-32:03) Gabe DeArmond of Power Mizzou joins us to talk about the Tigers wrapping up the regular season. Tigers post season hopes were dashed after the loss at Alabama. Good ending to Brady Cook's Mizzou career. Looking back on the disappointing offense throughout the year. Reasons to be optimistic after a 9-3 season even though no playoffs is disappointing. Brady Cook's comment on the negative culture in the program. Barry Odom's guy vs. Eli Drinkwitz's guys. Cook won't be getting a waiver for another year. Looking at possible bowl games. Who's Gabe's pick to win the CFP?

(32:04-38:21) The possibility of Mizzou and Colorado meeting in The Vegas Bowl. Audio of Deion Sanders talking about his seniors intending to play in the bowl game. It would be a game changer if everyone collectively bought into these bowl games. Doug's a BIG fan of Ralphie The Buffalo.

(38:22-52:01 ) How'd you like that SportsCenter update. Tim's unintentional spit take. Arch Madness. Taking people's temperature on the NBA talk. Pro Squash updates. Uniform Jack on Twitter. Swiming in a t-shirt. Supple man breasts. Band aids floating in the pool. Who's the guy moaning in the background? The infamous yellow diaper.

(52:02-59:42) Jackson's weekend wrap-up. Which sport has the best fighting? Baseball fights. Running down from the bullpen. Is Jackson down on UFC? No more talkey for Jackie.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9444545402.mp3?updated=1733158164" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 16:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-2-24) Hour 4 - Weekend Wrap Up &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-15:33) Who is the athlete version of the McRib is an actual question that was just asked. What alt cast would you most want to see across sports? Dick Van Dyke and Goldie Hawn. Did Ozempic get Lainey Wilson? Is Lainey interested in Chairman Steve? Duck Hodges. Those are my ass pants.

(15:34-19:25) All Lainey Wilson, all the time. YouTube premium.

(19:26-26:35) Just gettin' ourselves situated over here. Who is one player the Cardinals have traded or released in the last four years you would like to have back? Alright, fine, last five years. Let's just go back to Joy Behar. Brief airing of grievances. Pillows for road trips.

(26:36-35:44) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB9195723247.mp3?updated=1733161727" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 17:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-3-24) Hour 1 - Simps on Twitter</title><description>(00:00-24:06) We've got quite the lede today. Tim dresses like a gerbil. Mr. Lix is an Alliance Free Agent. What's the most sensual mascot. The Miami mascot, Sebastian, spittin' game at a Syracuse reporter. Mrs. Red can get it. A nose for news. Sweatiest coaches. Attracted to all three in different ways. Non plus on WPG's jerseys.

(24:07-35:16) The Papal Conclave met yesterday to name the November LOTM. Martin didn't realize it was a real thing. Congratulations John Skorcz. The math isn't mathing. It's serendipitous. Bob Wagon can't be happy about this. The process played out. Real men dry scoop. Split custody of the tumbler.

(35:17-49:52) Winnipeg: The Gateway to the West. Per Katie Woo, it's not a lock that Arenado is gone but clarity could come next week at the Winter Meetings. Switching from third-base to first-base. What happens with Helsley? Cards need to pick a path, in or out.

(49:53-54:21) You like this beat, Doug? Are resume reels still a thing? Adios, Luther. List of top reception leaders in Mizzou history.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8258192549.mp3?updated=1733236878" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-3-24) Hour 2 - Here I Am: Unsatisfied</title><description>(00:00-22:08) Ed Hermann is in-studio. Has he been retained as counsel in the November Listener of the Month shenanigans? Talking Cardinals &amp; Nolan Arenado. Putting the best product possible on the field vs. appeasing fans. Parity in baseball.

(22:09-35:27) John Kelly checking in talking about the Blues going up against Winnipeg. Audio of JK's call of Bnnington's Dominik Hasek-esque save Saturday night against Philly. Knowing whether you nailed a call or messed it up right away. Binnington and Hofer's internal competition. Relentless stretch for the Blues upcoming.

(35:28-50:52) Pritch better have my money. Jackson's not for the masses. Don't jinx Tim's beard. It's official: Luther Burden is declaring for the NFL draft. Audio of Drink talking about LB3's legacy at Mizzou. Where does Luther fit in the list of all-time Tigers? His NFL potential. Here I am, unsatisfied.

(50:53-1:07:28) Oh to be a fly on the wall in that box. Are Hotty Toddy or South Carolina gonna leap Roll Tide tonight in the CFP rankings? Hard to know what the criteria is with the committee. Jackson is going all Orlovsky over here. I just want some glory. The glory days of Dear Deidre.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7508039899.mp3?updated=1733240900" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-3-24) Hour 3 - Release The Hoosier</title><description>(00:00-08:44) Bad beat last night on MNF. The Full Jameis Winston Experience last night. Audio of Jameis after the loss last night. Uniform Jack on the Broncos helmet. The Sean Payton apology tour.

(8:45-20:59) Talking MLB's Golden At-Bat idea. Not to be confused with the golden goose. Is this idea worse than The Man &amp; The Woman? Release The Hoosier.

(21:00-32:17) Chris checking in on the phone lines with a question for Jackson. Chris has some interesting lineup ideas. Martin tries to butt in but he's having none of it. One of the best phone calls in show history, in my opinion.

(32:18-38:54) Jackson paying off on his SMU/Indiana tease from earlier in the show. Just a guy on Twitter. The Positive Feedback Loop in College Football. Get a blog, bro. Doug's belittling Jackson's passions.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6366387291.mp3?updated=1733244339" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-3-24) Hour 4 - Sky's Out, Thighs Out &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-8:27) Jackson's got questions. Worst fashion trends and ones you wish would come back. Short shorts. Ankles out. Dickies. Turtlenecks.

(8:28-10:04) Some big guests coming in-studio this week. Bengie Molina, Doug Armstrong, and Charlie Marlowe.

(10:05-16:32) Tony Finau has withdrawn from the Hero World Challenge. Is he leaving for LIV Golf? Hello, Drama. Rumors surrounding Jordan Spieth as well.

(16:33-22:24) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8229857374.mp3?updated=1733245966" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 17:06:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-4-24) Hour 1 - Get Off Your High Horse</title><description>(00:00-15:39) Boy Howdy, do we have a great one lined up for you today, Doug. Did Ruthsy pass on the Winnipeg trip? This show needs a decoder ring. Maybe I did, we talk a lot. Jackson on the lookout for Siamese Twins. Jordan Kyrou, how do you do? 7 of 8 points with Monty. Can we make Doug Armstrong weep? Big night for the fighting Tigers. Banners are forever. Vacationing in Hampton Village. A very Heteronormative Doug.

(15:40-34:23) Jackson's trying to slither away. Volume of engagement, Doug. Ward Manuel on the latest CFP rankings. Did Sebastian cost Miami a spot with his filthy behavior? Alabama gets the spot over Ole Miss. Which of the teams can make a run and win it all? The three-loss SEC teams are locked in place. Is Charlie Marlowe reeling?

(34:24-47:57) Martin has a question. TMA Sleeper Cell. Is Chris real? NHL '94. Starting Hofer over Binnington in Winnipeg. We need a take your shirt off remix.

(47:58-1:01:35) Scooter accident got the delectable Danny Pintauro. Are the Scooters a bad idea? The Golden Scooter. Off-season in The Vineyard. Lots of Jackson's friends went to SMU. Audio from an SMU Tailgate flexing their wealth. Gambling allowances. Herpes, right? Body Jelly. Barry Keoghan.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1656527847.mp3?updated=1733324120" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-4-24) Hour 2 - Doug vs. Zach Bryan Shaming</title><description>(00:00-17:57) Getting content out on the TMA socials. Some of the hosts collab, others not so much. Jackson's heatin' up. But he's got some hot coaching takes he needs to get off his chest. Gates's rotation. The Bunny Hill portion is over.

(17:58-27:09) Cruisin' around Francis Park with a subwoofer in the back. Audio of Dabo Swinney who is awful. The Alabama brand-itocracy. Mizzou's ranking helps Alabama's resume.

(27:10-36:07) Zach Bryan is trending and people are apologizing for listening to him. We all listened to Kendrick this year. Don't need to see your Spotify Wrapped. This is an a la carte menu. Doug and Chairman get in a heated debate over the Zech Bryan/Briana Chickenfry drama.

(36:08-40:35) Jeremy Rutherford in-studio to defend Jefferson County’s honor. It’s like a JeffCo trailer in this studio. 

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5280781130.mp3?updated=1733326957" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-4-24) Hour 3 - Jeremy Rutherford &amp; Bengie Molina</title><description>(00:00-17:50) Jeremy Rutherford in studio talking about the Blues turnaround with Jim Montgomery. The Take Your Shirt Off moment was a catalyst. Two-part questions.

(17:51-54:21) Bengie Molina in-studio for the rest of the 9:00 hour. Talking about his Christmas Toy Drive. Broadcasting the Cardinals' Spanish language broadcast. What the city of St. Louis meant to him and his brother. Spanish language listeners from all over the world. The possibility of Yadi someday managing in St. Louis. Would Albert and Waino join the staff? His thought on the Cardinals off-season.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6231718206.mp3?updated=1733330898" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-4-24) Hour 4 - Jamie Rivers, Mizzou News, &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-4:39) Breaking down Bengie Molina's comments on Yadi's desire to manage in St. Louis. Sounds like he doesn't want to coach. Waiting until his son is finished with high school.

(4:40-15:52) Jamie Rivers joins us to to talk about the Blues win over the Jets last night.

(15:53-21:57) Gabe DeArmond reporting he believes Mizzou has interest in USC quarterback, Miller Moss. Moss could be a bridge to Matt Zollers. Conner Weigman.

(21:58-30:28) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3286116861.mp3?updated=1733334532" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-5-24) Hour 1 - Saddledome Fact Checking</title><description>(00:00-30:38) Heavy on words, light on meat. Charlie Marlowe will be joining us in-studio at 9:00. The Four Nations Face Off is replacing the NHL All-Star game. Prague is beautiful this time of year. Doug's recruiting process to TMA. Breaking Doug news in the YouTube chat. Bengie Molina's comments on Yadi yesterday. Talkin' ball with the writers. Bengie mentioned Yadi having of a staff including Wainwright and Pujols. Martin's hat from yesterday.

(30:39-44:52) We're the talent. Doug doesn't wanna bug people. If Molina failed as Cardinal manager, how would it affect his legacy? We're getting fact-checked. Sock crust. Laundromat. Cardinal managers.

(44:53-54:45) Why did Jackson rig the Listener of the Month election? We've got a show announcement coming up at 9. Tickle, tickle. There's no such thing as waste. NBA Cup. Doug's fancy new haircut. Shirseys over hoodies: Is it Hoosier?

(54:46-1:02:44) Charlie Marlowe's resume tape. We'll figure it out. Jackson didn't send Robert Thomas his morning text. Mopes. The Red Screen of Death. Does sabotage need intent?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6517163761.mp3?updated=1733409939" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-5-24) Hour 2 - There's a Gerbil Down There</title><description>(00:00-13:32) It's show announcement time. Doug's gonna be dressing up like Santa. You can sit on his lap. Keep up with these nonsensical narratives. Could get a little naughty. End of the Year Awards will be given out next Thursday on-air.

(13:33-27:06) There's a gerbil down there. Is Buck Swope the better favorite for Listener of the Year. Shane Beamer isn't happy with the data points not adding up. The incentive to schedule tough non-conference games. The eye test comes down to brand. Audio of SMU Coach Rhett Lashlee talking about the craziness of the current system.

(27:07-38:27) Blues legend Bernie Federko joins the show. The Blues turnaround. Getting the offense going. Can the Blues climb back into the playoff race?

(38:28-49:35) Friend of the show, Charlie Marlowe joins us in-studio. Was he Martin's assistant? Missing the day-to-day of television and radio in St. Louis. All NASCAR, all the time. Partnering with Dale Earnhardt Jr. God bless those high schoolers. A symphony of Charlie Marlowe drops. Similarities between Jackson and Charlie.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5400032237.mp3?updated=1733413366" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 15:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-5-24) Hour 3 - Charlie Marlow &amp; The Naked Mark McGwire Era</title><description>(00:00-17:36) Hangin' with Chuckles. Editing clips for socials. Professional Liar. What did he learn from the Kevin Demoff incident? Easter eggs for the TMA audience. Learning NASCAR. Rubbin' is racing. NASCAR fights. Ohio State and Ryan Day. Planting the flag.

(17:37-33:06) Subscriber talk with Charlie. Dirty Mo Media. Blaming the Cardinals for the decline of his YouTube. Does Martin work for every station in the area? Jackin' around. The naked Mark McGwire era. Charlie No Text. More Charlie Marlowe drops. Doug's hair.

(33:07-37:46) Lydia Moss Bradley and Tuna Fish Vaughn. Can't get tuna too frequently. Charlie reports, you decide. Great times with Charlie today.

(37:47-40:31) Looking forward to the TMA Christmas Party and Santa Doug handing out tickets left and right.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2467729301.mp3?updated=1733420439" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-5-24) Hour 4 - Robert Thomas &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-16:29) Robert Thomas joins us. It's cold in Calgary this morning. He's not looking to continue Jackson's early morning texts. Did the "Take Your Shirt Off" fire the boys up? Players appreciating things like Montgomery playing Hofer in his hometown. The mindset of the team and their playoff possibilities. Morning skates.

(16:30-24:42) What comes over you when you feel naughty? Where The Wild Takes Are. Audio of Joe Bonigno claiming he got COVID from the Jets loss. Audio from the Dan Lebatard show in 2015 with Rob Manfred talking about The Golden At Bat rule.

(24:43-33:02) Recapping the comings and goings of the day &amp; EMOTD

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3009388983.mp3?updated=1733420418" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-6-24) Hour 1 - We Are Where The News Is</title><description>(00:00-18:29) Morning cuties, Happy Friday. Doug's a little washed out. Is Doug Armstrong nervous about coming in-studio? Which executives can you send a kissing emoji to? Robert Thomas can't stop scoring on days he comes on this show. Shout out to all stenographers out there. Jury duty. Would you sleep with Idris Elba? Ryan Helsley. Like gerbils in a tube. Trading bullets for the gun.

(18:01-40:07) What's a Don? Audio of Jim Montgomery talking about Parayko's OT game winner last night. Eating pizza waiting on the good goal call. Vaughn Index update. Jackson's not familiar with the Monday Night Miracle. Jordan Binnington on the team's commitment and excitement. Momentum in the room. Can you eat pizza on the bench? Bevo banned. How much does a moose weigh?

(40:08-54:08) Discussing the Post-Dispatch article asking if the Chiefs popularity in St. Louis will pass that of the Cardinals.

(54:09-1:04:35) Audio of Mike Francesa's reaction to The Golden Bat Rule. He's out. Big doings next Thursday night. Why does Doug hate Kung Fu Kenny? TMA End of the Year Awards Coming Soon.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6677498727.mp3?updated=1733497589" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-6-24) Hour 2 - Joey Vitale &amp; Drops of the Week</title><description>(00:00-16:57) Joey Vitale joins us for some Cadet on Cadet crime. Joey and Martin argue over the game winning goal in Calgary last night. How long can the Blues sustain this surge?

(16:58-19:13) We're so gonna let Doug Armstrong have it today. Might get a little awkward in the studio.

(19:14-30:47) Doug's down with the Tang. St. Louis's Top 5 songs of 2024. Shaboozey Fatigue. Stick season. The Barry Keoghan Sabrina Carpenter drama. Time to bathe in the brine of The Drops of the Week.

(30:48-44:16) Doug Armstrong joins us in-studio. Was he nervous? How much was timing a factor in the Jim Montgomery move? Never easy firing someone. Letting go of Ken Hitchcock. His longevity as Blues GM.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2614636798.mp3?updated=1733500106" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-6-24) Hour 3 - Doug Armstrong In Studio</title><description>(00:00-20:17) Doug Armstrong hanging out in-studio. The team's messaging and the way it has resonated with fans. His responsibility with the fan base. Does he read comments on message boards? Does the pressure vary based on the city? Players getting booed at the grocery store. His opinion on Kyrou. Fans equating dollars to points. Broberg and Hollway.

(20:18-27:51) Joe Buck texting in advocating for Doug Armstrong as a Member/Guest partner. What was his most difficult conversation with a player? His relationship with The Dewitts and The Cardinals. Losing The Rams galvanized the Blues and Cardinals' fan bases. Ope, Steener's calling.

(27:52-35:49) Really positive response to our conversation with Doug Armstrong. Doug wanted to show him his fantasy team but held back. TLR and Joe Petini. Would Mozeliak or Drink come in and join us?

(35:50-47:03) Hard to handicap this weekend's Conference Championship games. Just know Dan Lanning knows. Maybe we should all go to the Big Ten Championship. Pick Six.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB2487659231.mp3?updated=1733505083" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:05:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-6-24) Hour 4 - Gabe DeArmond &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-14:17) Gabe DeArmond of Power Mizzou joins us to tell which game he's looking most forward to this weekend. Laying out possible CFP scenarios. The week that was for Mizzou recruiting and the transfer portal. The Mizzou quarterback situation. Haynes King &amp; Miller Moss. Mizzou Kansas on Sunday. The Tigers' chances of getting a W.

(14:18-22:15) Jackson's doing some Christmas tree shopping this weekend. Not a toppings man. The Bumble and Hinge scene in Little Rock. Talkin' Gen Z. HVAC talk is an aphrodisiac.

(22:16-28:32) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7601369816.mp3?updated=1733506789" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-9-24) Hour 1 - I Am Nimble, Thank You</title><description>(00:00-25:03) Jackson is peacocking around a bit after that big Tiger win yesterday. Screaming obscenities outside in Brentwood. Can't tell me nothing. Jackson's down on the Braggin' Rights game schedule. Audio of Bill Self talking about the court storming. Audio of Dennis Gates wanting to encourage the crowd to storm the court. No coaching malpractice. Cousin John wants more drops. WAGs at the TMA Christmas Party.

(25:04-38:21) Juan Soto signs with the Mets for $765M. We really need to get Release The Hoosier off the ground and running. Weird sports injuries. Chairman Kurt broke his hand punching the dugout wall in college. Larry Bigbie.

(38:22-1:02:47) Josh Schertz will be in-studio again tomorrow. Doug's gonna sit in the corner. Joined by Tom Hart who was on the call for Mizzou's big win yesterday over Rock Chalk. Kansas didn't play well. Talking about the CFP and the committee's decisions. Booches &amp; Field House. SMU's second half saved them. The committee didn't want to penalize teams for playing in their Conference Championships.

(1:02:48-1:07:09) Will Mizzou be ranked in the next College Basketball poll?

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8413280334.mp3?updated=1733755807" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-9-24) Hour 2 - Chris Kerber &amp; Gabe DeArmond</title><description>(00:00-13:55) Chris Kerber joins us from Edmonton. He's a little skeptical of the gray hotel water. Blues giving up quick goals right after scoring. Ovechkin chasing down Gretzky's goal record. Broberg and Holloway. The inconsistency of Jordan Kyrou.

(13:56-29:44) What's ProdJoe been up to? Wold he come to the TMA Party on Thursday? Frank Haith body pillows. Too intimidated to say hello to Dennis Gates on the quad. So what'd your grandma think? Audio of Aaron Rodgers not thrilled with a reporter's question. Martin's putting on a little sports media seminar. Audio of a WFAN host and John Heyman getting a little banty.

(29:45-33:31) Nothing looks better next to the Yule Log than the TMA logo. Mizzou has only played Iowa once in football in the last 100 years.

(33:32-59:52) Gabe DeArmond of PowerMizzou joins us to talk about the big win at Mizzou arena yesterday. Kansas looked a little panicked yesterday. Mizzou's athleticism was tough for KU. Transfer portal SZN. Miller Moss. Next year's football schedule. Gabe's reaction to the CFP field.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4373075458.mp3?updated=1733760652" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-9-24) Hour 3 - Workin' Blue on Gameday</title><description>(00:00-08:40) The Boys of College Gameday were working blue on Saturday morning. Audio of Nick Saban dropping a word that'll be hard to explain to the children. Audio of Curt Cignetti lobbying for his Hoosiers to host a home playoff game. Cignetti's approval ranking plummeting.

(08:41-17:07) TMA Walrus Number 1 checking in on the phone lines. Controversey in the broadcast booth for the Desmet vs. Nixa state championship game. The announcer was pulled from the booth at halftime because of his Desmet bias.

(17:08-23:03) Reading a poorly written email that was sent in but the sentiment was nice. Describing the EMOTD segment to new listeners who may not be familiar.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8493947285.mp3?updated=1733762675" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 16:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-9-24) Hour 4 - Weekend Wrap Up &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-11:46) You can't tell Jackson nothing. The emails are a little long and graphic this morning. Jackson's Weekend Wrap Up. Pick Six results. Tim's hot tip got Jackson paid off. Jackson got himself a Holiday Tree. Looking at the CFP bracket.

(11:47-19:02) Timothy Chalamet on College Gameday. Was he fed information for his picks? You guys just don't watch Dune and it's a real shame.

(19:03-23:27) $100, who ya got winning the College Football National Championship. God was really on Clemson's side on Saturday.

(23:28-) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1721048337.mp3?updated=1733766440" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 17:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-10-24) Hour 1 - Insatiable vs. Infallible</title><description>(00:00-21:53) A little peek behind the curtains. Global Outage. The insatiable Craig Rutledge. Insatiable vs. Infallible. Going through it today. Yule Tide Positivity. Circling back to the significant other to the Christmas party thing. Drop Mission. Mo at The Winter Meetings. Intention to try. Is Arenado gone? Who's the next Cardinal Hall of Famer?

(21:54-38:23) Audio of Oli Marmol on MLB Network discussing his excitement level going into the year. Comparing it to audio of John Mozeliak from last year. Rightsholder Shuffle. Let's Just Get In MIndset. The Arenado/Cardinals relationship.

(38:24-52:10) Do the Cardinals was their hands before they play? More audio from Mozeliak cracking’ fifth starter jokes. Oli’s response. The Mozeliak Trolling Tour. Come for the baseball, stay for the laughs. St. Louis - The Canada of Baseball. Uniform Jack’s take on the new SLU kits. Michigan coded. 

(52:11-1:03:44) Audio of Steve Cohen talking about his civic responsibility to make the Mets fans happy. Charlie Marlow's thesis on owners. Billions = Good. The competitive balance in baseball.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4969563763.mp3?updated=1733842169" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-10-24) Hour 2 - Half Furry, Half Man, Full Lover</title><description>(00:00-15:35) Is it time to ban Q-Zips under a sports coat? Puffy vest, but not gortex. Housekeeping on air. Battlehawks coach Anthony Becht could be the next West Virginia coach. Would Martz be interested in coaching the Battlehawks? The used sybian market. How do we start a hedge fund? SLU AD is on board with Jackson.

(15:36-25:04) Jackson is answering the phone while Chairman is out tending to business. Caller Buzz calling in with some historical context. Buzz seeping into other 101 shows. Official furry correspondent.

(25:05-35:40) Andy Crouppen is in studio and he's got entrance music. Swifities everywhere. End of The Eras Tour.

(35:41-47:33) Audio of Oli Marmol talking about Jordan Walker. Buying or selling Jordan Walker stock. Cardinals guilty of overcoaching guys. Marmol talking about Contreras moving to first base. Cardinals trending downward defensively. A teasing symposium.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB4927356648.mp3?updated=1733845442" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-10-24) Hour 3 - Buried With The Mic</title><description>(00:00-14:34) We've got some breaking transfer portal news during the break. Williams Nwaneri is likely entering the transfer portal. Audio of Bill Belichick talking about being linked to the North Carolina job. Doug just loves the craft of radio.

(14:35-22:11) John Kelly joins us talking Blues hockey on this Canadian road trip.

(22:12-31:59) Tough time to be an ankle in the NBA. This is how we get behind on the clock. Ryen Rusillo got turned down by Princess Megan. Jackson down on Suits. She'd have been a Sports Media Princess. Sassie Cassie and Cassie Moore. A take disguised. Josh Schertz will be joining us in-studio next.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB7318664730.mp3?updated=1733850820" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 17:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-10-24) Hour 4 - Josh Schertz &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-12:25) Billikens Head Coach Josh Schertz in-studio. He took Doug's chair during the break. Building a program and then sustaining success. Did he ever get impatient looking for bigger schools to come calling?

(12:26-25:09) Coach Schertz talking the Billikens being St. Louis's basketball team. Uniform talk. State of The Billikens. Team searching for its identity. Maximizing the personnel that is available. Balancing a guy like Robbie Avila.

(25:10-36:40) Talking the overall state of college athletics with Coach Schertz.

(36:41-42:00) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3631993661.mp3?updated=1733852392" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 17:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-11-24) Hour 1 - Ginos &amp; Apples</title><description>(00:00-27:25) Is that Pigeon Forge? Jackson's hockey lexicon is coming along. Thommer's TMA bump. Dylan "Take Your Shirt Off" Holloway in OT. The Canucks black jerseys. Is a Canuck a whale? Year End Awards given away tomorrow along with the TMA Christmas party. Polar Express. We nearly lose Doug to a laughing fit. Is Doug trying to hook up with Tim? Feasting on Butt Asses.

(27:26-43:45) Hard to find, hard to hear, hard to stomach. Chairman Steve left a mic drop. Can you drink 13 beers? Audio of Nolan Arenado's agent talking about his client wanting to win. Very cryptic. Seems like Arenado may want out.

(43:46-56:15) The Pestus from Festus (Steven) is on the phone lines and he's fed up with Nolan Arenado. Put him on a rocket and shoot him outta here. But he loves KFC's mashed potatoes and gravy. Ben is up next and he's got a rebuttal for Steven. Creamy cole slaw or NOTHING!

(56:16-1:08:20) They weren't happy with national programming in the 5:00 hour this morning. Chris is on the phone lines and still wants the Cardinals hitting to the right side. Doug's Thanksgiving Pizza.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8687364401.mp3?updated=1733928358" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-11-24) Hour 2 - We Don't Opt Out</title><description>(00:00-8:53) JR coming up and he's got a surprise for us. Mr. Lix is on the phone lines after surprising Tim from behind last night. The incel listeners wouldn't have said hi. Now he's coming after Martin. Happy anniversary Plaza Frontenac. Mount Rushmore of stores at Plaza Frontenac. Is your sister free? Do we have letters?

(8:54-29:10) Jeremy Rutherford is in studio and he's got an in for us at the KFC in Festus. The buffet at KFC. Talkin' about these red hot Blues. Two part questions.

(29:11-41:43) Toosie Slide, Doug. It's transfer portal season and Kenny Dillingham has some thoughts. Jackson's guy Fran Brown from Syracuse has some thoughts but we don't have the audio. Ope, we got it. Jackson wants Fran Brown and Kim English.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8243279043.mp3?updated=1733931695" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-11-24) Hour 3 - Ken Hitchock &amp; Jamie Rivers</title><description>(00:00-10:23) Jackson likes to tease in the dossier. Audio of Ashton Jeanty laying out his case for the Heisman on Micah Parson's podcast. There's a path in the bottom half of that bracket, Doug. Lemme talk to you about this head-to-head. A brief moment of Stephen A. The Rose Bowl sunset.

(10:24-28:56) Former Blues coach Ken Hitchcock joins us from Palm Springs, California. Little warmer than Edmonton. His relationship with Doug Armstrong. His current role with the Blues. Could Hitch be lured back into coaching? His association with Bobby Plager. Does he see the Blues as a playoff team? Jordan Kyrou. Hitch's fine for walking into the wrong room in Philly.

(28:57-37:44) Nolan Arenado has expanded his list of teams he's willing to go to. Angels on the list. When Martin talks, you should listen. What didn't you like about Nolan Gorman's second half?

(37:45-46:23) Jamie RIvers joining us. The boys at TMA are consistent....consistently bad. Massive trip for the Blues. Gotta be happy with the way Joel Hofer has played. Hollywood Holloway. Sleeping on planes.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB8011321434.mp3?updated=1733937237" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-11-24) Hour 4 - Pontoon &amp; Holesknocker &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-11:38) There's a break-in epidemic during Monday Night Football. Audio of the 911 call from someone breaking into Joe Burrow's home. They ransacked the joint. Olivia Ponton, IMG swimsuit model. Jackson's Joe Burrow Swagger. Pontoon and Holesknocker. Was Raul well hung?

(10:39-15:29) Doug's getting that lap ready for tomorrow night. Let's address this situation with the TMA. We've had enough, and enough we've had.

(15:30-00:00) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1611624471.mp3?updated=1733938829" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-12-24) Hour 1 - We're Gonna Sit This One Out</title><description>(00:00-25:15) Hot word play. Tim's dad gave him the numbers. Roll Call Thursday. Martin's dressed like a dock worker. What's a stevedore. TMA End of the Year Awards gonna be handed out in the 10 o'clock hour. Jackson's been ice cold on the definitions. Doug's lap finna get a workout tonight. Chairman's dance card and mouth are wide open for tonight. The Illinois Peninsula.

(25:16-43:00) The Cards really are sitting this one out, eh? Sitting out of the Rule 5 Draft. MLB Network audio discussing the Nolan Arenado situation and the Cardinals offseason and rebuild. Players not waiving their no-trade. The Torey Krug situation. The Real Home of Baseball.

(43:01-1:02:01) Tim's theme song has always been "Rock Me Amadeus." Bill Belichick heading to North Carolina. Surprising Belichick wants to do the recruiting and the Grin &amp; Grab dinners. Why can't he get an NFL job? Oldest NFL coaches. TLR with the Diamondbacks.

(1:02:02-1:04:48) Looking forward to spring when Tim's calves come out. Come out and sit on Doug's lap tonight.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB5872032699.mp3?updated=1734014665" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-12-24) Hour 2 - Bernie Federko &amp; College Sports Tomorrow</title><description>(00:00-10:20) Blues legend Bernie Federko joins us. Dylan Holloway's impact. Team playing with confidence. Getting better in the 5 on 5 play. Bernie's not a fan of the 3 on 3. Tim went to a teasing camp.

(10:21-32:19) The 2025 Mizzou schedule came out. Doug missed the show last night. Is Mizzou allowed to leave Boone County? Is UMass in the SEC? Gotta get those hotel rooms early. Big Hotel is to blame. Lanoris Sellers, come home. Len Perna's 24 team playoff proposal. The College Sports Tomorrow solution.

(32:20-38:54) Martin wants name tags on the listeners tonight. Condolences to the family of Pat McBride. A legend in the St. Louis soccer community.

(38:55-48:11) Big day and we're just getting started. Doug's been receiving offers for bribes for tonight's prizes. Doug's looking forward to hanging with the listeners. The Captain of Team Burkett. Gene Stetschulte. Tim's a cross between Jason Statham and Matt Holliday.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB3614686148.mp3?updated=1734018458" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-12-24) Hour 3 - Sneaky Horny Dolphins</title><description>(00:00-08:21) Today we find out if today is Buck Swope's time. John Talty. Chapel Bill. The Belichick coaching tree. Tim's from the Rich Gould broadcast tree.

(08:22-28:11) Famous Tar Hells to come through our town. Audio from Inside the NBA and Steve Kerr a little upset with a loose ball foul call. Is reincarnation real? Declassified CIA documents may confirm it is, according to Bro Bible. Dolphins are sneaky horny. Audio of the Louisville coach talking about wearing sweats and having a hot wife. The life of a college coach.

(28:12-33:33) Just moments away from announcing the winners of the TMA End of the Year Awards. TMA helped launch Nikki Glaser's career. Doug doesn't watch enough heist movies.

(33:34-42:37) Oh, Doug, it's time. These awards changed Chairman Kurt's life just two years ago. The nominee for TMA Rookie of the Year: Thanks, Dad. Mother, this is Daniel. Caller Chris. My Cousin Vinny. Bob Wagon. Fan Page Member of the Year: Kevin Miller, Bang Bang Niner Guy, Cletus, John Cusick.

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB1976598507.mp3?updated=1734024498" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TMA (12-12-24) Hour 4 - End of the Year Awards &amp; EMOTD</title><description>(00:00-11:05) Our End of the Year Awards Gala continues. They're already angry about some of the winners. Texter of the Year Nominees: Arbor Day, Manut Bol Eligible, Brian Haenchen, Carlos Spicy Weiner, &amp; Flip Wilson. Caller of the Year: Caller Chris, Steve from Festus, Caller Janet, Mr. Lix, Steve in Wildwood, &amp; Caller Buzz. E-Mailer of the Year: Buck Swope, JV Golf Coach, Kevin Miller, Tunnels 12K, Ghost of Gangster Pete's Hat, Shooter McGavin.

(11:06-13:33) Democracy died today and elections have consequences.

(13:33-21:17) Feed Jackson your anger. Drop of the Year: Ruin Me. Pan Coins. Ok Gaslight Girl Boss Gatekeep. Roof Daddy. Anger over indifference. And it's time....Listener of the Year. Los Ween, Tiny Pee Pee, Mr. Smith, Mr. Lix, JVGC, Tucker, TMAWNo1, Caller Jen, BBB, Swope, and John Skorcz.

(21:17) E-Mail of the Day

Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/HUBB6034087578.mp3?updated=1734026038" length="0" type="audio/mpeg"/><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>